<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>jare.cloud</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Jare&#039;s Cloud</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 07:42:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-CA</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.3.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Now ANYONE can Make Money Online with My FREE Retail Arbitrage Tool!</title>
		<link>/2020/01/25/now-anyone-can-make-money-online-with-my-free-retail-arbitrage-tool/</link>
				<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 07:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insanely Marketable Business Ideas]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=455</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[For anyone who doesn&#8217;t know, #Retail #Arbitrage is #buying #low and #selling #high from different retail outlets or #platforms. I]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>For anyone who doesn&#8217;t know, #Retail #Arbitrage is #buying #low and #selling #high from different retail outlets or #platforms. I created an #aggregator that gets items via search and compares them for similar titles and shows the % and $ #gains, from #aliexpress to #ebay, for the top 300 results on each site. </p>



<p>This tool is #free! </p>



<p>Tool: <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://arb.jare.cloud/" target="_blank">http://arb.jare.cloud/</a></p>



<p>Backstory: <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/16/amazon-ebay-aliexpress-retail-arbitrage-as-a-service/" target="_blank">https://jare.cloud/2020/01/16/amazon-ebay-aliexpress-retail-arbitrage-as-a-service/</a> </p>



<p>Youtube of it in development: <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f7Pj7q3hXsU" target="_blank">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f7Pj7q3hXsU</a> </p>



<p>Opensource Github repository: <a href="https://github.com/DunnCreativeSS/arb.jare.cloud">https://github.com/DunnCreativeSS/arb.jare.cloud</a></p>



<h1>arb.jare.cloud</h1>



<p><a href="http://arb.jare.cloud/">http://arb.jare.cloud/</a></p>



<h2><a href="https://github.com/DunnCreativeSS/arb.jare.cloud#changelog"></a>Changelog:</h2>



<p>0.01.01: initial commit. Live. Works with Aliexpress and Ebay. Earns thru affiliate $.</p>



<p>0.01.02: Changed the logic so that ebay and ali objects are unique to sessions. This increases performance if there is more than one concurrent user from an unusable platform.</p>



<p>0.01.03: Added Git link to result page. Added Google Analytics tracking.</p>



<h2><a href="https://github.com/DunnCreativeSS/arb.jare.cloud#todo"></a>Todo:</h2>



<ol><li>Get Amazon affiliate sales.</li><li>Implement Amazon affiliate API for third aggregate source.</li></ol>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-64-1024x431.png" alt="" class="wp-image-457" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-64-1024x431.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-64-300x126.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-64-768x324.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-64-1536x647.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-64.png 1901w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2>The Pitch</h2>



<p>You can secure surebet, arbitrage income by searching whatever floats your boat and seeing how similar the titles match for these goods on Ebay and Aliexpress, For free! See those links there? Those are affiliate links &#8211; meaning that if you do find a way to earn big money buying low and selling high from one marketplace to another, I earn a percent of those sales. Want to sell hundreds of these items? Buy hundreds, then! Want to wait until your sale has gone through on Ebay, then buy the item with the proceeds and ship it directly to the customer? Chances are you&#8217;ll be doing it through my same referral link.. and we all win!</p>



<h2>Next Steps</h2>



<p>I want to include Amazon Affiliate API results to compare against these two. There&#8217;s a chance for more ways for people to arbitrage &#8211; buy on ebay, sell on Amazon? Alas, Amazon&#8217;s Affiliate API is only open for business after you sell three items on their affiliate platform. Boo!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-65-1024x632.png" alt="" class="wp-image-458" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-65-1024x632.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-65-300x185.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-65-768x474.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-65.png 1334w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2>How Does It Compare?</h2>



<p>Other retail arbitrage tools will charge you hundreds a month for membership. They also have fancy tools to help you bulk import selections, but my revenue model comes from those little affiliate links &#8211; so the bulk import tools aren&#8217;t necessarily conducive. Some people might prefer paying a subscription to get access to these premium tools &#8211; others would prefer cut costs and use a free tool to find their sure-fire winning merchandise!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Non-Technical Intro to How Brave Browser Protects You, Your Data, and Your Privacy!</title>
		<link>/2020/01/23/a-non-technical-intro-to-how-brave-browser-protects-you-your-data-and-your-privacy/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brave]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=433</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this post in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud! Ready to make the change, to become a more private and]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-60.png" alt="" class="wp-image-434" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-60.png 778w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-60-300x168.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-60-768x429.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 778px) 100vw, 778px" /></figure>



<p><a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/23/a-non-technical-intro-to-how-brave-browser-protects-you-your-data-and-your-privacy/">View this post in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<p>Ready to make the change, to become a more private and safe person on the entangled corners of the internet? <a href="https://brave.com/jar444">Download the Brave browser now</a>!</p>



<p>Does anyone else get horrified when the manipulation by the richest 1% is more obvious than not? An ad that implies your family will happily sit around a table and be cordial if you buy the right product for thanksgiving dinner? There&#8217;s literally rooms of people comparing the most effective ways to prey on your insecurities, win your trust and position things at you. Your worst enemies are indeed the products and services you recommend to your friends.</p>



<p>Are you new to Brave and the BAT ecosystem? Did you know you can earn &#8211; up to $100s US Dollars a month &#8211; using the Brave browser instead of your other alternatives? <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/21/the-insane-earning-potential-of-the-brave-browser-in-bat-and-how-to-turn-it-into-a-business/">Learn how much Brave can generate for you by browsing ads that don&#8217;t abuse your privacy or personally identifiable information</a>!</p>



<p>The obvious methods of influence and manipulation aside, it&#8217;s important to consider the less noticeable ways that an internet marketing company &#8211; like GOOGL, FB &#8211; track you, consume and potentially sell your data. There&#8217;s not only the giants to worry about, but countless smaller and more boutique agencies or government entities whose aims vary &#8211; both in their ends and in their means.</p>



<p>When you visit a website or a mobile app, they usually use some form of cookie or other internet trickery to track you beyond your stay on that site. These internet trackers will follow your browsing history, and your habits to assess new and better ways to target ads at you &#8211; to increase their effectiveness when someone tries to sell you something, increasing their overall Return On Investment for the advertiser. Should some companies see you browsing certain content, they&#8217;ll employ a strategy known as consumer re targeting to show you their ads again &#8211; more frequently &#8211; on other locations, like on your Facebook news feed. They&#8217;ve found you to be previously interested to some (measurable&#8230;) degree, and it&#8217;s far cheaper to acquire or keep you as a customer now than the average internet population.</p>



<p>The Brave browser automagically blocks all of these trackers around the internet. Now, as you&#8217;re browsing on your desktop or mobile, big marketing and small marketing companies can no longer exploit you for your personal data and habits. What&#8217;s more is that the more nefarious of these actors will actively sell or give away your information to the highest bidder (and all the other bidders), meaning you get all those spam and other marketing emails we&#8217;re used to receiving from people we never subscribed to when we gave our info to a site, platform or app &#8211; even when we&#8217;re trying to do the world some good and donate to a charitable cause, for instance.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-61.png" alt="" class="wp-image-436" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-61.png 1005w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-61-300x194.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-61-768x497.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-61-850x550.png 850w" sizes="(max-width: 1005px) 100vw, 1005px" /></figure>



<p>What&#8217;s more is that the Brave browser &#8211; by default &#8211; blocks all third-party ads around the internet. We&#8217;ve all witnessed them &#8211; when a site or platform shows you an ad from an online marketing strategy that isn&#8217;t from that same, original party, and redirects you off-site when you click the ad. What&#8217;s &#8216;bad&#8217; here isn&#8217;t necessarily the ad itself &#8211; after all, money makes the world go round &#8211; but it&#8217;s the way in which the ads and the clicks track your data and your personally identifiable info. For instance, when you click an ad off of Facebook (or Twitter, etc&#8230;) they&#8217;ll take on a variable to your request. This variable identifies you as an individual clicker on the internet, for these social giants to further use and abuse you and your data &#8211; selling to you better, more effectively, and with more of a winrate. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-62.png" alt="" class="wp-image-438" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-62.png 977w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-62-300x47.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-62-768x121.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 977px) 100vw, 977px" /></figure>



<p><a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/">Read the details of the Brave browser</a> and how they&#8217;re restructuring the rewards ecosystem of the internet into a Better Web &#8211; in my first-hand initial experience!</p>



<p>All in all, when marketing techniques are obvious they&#8217;re easier to ignore or approach reasonably. When these strategies are subliminal and behind-the-scenes, they&#8217;re much more easily affecting you and those close to you. The answer is to upgrade your browsing experience.. now!</p>



<p>Want to learn about new articles in tech and being a madman? Subscribe to my mailing list here: <a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL">http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</a>  </p>



<p> <br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Building an AI &#038;&#038; Everything You Need to Know About Artificial Intelligence</title>
		<link>/2020/01/22/building-an-ai-everything-you-need-to-know-about-artificial-intelligence/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 04:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coindex]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=425</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this post in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud! With Google&#8217;s execs offering warnings on regulating AIs and thinktanks predicting]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-28-1024x573.png" alt="" class="wp-image-427" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-28-1024x573.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-28-300x168.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-28-768x430.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-28.png 1086w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/22/building-an-ai-everything-you-need-to-know-about-artificial-intelligence/">View this post in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<p>With <a href="https://thenextweb.com/artificial-intelligence/2020/01/20/sundar-pichai-offers-a-cryptic-warning-against-over-regulating-ai/">Google&#8217;s execs offering warnings on regulating AIs</a> and thinktanks predicting artificial intelligence will take over all sectors of labor, and <a href="https://searchhrsoftware.techtarget.com/news/252477189/Impact-of-AI-on-jobs-goes-on-the-presidential-campaign-trail">AI stealing jobs having an effect on the campaign trail</a> &#8211; it&#8217;s as important as ever to know everything you need to know about artificial intelligence.</p>



<p>What are the pitfalls of AI? What are they really well suited at doing? How do they work?</p>



<p>AI &#8211; traditionally &#8211; take a bunch of data (a training set) and figure out ways to approach problems by being rewarded or reprimanded points, which affects the fitness of a model. By telling the AI what we want, we can achieve the results we&#8217;re after. It&#8217;s then applied to new, raw data, with the idea that it can predict an outcome or achieve an objective.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://images.idgesg.net/images/article/2018/10/ai_virtual-monitor_circuitry_binary_robot_robotic-100777427-large.jpg" alt="Image result for ai"/></figure>



<p>Artificial Intelligence &#8216;learns&#8217; better ways to approach a problem, and modifies its approach to do it better. It&#8217;s naturally suited to things like recognizing faces in images or <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/22/how-to-build-a-winning-tool-for-sentiment-analysis-of-twitter-data/">identifying emotions or sentiment in text &#8211; even if it&#8217;s expressed sarcastically</a>.</p>



<p>When does it fail? AI can be trained on too large of a dataset or with too many rewards/detriments, which is called &#8216;overfitting&#8217; the model. This would mean that the programming becomes too familiar with the older data, which looks better on paper but in reality causes it to be less accurate when it&#8217;s thrown to the wolves with new, live data &#8211; and it performs worse than a less &#8216;fitted&#8217; model might have. Boo!</p>



<p>As Chief Liquidity Officer for Coindex Labs, we&#8217;re employing a new and novel approach to AI that is naturally resilient against overfitting. <a href="https://jare.cloud/2019/11/07/we-used-evolutionary-ai-and-novel-search-to-build-a-money-making-machine/">This is a neuro-evolutionary  AI</a> &#8211; meaning that it not only learns on a training set based on +1/-1, it also has competing datasets in a generation that see who can perform better &#8211; and they pass down certain genetic traits when they&#8217;re successful to the next generation&#8217;s population, for them to compete again. We&#8217;re first applying it to new &amp; novel markets for trading financial assets, then transferring those lessons to more traditional markets, and finally going to use the research to solve basic human needs.</p>



<p>What does this mean for you? While artificial intelligences become smarter and achieve more and more objectives, they&#8217;ll be able to replace human labor in more and more sectors. While this might not necessarily put you out of the job any time soon, you should certainly ensure that your kids know enough code to be dangerous in a New World Economy where the wage earners are those teaching the AIs to do things that &#8211; in the 2010s &#8211; millions of wage earners used to accomplish. Case in point is self-serve checkouts &#8211; or even in the generation before, Automatic Teller Machines. <a href="https://newsexaminer.net/food/mcdonalds-to-open-restaurant-run-by-robots/">There are even whole McDonalds restaurants without any human staff</a>!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://newsexaminer.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/McRobot-810x553.jpg" alt="New McDonald’s In Phoenix Run Entirely By Robots"/></figure>



<p>To stay ahead of the curve, you can encourage kids to take part in logic, code and maths. While this might not seem exciting, the right programs will focus a kid&#8217;s attention on the fun that can be had with code: I was introduced to C++ in the 90s and immediately started to build an RPG for my friends and I to play. This is the kind of introduction, positioning and framing that allow kids to associate their favorite activities with this new &#8211; and life-long &#8211; challenge.</p>



<p>With all change and even change that negatively affects many comes new and interesting opportunities. The advances in AI and associated new and novel tech like augmented reality, virtual reality, and whole ecosystems popping up surrounding the artistic need for these communities, products and services will never be able to be fully replaced by the machine. Someone in the future will be able to completely provide for themselves and their families by creating fun artistic pieces that manifest in a digital world. Indeed, people already are!</p>



<h2>A Plug (or Two)</h2>



<p>Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<p>Want to learn about new articles in tech and being a madman? Subscribe to my mailing list here:&nbsp;<a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL">http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</a> </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 3 Ways: How to Influence People and Make Friends (and How Maslow Theory Applies)</title>
		<link>/2020/01/22/top-3-ways-how-to-influence-people-and-make-friends-and-how-maslow-theory-applies/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 03:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=421</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Read this post in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud! Do you need motivation? Learn how to influence people and make]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="/2020/01/22/top-3-ways-how-to-influence-people-and-make-friends-and-how-maslow-theory-applies/">Read this post in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-27.png" alt="" class="wp-image-422" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-27.png 700w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-27-300x171.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></figure>



<p>Do you need motivation? Learn how to influence people and make friends with this quick cheat-sheet, straight from the mind of someone who&#8217;s almost a narcissist! </p>



<p>No, wait, before you click off thinking &#8216;yeah yeah edgelord&#8217; consider this: the people who know most about how to manipulate people are those with Cluster B Personality disorders &#8211; like narcissism or, in my case, anti-social personality disorder. You can <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/why-schizophrenia-is-the-most-under-represented-of-all-the-death-sentences/">read more about my various diagnoses here</a>, and how I&#8217;ve managed to overcome most of the disadvantages of having the mind of a maniac.</p>



<p>Regardless of how you look at it, the act of influencing is indeed a form of manipulation. Your goal is to drive a result, and that result is making friends &#8211; and your means are all positive, helpful, and adding value. There&#8217;s nothing nefarious going on here, just a silly &#8216;bad word!&#8217;</p>



<h2>1. Anticipate Their Needs</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://www.investorincustomers.com/images/blog/cf873c91edf95f87026e60b7b73f5c9e__033c/zoom334x304z50000cw668.jpg?etag=2ba284b2f6a6ae13a7bdfd7270ab49ad" alt="Image result for anticipate needs"/></figure>



<p>Maslow&#8217;s hierarchy of needs teaches us that people require certain things in a certain order in order to achieve fulfillment or happiness. People worried about being bombed usually aren&#8217;t focusing on reaching their inner potential with the cello. If you can get a grasp on the evolution of someone&#8217;s needs, you can help them achieve these goals &#8211; and together, you&#8217;ll conquer more barriers faster. They&#8217;ll be grateful.</p>



<p>What is Maslow&#8217;s hierarchy? <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/21/maslovs-hierarchy-of-needs-universally-applied-for-1st-world-countries-anyways-heres-a-wellness-pyramid/">Click here to read my other article on happiness pyramids</a>, and how they apply more generally and in first-world populations. In reality, everyone&#8217;s Maslow hierarchy of needs is individual and their own experiences, desires and barriers apply.</p>



<p>For instance, at school or work there might be subjects where you&#8217;re stronger, and the person or people you&#8217;re looking to influence might be lacking. In this kind of situation, you can lend your know-how in small and maybe even subliminal ways &#8211; if you lend a hand, chances are it&#8217;ll gain you some affection.</p>



<h2>2. Create Opportunities to Share Time</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://inspiringtips.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/couple-spending-quality-time.jpg" alt="couple spending quality time"/></figure>



<p>This one is a no-brainer. A long time ago a friend was giving me her opinion of winning the affection of someone of her same sex, and recommended that I maximize the amount of time I&#8217;m around that person. The theory was if I was there more often, and able to talk and listen more often, then that person would become more attached to me and I would eventually become someone of more value to them. It was true! </p>



<p>Following Maslow, we could find or anticipate the activities these people or this person likes to or may like to partake in. We can recommend they join us &#8211; whether it be groceries or some other basic human need, or something higher on the happiness pyramid like chess club. Be creative! Everyone&#8217;s heard &#8216;want to join me for a coffee?&#8217; but not many people hear &#8216;let&#8217;s go ziplining!&#8217; that often.</p>



<p>The internet is awash with ideas on how we can <a href="https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-e-g-most-efficient-way-to-spend-time-with-someone-with-the-aim-of-deepening-a-friendship-or-relationship">spend more time with people to deepen friendships</a>, or to <a href="https://inspiringtips.com/ways-to-spend-quality-time-with-your-partner/">spend more time with our partners</a>. As with anything else on the internet: take what you read with a grain of salt, and apply your own reasoning and logic on the tips and tricks you read. It&#8217;s your life, remember! </p>



<h2>3. Listen More, Speak Less</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://www.slickwords.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/09/they-listen-more-when-you-speak-less-63059.png" alt="Image result for listen more speak less"/></figure>



<p>This piece of advice is helpful across segments of anyone&#8217;s life. It seems that a generational problem we&#8217;re facing is that people will often listen enough to form an opinion and then &#8211; as if they like to hear their own voice &#8211; will interrupt, speak up and move the conversation off the original speaker&#8217;s point. Try to avoid this! According to Maslow theory, we can identify which of their tiers of needs are being met and what their more critical problems are. Someone trying to find housing is more concerned about meeting that basic need than they are about finding a partner. Focus on the problems that resonate with the person, and actively listen &#8211; find the points and passion in their story &#8211; and think before you respond!</p>



<p>Interested in how people with psychoses think? You can read a creative <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/14/how-do-people-with-mental-health-illnesses-like-schizophrenia-or-other-psychoses-think/">piece about symptomatic thoughts</a> I authored here!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Build a Winning Tool for Sentiment Analysis of Twitter Data</title>
		<link>/2020/01/22/how-to-build-a-winning-tool-for-sentiment-analysis-of-twitter-data/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coindex]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=368</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[See this post in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud! Today, we&#8217;ll summarize my continued efforts to build a sentiment analysis]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/22/how-to-build-a-winning-tool-for-sentiment-analysis-of-twitter-data/">See this post in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<p>Today, we&#8217;ll summarize my continued efforts to build a sentiment analysis tool. This tool is using the Twitter API to consume 97 different Twitter handles, that provide Crypto trading signals. This method can easily be applied to traditional markets &#8211; effectively capitalizing on new and highly lucrative means for trading stocks online. We&#8217;ll be reviewing the opportunities to add a neuro evolutionary AI to our bot. You can review the <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/automated-crypto-trading-bot-to-buy-pump-and-dump-sentiment-signals-from-twitter/">first iteration of this series on Twitter sentiment bots here</a> on my blog.</p>



<p>When it comes to classical issues facing sentiment analysis applications, it&#8217;s important to consider how algorithms work. If we&#8217;re using a Natural Language Processing tool to rank the individual words in a phrase based on positive, neutral and negative sentiment, wouldn&#8217;t a product review like &#8216;All these wonderful new features! Although none of them work!&#8217; confuse the machine? Words like &#8216;none&#8217; are the true sentiment &#8211; being negative &#8211; but the overall feeling the programming gets from the message involve words like &#8216;wonderful&#8217; &#8216;new&#8217; &#8216;work.&#8217; This would yield a false positive in the ranking and scoring of phrases. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-14-1024x329.png" alt="" class="wp-image-370" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-14-1024x329.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-14-300x96.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-14-768x247.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-14.png 1110w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>What we need is a way for the computer to overcome this sarcasm in the tweets. Certain <a href="https://medium.com/dair-ai/detecting-sarcasm-with-deep-convolutional-neural-networks-4a0657f79e80">AIs are capable of establishing context</a> by ranking sentiment, emotion and personality. We&#8217;ll then apply this when we analyze Twitter data. As <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jarettdunn/">Chief Liquidity Officer of Coindex Labs</a>, I have access to a new and novel way to train datasets and apply resulting genomes on configurations &#8211; using an AI that&#8217;s naturally resilient to over-fitting.</p>



<p> AI has other advantages when it comes to sentiment analysis, like identifying unique opinions that may otherwise get re-hashed, re-worded, and delivered in a separate &#8216;original content&#8217; tweet. This doesn&#8217;t really apply as much in our trading bot, as we&#8217;re limiting our input tweets to those 97 Twitter accounts, but with a larger dataset this is critical. To identify the true emotion of the Internet at large, we&#8217;d need a way to filter out people (and even computers) with accounts that are used to artificially manipulate people&#8217;s sentiment bots. It&#8217;s &#8216;a feint within a feint within a feint,&#8217; as Muad&#8217;Dib would have said!</p>



<p>Once we&#8217;ve created our new model and use it to weed out the bad apples, our analysis of sentiment will be far more effective. As far as sentiment scores go, this tweet that my Twitter bot picks up on is ahead of the bell curve &#8211; but, on manual inspection, it looks as though it&#8217;s a joke rather than actual sentiment one way or another.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-58.png" alt="" class="wp-image-369" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-58.png 815w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-58-300x99.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-58-768x253.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 815px) 100vw, 815px" /></figure>



<p>Entries like these should be ignored in the final product. I&#8217;ve toyed with the idea of human intervention before acting on a given signal, but the delays involved would mean that the average trader would miss 70% of the swing. Ideally, the bot would act on the &#8216;good&#8217; signals within a matter of seconds or minutes &#8211; beating the overall shift in the markets when others pick up on the sentiment, before everyone exits. This is how the goldmoney is made.</p>



<p>This is what a profitable tweet looks like, and currently our win/lose ratio is far higher than 50% &#8211; combined with a creative trailing takeprofit, we can establish an edge on the market:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-59-1024x190.png" alt="" class="wp-image-372" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-59-1024x190.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-59-300x56.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-59-768x143.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-59.png 1361w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://media.discordapp.net/attachments/666371834102677565/667705444596187136/SmartSelect_20200117-122805_TabTrader.jpg?width=367&amp;height=658" alt=""/></figure>



<p>The next steps are to build out the AI&#8217;s training set with loads of tweets to run analysis on. These will then serve as a benchmark with which to apply to forward-testing data with live, real incoming tweets based on our followed list. Then, our evolutionary part of the neuro evolutionary AI will create competing sets of genomes with the different input variables, and the best-performing genome will become the champion set that runs the live trader. The next generation of genomes will then (likely, by and large) perform better vs the previous generation, and a new champion might be selected. </p>



<p>Are you more interested in how to automagically grow your Twitter following? Check out this article I wrote on <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/21/7-days-creating-a-twitter-growth-service/">consuming the Twitter API to hack your account&#8217;s growth</a>! All in all, we have a clear plan for how our analysis of Twitter for fun &amp; profit will continue to become more sophisticated and the win/lose ratio will increase significantly. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Maslow&#8217;s Hierarchy of Needs: Universally Applied (for 1st World Countries, anyways), Here&#8217;s a Wellness Pyramid!</title>
		<link>/2020/01/21/maslovs-hierarchy-of-needs-universally-applied-for-1st-world-countries-anyways-heres-a-wellness-pyramid/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=304</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this post in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud! In a given Maslow&#8217;s Hierarchy of Needs you&#8217;ll find a tiered]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/21/maslovs-hierarchy-of-needs-universally-applied-for-1st-world-countries-anyways-heres-a-wellness-pyramid/">View this post in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<p>In a given Maslow&#8217;s Hierarchy of Needs you&#8217;ll find a tiered pyramid that starts with you being fed, and climbs  thru safety then belongingness and love, esteem, and finally &#8211; at the highest tier &#8211; self-actualization.</p>



<p>A brief search on your favorite search engine will find images like so:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/maslow-5.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-358" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/maslow-5.jpg 900w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/maslow-5-300x223.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/maslow-5-768x572.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" /></figure>



<p>What I&#8217;d like to suggest is a Maslow Hierarchy for people in first-world countries: where we take safety for granted. What do we need in our Wellness Pyramid in order to be, well, well?</p>



<p>On our first tier, we&#8217;ll find rest and liquids. Any doctor worth his weight in gold (or bitcoin) will tell you that the tricks to becoming well are rest and liquids. Without sleep, we&#8217;d eventually turn insane and then die &#8211; and without water, we&#8217;d die within days. Days! Interested in bitcoin? <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/">Read here how you can turn your daily browsing into potentially hundreds of dollars a month</a> &#8211; as advertisers pay YOU for viewing your ads, all the while blocking dangerous 3rd-party ads (like YouTube ads).</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-54.png" alt="" class="wp-image-359" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-54.png 981w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-54-300x210.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-54-768x537.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 981px) 100vw, 981px" /></figure>



<p>Stay hydrated!</p>



<p>On our next tier we&#8217;ll find the other stuff that medical professionals recommend for anyone, regardless of their physical or mental ailment (barring extremes, like catatonic schizophrenia): Exercise, and healthy diet!</p>



<p>We can control a whole bunch of our brains worst and best tendencies if we practice these two essential parts of our lifestyles. <a href="https://thesleepdoctor.com/2017/05/22/benefits-exercise-sleep/">With proper and regular exercise we not only sleep better</a>, but we feel better and we live longer. Fact! With healthy diet we can make sure that we keep our body&#8217;s needs in check and also feed our brains the vitamins, minerals and all that jazz that it sorely needs in order to think better, <a href="https://www.theemotionmachine.com/how-to-use-diet-to-impact-positive-thinking/">think more positively</a> and think more often.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-55.png" alt="" class="wp-image-360" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-55.png 999w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-55-300x196.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-55-768x503.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-55-120x80.png 120w" sizes="(max-width: 999px) 100vw, 999px" /></figure>



<p>Now, to be well we need to be stress-free. The #1 way to be stress-free is to distract yourself: like <a href="https://www.verywellmind.com/the-importance-of-hobbies-for-stress-relief-3144574">to spend time with hobbies reduces stress</a>, jobs, a gamenight with family or the internet&#8217;s world of memes and joy can all help you spend the time. These distractions give you little doses of dopamine throughout the day that you can expect and count on. Down this road also lies dangerous, negative solutions like drugs and alcohol giving you that same release &#8211; so take care, and try to surround yourself with activities that attribute to your overall success rather than detract from them. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-56.png" alt="" class="wp-image-361" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-56.png 999w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-56-300x206.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-56-768x527.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 999px) 100vw, 999px" /></figure>



<p>What crowns our new wellness and happiness pyramid? </p>



<p>Fulfillment.</p>



<p>We&#8217;re all trying to be heard, to be cared about and to have an effect on someone&#8217;s life, way of thinking, or their own wellbeing &#8211; whether they be close to us, or the greater population at large. Some of us take up blogging &#8211; some of us, journalism &#8211; and some of us just want to make sure we have some kind of everlasting imprint on our kids, friends or other loved ones.</p>



<p>This is quintessential to your wellbeing and health when all else is taken for granted.</p>



<p>As you grow older, you may notice that your mobility and autonomy start slipping away. You&#8217;ll no longer be able to drive, to garden, to sing &#8211; and you may find yourself less and less responsible for other people&#8217;s schedules, days, and otherwise find yourself proving less and less of a use.</p>



<p>If you&#8217;re young now: enjoy your autonomy and mobility. Enjoy the ways in which you influence others and win friends.</p>



<p>If you&#8217;re getting older: try and find new and exciting ways to have an effect on the world (like blogging, writing a book, or otherwise expressing yourself in a low-effort way. Did you know you could speak to your internet browser, and have it type out what you&#8217;re saying? It&#8217;s called Speech-to-Text!). </p>



<p>Are you interested in blogging, or are you already blogging, but want to feel a little bit extra dopamine when you&#8217;re expressing yourself? <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/20/publish0x-allowing-rewards-for-content-with-their-own-funds-re-distribution-of-wealth-defined/">Sign up for Publish0x as an author and get rewarded by people tipping you</a> &#8211; the tips come from their own funds, and the tipper earns a custom % of the tip, too, so everyone wins!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-57.png" alt="" class="wp-image-362" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-57.png 986w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-57-300x212.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-57-768x543.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 986px) 100vw, 986px" /></figure>



<p>And that concludes our Wellness Pyramid, a Maslow Hierarchy applied to everyone living where the basics are taken for granted!</p>



<h2>A Plug (or Two)</h2>



<p>Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<p>Want to learn about new articles in tech and being a madman? Subscribe to my mailing list here:&nbsp;<a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL">http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</a> </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Insane Earning Potential of the Brave Browser in BAT, and How to Turn it Into a Business</title>
		<link>/2020/01/21/the-insane-earning-potential-of-the-brave-browser-in-bat-and-how-to-turn-it-into-a-business/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 20:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brave]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=353</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[New to BAT and Brave? Here&#8217;s an article I wrote describing the Brave ecosystem&#8217;s value proposition &#8211; how you can]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-embed-reddit wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-reddit"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
    <blockquote class="reddit-card" >      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/er28xp/i_havent_sent_any_bat_but_theres_a_disconnect/?ref_source=embed&amp;ref=share">I haven&#8217;t sent any BAT, but there&#8217;s a disconnect from what&#8217;s in my wallet and what I&#8217;ve earned. Where do I find my missing BAT?</a> from      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/">BATProject</a>    </blockquote>    <script async src="https://embed.redditmedia.com/widgets/platform.js" charset="UTF-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-354" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1.jpg 378w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-300x259.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 378px) 100vw, 378px" /></figure>



<p>New to BAT and Brave? Here&#8217;s an article I wrote describing the Brave ecosystem&#8217;s value proposition &#8211; <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/">how you can earn money by browsing with a safer, more private browser</a>!</p>



<p>As highlighted in the above article, some users in the US are earning as much as $107 USD / month / browser for their BAT-enabled Brave browser. </p>



<p>This led me to DuckDuckGo some prices for low-tier Chromebooks and Android devices:</p>



<p> <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/er653q/has_anyone_thought_about_brave_hardware/">https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/er653q/has_anyone_thought_about_brave_hardware/</a>  </p>



<h1>Has anyone thought about Brave hardware?</h1>



<p>I think a Chromebook series running Brave&#8217;s Chromium wouldn&#8217;t be too difficult to create &#8211; legalities aside, all you need to do is enable dev mode and replace the browser, or boot it into a Linux crouton build with Brave as the default browser in a Linux build&#8230; with DDG as default search, to boot&#8230; if you figure in Brave Rewards over a year (or 5yr) the price of a given chromebook line becomes almost negligible, or 0.</p>



<p>Wouldn&#8217;t businesses die over the opportunity for 0-cost or revenue-generating hardware?<strong> </strong></p>



<p>$155.99 CAD Chromebooks galore:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.shopbot.ca/m/portable-devices-laptops?q=chromebook&amp;sort=price" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank">https://www.shopbot.ca/m/portable-devices-laptops?q=chromebook&amp;sort=price</a></p>



<p>My 3-day BAT earnings: 0.24 USD, 0.314 CAD</p>



<p>1-day average: 0.1046 CAD<br>365 days/yr: $38.21<br>Break-even: 4.08 yr</p>



<p>&#8230;. that&#8217;s infinite money to these people that underwrite machines&#8230;</p>



<p>The community had some thoughts about a link between Eich and KaiOS, and even linked to a method for <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/unixporn/comments/eqkx5g/lxde_summer_is_coming_d/">removing Chrome from Chromebooks</a>.</p>



<p>What I think this allows the tech-savvy entrepreneur to do is a few things:</p>



<ol><li>You can buy a line of Chromebooks at a discount price<br>For as cheap as $156, and even cheaper in bulk, Chromebooks are the most interesting subject for this idea as all of their activity happens within the browser inside the device. There are no desktop apps.</li><li>Set their browser to use Brave Chromium<br>This is fairly technical, but someone can replace the browser on Chromebook with Brave-flavored Chromium.</li><li>Resell these laptops to any person that uses the internet<br>The logic is in the money&#8230;</li><li>Along with their new, lightweight and cost-effective machine is the Brave Browser<br>It&#8217;s faster, more private, and more secure!</li><li>Which will earn them BAT for viewing ads as Brave Rewards<br>Within the first day, the investment will start paying itself off&#8230;.</li><li>And so, over time, their investment in the hardware goes down<br>Each month there&#8217;s a new Brave Rewards payment that &#8211; if you apply it to the cost of acquisition &#8211; lowers the barrier to entry for computing!</li><li>If the case is true of certain geos earning >$100 per month in BAT, then the ROI for your new machine is &lt;2 months<br>If I told you you could have a new computer every 2 months, wouldn&#8217;t you be interested? Wouldn&#8217;t you become a return customer??</li><li>In the case of larger organizations that require many dozens, hundreds of machines, they can get a loan for a working web browsing device (or even larger, heftier Windows-based machines) and after a few months start earning income on top of the cost of the machine<br>This is where the big money is. If an organization can acquire net-free pr net-earning hardware in their regular line of business, that would have otherwise been a cost, wouldn&#8217;t they be inclined to?</li><li>This allows a huge advancement in the way people look at equipment financing<br>Net-free or net-revenue generating equipment = $$$.</li><li>Which, in turn, helps the adoption of BAT and Brave<br>More users, more ads, more creators and publishers!</li></ol>



<p>The real questions are how do we create a version of Brave that allows a small- medium-sized organization limit the use of the Chromium browser, ie. block certain sites &#8211; or those other than a whitelist? I&#8217;m sure they can achieve this effect on the network level, though! Also, how do we create institutional-level Brave rewards accounts, so that the individual user on the individual browser isn&#8217;t able to redeem or move around Brave tokens &#8211; rather, they&#8217;re sent to one larger chest?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Some Recent Reddit Posts of Mine: Microtipping, the Future of Social Rewards, Driving Crypto Adoption, and Code for a 1st Party Ad Rotator</title>
		<link>/2020/01/21/some-recent-reddit-posts-of-mine-microtipping-the-future-of-social-rewards-driving-crypto-adoption-and-code-for-a-1st-party-ad-rotator/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 19:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brave]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=350</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Microtipping: Future of Social Rewards? With a minimum BAT tip of 1 BAT, there&#8217;s been some discussion around the interwebs]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-embed-reddit wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-reddit"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
    <blockquote class="reddit-card" >      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/eryy2e/microtipping_future_of_social_rewards/?ref_source=embed&amp;ref=share">Microtipping: Future of Social Rewards?</a> from      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/">BATProject</a>    </blockquote>    <script async src="https://embed.redditmedia.com/widgets/platform.js" charset="UTF-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<h1>Microtipping: Future of Social Rewards?</h1>



<p>With a minimum BAT tip of 1 BAT, there&#8217;s been some discussion around the interwebs of instituting a custom # BAT tip.</p>



<p>This would allow, as one user mentioned, the ability to microtip a fraction of a BAT at the same time they save a tweet for later &#8211; which would benefit everyone. Whereas, at present, a whole BAT might not be sustainable for each time I&#8217;d want to share some love &#8211; a fraction of a BAT would.</p>



<p>With Uphold as the present custodial license for holding and transferring BAT and BAT rewards around the Brave ecosystem, does this work super easily &#8211; comparing it to microtipping BAT on the Ether blockchain? Is Uphold off-chain, allowing any number of smaller transactions? Would future custodial solutions that aren&#8217;t requiring KYC allowing us to also microtip in this fashion?</p>



<p>Microtipping (along with the ease of use of the Tip function on social sites that Brave allows) would restructure the way people use (and think about) social interaction online.</p>



<p>+1</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-reddit wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-reddit"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
    <blockquote class="reddit-card" >      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/erx4j4/example_of_driving_bat_and_crypto_adoption_thru/?ref_source=embed&amp;ref=share">Example of Driving BAT and Crypto Adoption thru Responding to LinkedIn Promotion</a> from      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/">BATProject</a>    </blockquote>    <script async src="https://embed.redditmedia.com/widgets/platform.js" charset="UTF-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<h1>Example of Driving BAT and Crypto Adoption thru Responding to LinkedIn Promotion (since removed by mods)</h1>



<p>Preface: Lisa was an outstanding connection request on LinkedIn I confirmed maybe 24 hrs ago. She has 10 mutual connections, and 500+ total.</p>



<ul><li>Hi, I am Lisa, Web Development Manager and I work with experienced IT professionals who are into: * Create a New Website * Redesign a website? * Website Design and Development * Update Your Existing Website * E-Commerce Solutions If you are interested, then I can send you our Price list, company information and an affordable quotation with the best offer. Sincerely, Lisa</li><li><strong>TODAY</strong>&nbsp;1:33 AM</li><li>We are really looking forward to receiving your answer so that we can get to any final conclusion Best Lisa<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/1f4f7.png" alt="📷" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></li><li>Jarett Dunn 12:30 PM</li><li>Hey, no thanks!</li><li><strong>Jarett Dunn</strong>&nbsp;12:34 PM</li><li>To drive revenues, you should let your website proprietors know above Brave browser and BAT:&nbsp;<a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank"><strong>https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter</strong></a>/ Since verifying myself as a Brave publisher a/o 4 days ago I&#8217;ve earned ~11 BAT ($2.20 USD) in donations to my different platforms. That might not seem like much, but for someone with a larger audience or following it can serve as an additional revenue stream. This is compared to my&nbsp;<a href="http://medium.com/" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank"><strong>Medium.com</strong></a>&nbsp;earnings for the last ~12 days, at $1.80 USD.&nbsp; As a Brave affiliate you can also earn up to $7.50 USD for browser installations that remain installed after 30 days. Since putting up that Brave article that I linked you to, I have 7 downloads and 4 installs &#8211; this could yield up to $30 USD in affiliate income, over 4 days of referrals so far.</li></ul>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-reddit wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-reddit"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<div class="reddit-embed" data-embed-media="www.redditmedia.com" data-embed-parent="false" data-embed-live="false" data-embed-uuid="ea01df20-3c87-11ea-892c-0e5220be9fd7" data-embed-created="2020-01-21T19:55:03.246117+00:00"><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/ers2v6/interesting_data_about_medium_writer_earnings_and/ff6ar36/">Comment</a> from discussion <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/ers2v6/interesting_data_about_medium_writer_earnings_and/">h3xadecimal2&#8217;s comment from discussion &quot;Interesting data about Medium, writer earnings and usage &#8211; I&#8217;m convinced BAT would be way better if we had 250MAU&quot;</a>.</div><script async src="https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Comment: I agree with <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.reddit.com/u/O1O1O1O/" target="_blank">u/O1O1O1O</a> &#8211; because Brave rewards users with advertiser&#8217;s funds to then pay (or not..) their favorite content producers, then every user eventually has a BAT or a few to redistribute &#8211; and everyone wins. Brave also allows content creators/publishers of many times &#8211; theoretically any platform that includes an API where we can decide if one user&#8217;s view on a profile is for a specific other user. This discounts sites like Facebook, Minds, but is already beautifully connected on Twitter and here on Reddit. This is potentially far more views, far more publishers and far more ad spend than Medium.<br></p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-reddit wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-reddit"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
    <blockquote class="reddit-card" >      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/erapuj/1st_party_ad_rotator/?ref_source=embed&amp;ref=share">1st Party Ad Rotator</a> from      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/">BATProject</a>    </blockquote>    <script async src="https://embed.redditmedia.com/widgets/platform.js" charset="UTF-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>In the next iteration of my 1st party ad service, I created Javascript code that randomly chooses one of two ads to display in the header of each of the pages on my blog. This Brave-friendly ad displays content about Brave or Publish0x. It also detects mobile displays and gives a smaller banner for mobile.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s genius in it&#8217;s simplicity. . . I half want to re-package this into a WordPress plugin for other Brave content creators on WP.</p>



<p>Here&#8217;s some code:</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>if (/Android|webOS|iPhone|iPad|iPod|BlackBerry|BB|PlayBook|IEMobile|Windows Phone|Kindle|Silk|Opera Mini/i.test(navigator.userAgent)) {

	var random = Math.random(1)

	if (random &lt; 0.5){

	$('#masthead').prepend('&lt;a href="&#91;https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/](https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/)">&lt;img src="&#91;https://jare.cloud/468.png](https://jare.cloud/468.png)" />&lt;/a>')


}
	else {

$('#masthead').prepend('&lt;a href="&#91;https://jare.cloud/2020/01/20/publish0x-allowing-rewards-for-content-with-their-own-funds-re-distribution-of-wealth-defined/](https://jare.cloud/2020/01/20/publish0x-allowing-rewards-for-content-with-their-own-funds-re-distribution-of-wealth-defined/)">&lt;img src="&#91;https://jare.cloud/468-2.png](https://jare.cloud/468-2.png)" />&lt;/a>')	
}

}

else {

	var random = Math.random(1)

	if (random &lt; 0.5){

	$('#masthead').prepend('&lt;a href="&#91;https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/](https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/)">&lt;img src="&#91;https://jare.cloud/728.png](https://jare.cloud/728.png)" />&lt;/a>')

}



	else {
$('#masthead').prepend('&lt;a href="&#91;https://jare.cloud/2020/01/20/publish0x-allowing-rewards-for-content-with-their-own-funds-re-distribution-of-wealth-defined/](https://jare.cloud/2020/01/20/publish0x-allowing-rewards-for-content-with-their-own-funds-re-distribution-of-wealth-defined/)">&lt;img src="&#91;https://jare.cloud/728-2.png](https://jare.cloud/728-2.png)" />&lt;/a>')
	}

}

})
</code></pre>



<p>Check it out: <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://jare.cloud/" target="_blank">https://jare.cloud/</a></p>



<p>Check out this fellow Redditor&#8217;s extension of this idea:   <a href="https://gist.github.com/thefallofbecause/26022a05836a2990d99df80b94494e34">https://gist.github.com/thefallofbecause/26022a05836a2990d99df80b94494e34</a> <br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>7 Days Creating a Twitter Growth Service</title>
		<link>/2020/01/21/7-days-creating-a-twitter-growth-service/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 17:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brave]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=234</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[See this post in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud! Interested in a way to utilize Crypto Pump n Dump tweets]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/21/7-days-creating-a-twitter-growth-service/">See this post in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<p>Interested in a way to utilize Crypto Pump n Dump tweets &#8211; for fun &amp; profit? <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/automated-crypto-trading-bot-to-buy-pump-and-dump-sentiment-signals-from-twitter/">Check out this article I wrote on making mad stacks on Twitter sentiment</a>!</p>



<h2>Day 1</h2>



<p>I had a thought: if some of my traffic comes from Twitter to Medium and my blog, wouldn&#8217;t I want to maximize this &#8211; in a hands-free fashion? I&#8217;ve done this before &#8211; some of my accounts had 5k+ followers in a few months. I had bought a Google sheets templated sheet doc with Twitter integrations, and bam it flew. I later created a Github repo for a hackathon starter fork where I put in all these juicey follow, retweet, favorite logics into a prettier UI.</p>



<p>The benefit of the hackathon starter is that I can login via oauth &#8211; meaning the app has api keys, but the user does not. We&#8217;re all used to oauth login &#8211; do you want to login using gmail/facebook/twitter? Redirect to platform, redirect to site, success!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-21.png" alt="" class="wp-image-236" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-21.png 876w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-21-300x245.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-21-768x627.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 876px) 100vw, 876px" /></figure>



<p>I resurrected my gsheet today and started the magic. I made some edits to the code: specifically we want to follow, retweet and favorite. Hooah!</p>



<p>Let&#8217;s set our benchmark&#8230;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-20-1024x303.png" alt="" class="wp-image-235" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-20-1024x303.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-20-300x89.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-20-768x227.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-20.png 1032w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2>Day 2</h2>



<p>Well, we have some initial results! Twitter app on my phone has been blowing up. Let&#8217;s analyze the results so far&#8230;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-22.png" alt="" class="wp-image-237" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-22.png 1009w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-22-300x98.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-22-768x250.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1009px) 100vw, 1009px" /></figure>



<p>We&#8217;ve gained 13 followers in 24 hours! That might not sound like much, but it&#8217;s a full 10.8% increase over where we were. Even better than that, the amount of followers vs the amount of people I&#8217;ve followed &#8211; an important metric on Twitter &#8211; has actually increased! </p>



<p>I did notice that the UI on Twitter wouldn&#8217;t let me follow people. This is dangerous, as if we try to follow too many people and get errors because our account is limited, Twitter may ban the account. We remove the follow directives, and increase retweets and likes.</p>



<h2>Day 3</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-23-1024x364.png" alt="" class="wp-image-238" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-23-1024x364.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-23-300x107.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-23-768x273.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-23.png 1048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Wow! A further 12% increase in followers! Our ratio increased again, too. That&#8217;s fantastic news&#8230; I&#8217;m greedy now, and so I&#8217;m going to increase the retweets and favorites from one per search term per hour up to 3. This should accelerate this monster&#8230; let&#8217;s wait and find out!</p>



<p>UPDATE: 3/4 the way through Day 3, let&#8217;s take a look at results. Just because I hate waiting. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-24.png" alt="" class="wp-image-239" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-24.png 977w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-24-300x119.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-24-768x306.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 977px) 100vw, 977px" /></figure>



<p>Well, that strategy appears to be working! No longer is my account limited, and also my followers increased a further 12% on top of the last 12% and 10% &#8211; an increase in rate. When we check in in another 6ish hours we&#8217;ll hopefully see that the data for the 18th reflect a massive increase.</p>



<p>What&#8217;s even better is that my follower vs followed ratio is increasing SIGNIFICANTLY. Because I&#8217;m no longer following people using the bot &#8211; although I did some manually, messing up stats &#8211; this ratio is now EXPLODING. </p>



<p>Twitter limits your ability to follow new people after you follow 5k, and if this ratio is too too deep then everyone will assume you&#8217;re digging for followers and your rate of follow backs will decrease. D&#8217;oh!</p>



<h2>Day 4</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-33-1024x761.png" alt="" class="wp-image-295" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-33-1024x761.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-33-300x223.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-33-768x571.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-33.png 1045w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption>Twitter: Free Money</figcaption></figure>



<p>Social traffic and engagements are literally free money if you monetize your visitors in any way, or put a dollar value on them.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-48-1024x249.png" alt="" class="wp-image-339" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-48-1024x249.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-48-300x73.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-48-768x187.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-48.png 1050w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Plus &#8211; we&#8217;ve seen a massive increase in both followers and the ratio! Booya!</p>



<h2>Day 5</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-49-1024x259.png" alt="" class="wp-image-340" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-49-1024x259.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-49-300x76.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-49-768x194.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-49.png 1035w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>The followers and ratio continue their upwards trend, although slowing down&#8230;</p>



<h2>Day 6</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-50-1024x285.png" alt="" class="wp-image-341" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-50-1024x285.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-50-300x84.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-50-768x214.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-50.png 1041w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Oh! I know why my followed is still trending up. My code had a hard-coded &#8216;followback&#8217; feature. Let&#8217;s turn that off!</p>



<h2>Day 7</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51-1024x680.png" alt="" class="wp-image-342" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51-1024x680.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51-300x199.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51-768x510.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51-120x80.png 120w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51.png 1035w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Looking good&#8230;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-52.png" alt="" class="wp-image-343" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-52.png 1022w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-52-300x97.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-52-768x248.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1022px) 100vw, 1022px" /></figure>



<p>We&#8217;ve now accomplished the 2nd-highest daily increase in % follower/followed ratio. Hooah!</p>



<p>That concludes our 7-day adventure into automating Twitter engagements, for fun and profit. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-53.png" alt="" class="wp-image-344" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-53.png 337w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-53-300x87.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 337px) 100vw, 337px" /></figure>



<p>We&#8217;ve seen an 85% increase &#8211; nearly double! In followers over 7 days, and 30% increase in follower/followed ratio. These are huge numbers, indicative of a healthy and growing Twitter following.</p>



<p><a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/">Learn how to monetize your new Twitter following with Brave Browser and BAT tokens</a>! Better yet? It blocks all third-party ads! AND protects your privacy!</p>



<h2>A Plug (or Two)</h2>



<p>Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<p>Want to learn about new articles in tech and being a madman? Subscribe to my mailing list here:&nbsp;<a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL">http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</a> </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Publish0x: Allowing Rewards for Content With Their Own Funds! Re-Distribution of Wealth, Defined!</title>
		<link>/2020/01/20/publish0x-allowing-rewards-for-content-with-their-own-funds-re-distribution-of-wealth-defined/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 08:19:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Brave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Publish0x]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=327</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this article in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud! Sign up for Publish0x and start rewarding your favorite content &#8211;]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p> <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/20/publish0x-allowing-rewards-for-content-with-their-own-funds-re-distribution-of-wealth-defined/">View this article in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud</a>! </p>



<p><a href="https://www.publish0x.com/?a=olejNWvejN">Sign up for Publish0x and start rewarding your favorite content</a> &#8211; without paying a cent! You also get paid!</p>



<p>As one of my first ads delivered through the Brave browser was for Publish0x, I had originally been quick to dismiss it. On later inspection &#8211; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/er28xp/i_havent_sent_any_bat_but_theres_a_disconnect/">when I figured out I could 2.5x my BAT rewards by switching my Brave Rewards from 2 ads/hr to 5</a> &#8211; I found I could earn BAT and DAI for blogging&#8230; or reading!&#8230; my favorite content on their platform.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-43.png" alt="" class="wp-image-328" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-43.png 965w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-43-300x160.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-43-768x411.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 965px) 100vw, 965px" /></figure>



<p>This, together with syndication for my blog and juicey backlinks, allowed me to quickly sign up and find that indeed &#8211; I was able to tip every few minutes and choose what % of that tip I wanted to keep for myself.</p>



<p>Win-win-win! The money comes from their big ol&#8217; community chest of possible rewards, spanning many coins.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-44-1024x259.png" alt="" class="wp-image-329" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-44-1024x259.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-44-300x76.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-44-768x195.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-44.png 1042w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-45-1024x164.png" alt="" class="wp-image-330" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-45-1024x164.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-45-300x48.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-45-768x123.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-45-1536x246.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-45.png 1567w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>In such a way, I&#8217;ve earned BAT, HYDRO and DAI already on the platform &#8211; by voting on 4 articles. Genius!</p>



<p>This is the definition of redistribution of wealth. The communist&#8217;s dream, in a capitalist application!</p>



<p>Hint: they also sport a fancy Ambassador program &#8211; allowing you, too, &#8216;Earn&nbsp;<strong>5%</strong>&nbsp;of every tip generated by your referrals using the tipper at the bottom of each article. This includes both the tip to the author and the amount claimed by your referral.&#8217;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-46-1024x414.png" alt="" class="wp-image-331" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-46-1024x414.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-46-300x121.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-46-768x310.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-46-1536x621.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-46.png 1640w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Check it out! My buddy signed up and tipped a writer.. and I earned, before I even finished this promotional post! That&#8217;s free money begetting free money. I&#8217;m sorry, but you NEED to sign up now! It&#8217;s basically a DAI/BAT/ et cetera faucet for content you&#8217;d enjoy regardless!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-47-1024x338.png" alt="" class="wp-image-335" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-47-1024x338.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-47-300x99.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-47-768x253.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-47-1536x506.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-47.png 1568w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Ready to get paid for reading whatever floats your boat? <a href="https://www.publish0x.com/?a=olejNWvejN">Sign up for Publish0x now</a>!</p>



<h2>A Plug (or Two) (or Three)</h2>



<p><a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/">Read more about how Brave rewards you to browse, while protecting your privacy online!</a></p>



<p>Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<p>Want to learn about new articles in tech and being a madman? Subscribe to my mailing list here:&nbsp;<a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL">http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</a> </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
