<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>jare.cloud</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Jare&#039;s Cloud</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 02:31:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-CA</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.3.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>In Simple Terms: Risk-Free (Free Money!) Futures Trading by Leveraging Options Strategy</title>
		<link>/2020/01/14/in-simple-terms-risk-free-free-money-futures-trading-by-leveraging-options-strategy/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 01:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=176</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this content in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud! Introduction In short: using an options strategy, we can trade any]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1575/1*wQN_FGI4ff7a26rJBS45Og.jpeg" alt=""/></figure>



<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/14/in-simple-terms-risk-free-free-money-futures-trading-by-leveraging-options-strategy/">View this content in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<h1 id="4def">Introduction</h1>



<p>In short: using an options strategy, we can trade any sideways futures strategy with absolutely 0 risk. Price movements up, down, or sideways all yield profitable results. Markets go bullish, bearish, sideways or do a dance — you win no matter what!</p>



<p>Awhile ago, on my Hackernoon, I penned this technical article on&nbsp;<a href="https://hackernoon.com/risk-free-futures-market-making-by-hedging-long-straddle-options-pc1236bl" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Risk-Free Futures Market Making by Hedging Long Straddle Options</a>. In this article I will strive to deliver the points discussed in that first article to a less technical audience — who might be left scratching their heads.</p>



<p>What I mean by ‘sideways’ is that the futures strategy wants to earn the best it can when the markets are neither upwards (bullish) or downwards (bearish).</p>



<h1 id="3b67">Options Strategy</h1>



<p>Places like Deribit via&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/c1bc81c4789b?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Deribit</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/c1bc81c4789b?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Deribit</a>&nbsp;(yes, two separate accounts) and Binance’s JEX platform via&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/57600910a883?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Binance</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/590e572dc6e7?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Miko Ilas</a>&nbsp;allow you to buy and sell BTC (and other coins…) options. An option is a deriviative, meaning that it’s value is derived from the underlying asset but not necessarily correlated — there’s loads of other ‘deriviatives,’ like futures, and that’s why we can trade with so much more leverage on options and futures — they’re not representing the actual asset, but an ‘derived’ idea.</p>



<p>When you buy a call and a put you’re buying the right or ability to buy or sell (respectively) an underlying asset for the specified quantity and price sometime in the future. In European options, this point in the future is only on the day the options expire — or when they run out of time. Note that I’m not obligated to buy or sell — I simply have the right to, should I want to (or it makes financial sense). This means that (if I pay enough money, and someone is there to sell me this option) I should be able to buy the ABILITY to buy BTC for $1 sometime within the next month. That’s probably going to be a very lucrative deal, right? That’s why this option would be worth A LOT of money, and probably astronomically expensive to buy. The price at which you may buy or sell the underlying in the future is called ‘the strike.’</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/2118/1*_Ox5mK27cfvVSMM-VMvZhA.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>In the above screenshot, we see the calls and puts for BTC should the underlying index reach a price of $6750 on expiry or $6500 on expiry. Not that the price of the calls — the right to buy the asset — increases as the strike price decreases, while the cost of puts is decreasing along with it.</p>



<p>On the other side of potential prices for BTC on 24 Jan 2020 (the date the options expire, or end), we see the opposite effect.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/2128/1*90q1y2_UhEPPSN60AfcKew.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Calls are cheaper, puts are more expensive.</p>



<p>Anyways, to get to my point — if you buy both a call and a put with two different strike prices at the same expiry, then you can do so for&nbsp;<em>VERY&nbsp;</em>cheap.</p>



<p>What happens if the price remains around the same? The value of both the call and the put will reduce over time (as their distance to expiry is one of the things that gives them value — the uncertainty and possibility of volatility in this case means that they’re worth more now than they are tomorrow). Eventually, by expiry, they expire worthless.</p>



<p>What happens if the price goes up? The value of the put goes down, and the call goes up. The more the price moves upwards, the less the put is worth — all the way down to worthless — while the call increases in value&nbsp;<em>EXPONENTIALLY</em>.</p>



<p>What happens if the price goes down? The&nbsp;<em>OPPOSITE</em>. One $0 and the other gains value&nbsp;<em>EXPONENTIALLY</em>.</p>



<p>This options strategy is called a ‘long straddle,’ and it essentially means you’re betting on the price moving up or down by a large amount. It’s handy in markets you expect to be volatile — like stocks on days they report earnings or, much less likely in practice, you’re aware of someone’s unannounced merger and acquisition. What this also means is that cryptocurrencies — arguably the most volatile of the assets — allow an options trader to reap in the benefits of a highly volatile market.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1680/1*YnzM0Mta90lpGCtm-wzjKg.jpeg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>For instance, we know that Bitcoin’s mining yields will be half what they have been for awhile sometime in the not-so-distant future. We can surely bet that the price will either go up or down&nbsp;<em>drastically</em>&nbsp;in a short period of time. Take out a long straddle!</p>



<p>Anyways, the above article I wrote on Hackernoon goes on to say that you can use some smart guys math to guesstimate the potential future ‘fair value’ for these long straddles. There’s a few smart guys to choose from, I chose Black Scholes. Now we have a programmatic way to say ‘hey if price moves 5% then I can expect my long straddle to be worth x% more,’ their math model solves for x.</p>



<p>Now, where long straddles lose money is when the markets are sideways. I actually found this strategy when I was dreaming up ways to have less risk with my sideways market trading strategies — be they market makers, for instance, they lose money when the markets go up and down and they’re caught holding a bag of $$ that takes away all my yields.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/974/1*OeEhtZQFJ88ZqAvFzTlVjQ.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>These Market Makers make $$ when the markets are sideways, by earning on $ fees and $ spread. On Deribit,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/94b52ae5502e?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">BitMEX</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/b7ff9821c710?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bybit</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/724240b60d22?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bitfinex</a>&nbsp;Kraken and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/316a1a75d708?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinFLEX</a>&nbsp;they give you REBATES on fees you can earn when people trade against your orders. When you add liquidity to their exchanges, they split their earnings with you — sometimes 50/50!</p>



<p>This means that if I was to know that my max exposure is (how many positions of what sizes I might hold if the markets go one way or another) in $$ and if the market moves y% at 6x leverage, I then liquidate at y%. This is normally bad, but…</p>



<p>I can buy the exact (or almost exact) number puts/calls I need to make sure that if price goes up OR down by any % all the way up to liquidation % then I’m making money on my long straddle when I’m losing money on my Market Maker.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1096/1*f-8ikqYVWMFzCSgXAEthng.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>This applies to any strategy that generates yield when sideways, not just market makers. Say price goes up 5% in a day and my sideways strategy liquidates, and out of my puts and calls one of them is $0 and the other one increased in value&nbsp;<em>A WHOLE HECK OF A LOT.</em></p>



<p>The only way this doesn’t work is if your sideways strategy doesn’t earn more than what you lose when you hold onto the long straddles and their value goes down over time…</p>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization — where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;!!</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Money-Making Decentralized Finance #DeFi Applications</title>
		<link>/2020/01/14/top-money-making-decentralized-finance-defi-applications/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 01:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Github]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=172</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this content in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud! Preface Today we’ll discuss some of the top Decentralized Finance (DeFi)]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1134/0*6V4x3aCeDeW4pZJ9.jpeg" alt=""/></figure>



<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/14/top-money-making-decentralized-finance-defi-applications/">View this content in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<h1 id="cfa9">Preface</h1>



<p>Today we’ll discuss some of the top Decentralized Finance (DeFi) applications that exist, serving people in a trustless manner around the world.</p>



<p>What do I mean by trustless? Given Ether’s immutable (cannot change) smart contracts, the behavior of the money moved around DeFi is such that it cannot be stolen, hacked, lost or misappropriated. Moreover, to earn the word ‘trustless,’ I don’t have to put my trust into a given person or organization — instead, I trust the underlying technology of the contracts they’ve devised. It’s trustless!</p>



<p>I’ve separated the following doc into four sections, comparing the platforms in each: Trading, Borrowing, WBTC Borrowing, and Lending.</p>



<h1 id="f070">Trading</h1>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image.png" alt="" class="wp-image-180" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image.png 892w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-300x139.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-768x356.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 892px) 100vw, 892px" /></figure>



<p>With up to 5x leverage available to traders, dydxprotocol at&nbsp;<a href="http://dydx.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">dydx.exchange</a>&nbsp;and folks like&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/b3d17ffd3219?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Antonio Juliano</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/67f0a6970a7c?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Zhuoxun Yin</a>&nbsp;bring you a beautiful night-mode interface that allows you to trade some of your favorite assets. Some people — especially those burned by Mt. Gox or other exit scams — are risk-averse to what we call ‘counterparty risk.’ What this means is that some people would much rather have less single points of failure when it comes to the custody of their money — and now we can even trade with leverage on platforms like dydx, so who needs centralized exchanges and their bankster owners?</p>



<p>Dydx lets you borrow, too, but we’ll discuss that more in detail in a future section of this article.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1358/1*b6kUKIB8rLIy9QBa_KE7hw.png" alt=""/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1264/1*Bb6NKV_XMMXdEZkAw1_cfQ.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>I do like how the people at <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://fulcrum.trade/" target="_blank">fulcrum.trade</a> (their parent org: bZx) separated their trading interface from their borrowing interface. We’ll have a closer look at their not-for-margin-trading borrowing interface in a later section, but the fulcrum.trade interface lacks some of the leverage available to dydx — although that negative is helped by having a broader selection of coins.</p>



<h1 id="2015">Borrowing</h1>



<p>With a resounding set of achieved milestones and growth,&nbsp;<a href="http://compound.finance/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">compound.finance</a>&nbsp;and some of the team&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/54f6f223cd12?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Robert Leshner</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/8808a762900f?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Calvin Liu</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/42c8b7010550?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Jayson Hobby</a>&nbsp;have been building another Ether unicorn to add to our growing list.</p>



<p>With millions under management, and a wide variety of coins to choose from to use as collateral, Compound provides a unique opportunity in traditional financial history. It’s apparent that we can over-collateralize loans in crypto against stablecoins and be long those cryptos while getting spending money for the time being — the bullish attitude we have towards these cryptos says that their underlying growth in equity value will outperform the interest rates we’re paying on our stablecoin loans. Boom, we’ve just earned ‘free-ish’ crypto!</p>



<p>Wait, though, this really only applies to Ether and the Ethereum tokens listed on Compound At Time of Writing, and doesn’t appear to apply to WBTC? I really had hoped to diversify my collateral I’m holding to maximize the upwards potential of both DeFi and The King of Coins, $BTC!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/2019/1*ar7ch_ZSKslofPWRdvGJQg.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>(See, a ‘Collateral Factor’ of 0% means we can’t use Wrapped BTC as a collateral coin).</p>



<p>Whatever are we to do?</p>



<h1 id="1990">Borrowing Against WBTC</h1>



<p>Like I’d mentioned above,&nbsp;<a href="http://bzx.network/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">bzx.network</a>&nbsp;has the tools&nbsp;<a href="http://fulcrum.trade/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">fulcrum.trade</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="http://torque.loans/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">torque.loans</a>, and some of the people working wonders like&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/e65fe39afe1d?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Nick Sawinyh</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/7c5899852965?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Kyle J Kistner</a>&nbsp;or their team account here&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/c84b634c7ca3?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">bZx Team</a>. We discussed fulcrum.trade above and hinted at the existence of torque.loans — as a flipside of the same coin, instead of lending and borrowing under-collateralized loans for the purpose of margin trading (a la dydx) we can lend and borrow over-collateralized loans for the purpose of hedging, or whatever other purpose you had in mind (a la compound)!</p>



<p>Simply load up your MetaMask or other wallet, select the token to receive, change your collateral to WBTC and — oh, spoke too soon! Found an error among all tokens when selecting WBTC as collateral.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/2489/1*7FQA5lzB_AAtgsnIVkEJsg.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Wonder if there’s a bug bounty…</p>



<p><em>Soon</em>! You’ll be able to achieve all that diversification and goodness I was speaking about earlier.</p>



<p>EDIT: 15 minutes after my Tweet to bZx and everyone else, at some ungodly hour in the morning that it is right now:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1104/1*APv0pSO6xIE8ozzlL9sNvA.png" alt=""/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1134/1*AGRk-fkbzxjZQ2RZ7dhrsw.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>When was the last time your banks answered the phone that quick?</p>



<p>EDIT AGAIN: It looks as though the bug was on my side, and it’s working fine now that I’ve restarted my machine trying to take a screencast for their team — all is good in the hood, and likely no cause for alarm! I’m going to leave this little diversion in here about the bug-that-could-have-been, because it illustrats how prompt, friendly and helpful bZx’s team are.</p>



<p><a href="https://twitter.com/jarettdunn/status/1216982964233437185" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Check Out the Chat and Follow My Twitter</a>!</p>



<h1 id="85de">Lending</h1>



<p>What do diversified assets and Albert Einstein have in common?</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1181/1*KlOBylBk6AmLAj9PNKQO1w.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Einstein knew that being on the winning side of compound interest would free people — and diversifying your portfolio is step #1 to earning consistent returns. All our moms (or indeed dads, or indeed people-y people) told us ‘don’t put all your eggs in one basket,’ right?</p>



<p>Here’s where stuff gets interesting. Because the three solutions noted above are all open-source and allow and encourage people to develop tools to add to their utility,&nbsp;<a href="http://staked.us/?pid=fr5BC09Vgc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">staked.us</a>&nbsp;of course at&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/2e226f754735?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Staked</a>&nbsp;developed their tool&nbsp;<a href="https://staked.us/v/robo-advisor-yield/?pid=fr5BC09Vgc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Robo Advisor for Yield</a>. Edit: Shoutout to their man&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/94138e7bc2b8?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Devan Purhar</a>, who handles all my support tickets I’ve had on their GitHub (one example link and ensuing conversation to follow). Much appreciated!</p>



<p>What’s it do?</p>



<p>At present, it indexes Compound, dydx, and fulcrum.trade and gives you the best rate among each of them — meaning that if you were to have Robo Advisors for Eth, USDC, DAI and SAI, you’d be earning the best yields for four different assets (one might moon! And: eth staking, coming soon!) — maybe more different assets in the future:&nbsp;<a href="https://github.com/Stakedllc/robo-advisor-yield/issues/5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://github.com/Stakedllc/robo-advisor-yield/issues/5</a>&nbsp;at any given point.</p>



<p>They’ve used on-chain, open-source solutions in the keeping with crypto spirit and in order to bolster the offerings of the participant protocols. This means that they add a layer to the tech without adding a party to be considered when thinking about counterparty risk — the trust is still in the tech (which has all been thoroughly audited, be sure)!</p>



<h1 id="050e">Conclusion</h1>



<p>So head on over to&nbsp;<a href="http://staked.us/?pid=fr5BC09Vgc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">staked.us</a>, check out their platform where you can earn returns on staking PoS coins, but more importantly check out their&nbsp;<a href="https://staked.us/v/robo-advisor-yield/?pid=fr5BC09Vgc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Robo Advisor for Yield</a>&nbsp;today. You can mint your own RAYs and begin the journey to doubling your crypto, too!</p>



<p>Looking to trade undercollateralized loans, on the blockchain and without a third party? Check out some of the other solutions, like dydx.exchange and fulcrum.trade.</p>



<p>Looking to borrow funds against your crypto? I’d recommend compound.finance or torque.loans.</p>



<p>DeFi is here to stay — banking the unbanked — let the games commence!</p>



<h1 id="0d3a">Bonus 1: Nuo.Network</h1>



<p>Nuo.network (with an encouring team including team account&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/d834ca07a5ac?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Nuo Network</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/29f0b8f49104?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Varun Deshpande</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/2e63d860a40d?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Siddharth Verma</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/a48f2610a12d?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Praneet Sinha</a>&nbsp;allows you to lend and borrow — including WBTC — and margin trade using non-custodial addresses, like the other contenders in this list.</p>



<p>Why didn’t Nuo make the original list?</p>



<p>Their smart contracts aren’t public — meaning that&nbsp;the interface to build on nuo.network is controlled by their team, and doesn’t allow folks to create additional value by plugging pieces together and offering something brand new — like&nbsp;<a href="https://staked.us/v/robo-advisor-yield/?pid=fr5BC09Vgc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">staked.us’s Robo Advisor for Yield</a>&nbsp;does.</p>



<p>However, the Staked team reassures us that they’ve been in touch with Nuo’s and that — pending an upcoming update — the code will be public and the joys of Nuo can be introduced into the Robo Advisor for Yield.</p>



<p>Check more details on this post I made outlining Nuo as a possible way to earn yield (and earn yield on WBTC) on Staked’s RAY:&nbsp;<a href="https://github.com/Stakedllc/robo-advisor-yield/issues/5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://github.com/Stakedllc/robo-advisor-yield/issues/5</a></p>



<h1 id="3258">Bonus 2: Uniswap</h1>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1389/1*h9q1b-UntQQAeNW0MQfWMw.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>People like&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/5b6f44a990f8?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Callil Capuozzo</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/ec7001b3c11f?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hayden Adams</a>&nbsp;have been building Uniswap: Heralded as Ethereum’s unicorn — Uniswap allows a whole bunch of interesting features. These include swapping Ether tokens and paying a small fee all the way up to submitting your own new exchange (token) to the network and having all your friends increase your token’s liquidity.</p>



<p>What happens (as far as I know, and in Laymen’s) is, as I undertand it, a liquidity pool I can put funds into so that market makers and other parties can execute trades at leverage or for ‘free-ish.’ These funds then produce yield as the market makers have paid fees which gets added to the pot, then available for the liquidity providers to later withdraw. I may be incorrect in my understanding or I may have forgotten something.</p>



<p>Check out an idea I had to generate yield by COMBINING Compound and Uniswap (I know, insane) here:&nbsp;<a href="https://github.com/Stakedllc/robo-advisor-yield/issues/3" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://github.com/Stakedllc/robo-advisor-yield/issues/3</a></p>



<p>And see an idea of mine for integrating Uniswap in their own traditional sense into Staked.us’s RAY here:&nbsp;<a href="https://github.com/Stakedllc/robo-advisor-yield/issues/6" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://github.com/Stakedllc/robo-advisor-yield/issues/6</a></p>



<h1 id="524f">Disclaimer</h1>



<p>No, I don’t work for Staked.</p>



<p>Yes, I am an affiliate and will earn affiliate commissions if you sign up using my links.</p>



<p>No, there are no other affiliate links in this doc — I gave an honest and unbiased opinion here, not affiliate spam <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/1f642.png" alt="🙂" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>



<p>You can be Staked.us affiliated, too!</p>



<p>After signing up for Staked.us (here’s the full url of my affiliate link:&nbsp;<a href="https://staked.us/?pid=fr5BC09Vgc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://staked.us/?pid=fr5BC09Vgc</a>) , you’ll have access to the Partners area:&nbsp;<a href="https://staked.us/stake/partners/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://staked.us/stake/partners/</a></p>



<p>The author is, however, employed by Coindex Labs — leading us nicely into a plug:</p>



<h1 id="cfd7">A Plug</h1>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization — where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;!!</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>How do people with mental health illnesses like schizophrenia or other psychoses think?</title>
		<link>/2020/01/14/how-do-people-with-mental-health-illnesses-like-schizophrenia-or-other-psychoses-think/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 01:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=168</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this article in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud! He stared out from behind his eyes wide shut. In front]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/722/0*xYsewcQ1HGRJq-Us" alt=""/></figure>



<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/14/how-do-people-with-mental-health-illnesses-like-schizophrenia-or-other-psychoses-think/">View this article in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud!</a></p>



<p>He stared out from behind his eyes wide shut. In front of him, displayed like countless myriad millions television screens laid one next to each other, were the lives of everyone he’d ever lived — partially, completely, not at all or fully.</p>



<p>He focused on one where he was little Jane being picked up and twirled by her dad. In ecstasy, Jane laughed in joy and giggled in fear as she twirled higher and faster. These are the moments she would remember with elation for the rest of her life, years after her father died in a tragic motorbike accident that could have been avoided — years after Jane has her own kids, twirling them with the same gusto every opportunity she’d had.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/39/0*qdoq097kM6cGT8MP.jpg?q=20" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Focusing again, James was Ira being raped by four men in a back alley. The pain, anguish, fear and feel of the knife built anxiety and pain, paranoia and shame for a lifetime — never to be forgiven, forgotten, and never to be repaired.</p>



<p>He was the rapists, exacting dominance. Both the shameful and the shameless.</p>



<p>He was the onlooker, too scared to intervene. Coward. Dastardly.</p>



<p>He was the doctor, the father, the stillborn.</p>



<p>James’ eyes shifted and saw 100s more ‘screens,’ 100s more entries into the days, moments, lifetimes of people around the world — billions of people he was doomed to relive the lives of, over and over, backwards and forwards throughout time and back again.</p>



<p>There was no escape.</p>



<p>He is God, having only ever wanted to sacrifice immortality and — as is the only Godly pursuit — die and be forgotten.</p>



<p>He is Jane.</p>



<p>He is Ira.</p>



<p>He will wake up tomorrow and be Josh for a day.</p>



<p>A moment, Alex.</p>



<p>An infinity, Gods long dead and forgotten by history. Contrived and devised, planned and propagated by people — propagated to subjugate, control, extract money and exact dominance — immortal by design, infinite in the eyes of those who can’t plausibly conceive infinity.</p>



<p>Eyes wide shut.</p>



<p>Countless more animals, rocks, alien worlds — dissociation is a scary, scary thing. One loses one’s senses and knowledge of one’s self, one loses one’s memories and sense of humanity. As a rock on Mars, what do we remember of the Holocaust? What do we remember of Christianity? What do we remember of James? As a rock on Neptune, what do we remember of the rock on Mars?</p>



<p>Being God, how could he refute God?</p>



<p>He’d long since felt the panic leave his body. He’d long since laid there, catatonic, wishing for a sanity he remembered in his childhood. Drifting in and out of consciousness, drifting in and out of the conscience of others. He was all of his ex lovers, he was every side of every argument he’d ever had. He was the ultra-rich. He was the ultra-poor. He was puppy, squid, house. Woman, house, fish, bee. Acceleration, deceleration. Up, down.</p>



<p>As his mind entered the all-familiar mantra of dichotomies, a part of him wondered if he were stuck like this — forever lost between perceptions and realities, forever without a name, legacy, or history. A part of him chimed in that this is what happens every time, and like the Beatles said the sun will come out tomorrow.. There will always be another day, another dawn, another lapse of time where he was he and he wasn’t Jane, Ira, or God. These two parts argued — there were other voices that chimed in — the voices argued, and took bets amongst themselves about whether or not this was the last time, the final straw that broke that camel’s back and landed him forever lost. The voices took bets whether or not he would commit suicide today, tomorrow, die by arrow or die by plane engines falling from the sky — the voices argued…</p>



<p>The dichotomies grew louder to keep them from taking over. To keep them at bay: ocean, sky. Arrow, wound. Nothingness, everything. Quantum. Three states. On, off, both and neither. 1, 0,…</p>



<p>Catatonic. Not moving. Not interacting. Fearing the next day, fearing the chances the voices won and saw him off himself with a bottle of bleach. Fearing God’s revenge. Fearing Ira’s rapists. Fearing Jane’s dad’s drunk driver hit-and-run. Panic sets in…</p>



<p>The heart feels on fire, the heart feels as though it’ll give out. The breathing speeds up. The thoughts continue, and the feedback cycle sets in — faster heart, faster breathing, more psychosis, faster heart, faster breathing.. In the past, James had called emergency services fearing the physical symptoms. Now, having learned how his body tricks his mind tricks his body — a tango nobody wants to endure — he endures it. He sits through it. Looking out from eyes wide shut, he’s aware of the room around him behind closed eyes. Open eyes? He can’t tell anymore. They’re shutting and opening, he can see through them when shut. He is infinite. He is God.</p>



<p>He wouldn’t wish this fate on his worst enemies.</p>



<p>He is patient zero.</p>



<p>He wants to start support groups. He wants to help. He wants to educate, lift stigma, teach, and help others find a peace within themselves they can’t find on their own. He wants to be a voice for those without a voice.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/39/0*L3XI76HxjbFRSB_a?q=20" alt=""/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/39/0*FUcYxeuEueSWPZ0J?q=20" alt=""/></figure>



<p>He can’t.</p>



<p>He’s disabled.</p>



<p>He’s destroyed — inwardly, outwardly — he lays there each night on the brink of madness and puts on a smile each day for friends and family. He turns to drugs and alcohol to turn down the mantra, turn down the voices, and takes his medication knowing that The Man’s pharmaceutical agenda is to keep his voice from being heard. He’s dangerous. He threatens the status quo.</p>



<p>He’s not alone.</p>



<p>Squelched by the drugs — prescribed and not — he’s silenced by a system that didn’t give him a chance. The trade is a fair one — lose your autonomy for a series of time that goes by without hallucinations or delusions. Keep yourself in the ‘real’ reality, take these pills, we’ve supplied loads of cocaine on the street to keep you in check.</p>



<p>He is your cousin, your son, your friend, your lover.</p>



<p>As much as he’s everyone, everyone is him.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Proposing a Blockchain Solution During an Interview</title>
		<link>/2020/01/14/proposing-a-blockchain-solution-during-an-interview/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 01:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=164</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this article in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud! The Interview The other day, I interviewed for a supervisor role]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/840/1*GYULX2E1ENRA06Kz1_6lpg.jpeg" alt=""/></figure>



<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/14/proposing-a-blockchain-solution-during-an-interview/">View this article in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud!</a></p>



<h1 id="bdb7">The Interview</h1>



<p>The other day, I interviewed for a supervisor role within a top domain name registrar. Although most of the requirements are something I’ve already done before, it should prove an interesting diversion and provide funds to fuel my other ventures into creating passive income. Moreover, it would allow me to concentrate on my overall health and wellness — and support my goals of starting a family. While working in crypto is fun and exciting, it would be nice (wonderful?) to have a sustainable income I can depend on, while funding retirement plans ie. ~3% APR on WBTC on some providers or ~4–4.5% returns across many DeFi on the&nbsp;<a href="http://staked.us/?pid=fr5BC09Vgc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">staked.us</a>&nbsp;Robo Advisor. Even better — there are certain advantages to working in an environment with other people, for once, that I’ve been sorely lacking for the last 7–8 years working remotely from home — as well as benefits, employment insurance contributions, tax withholdings,.. etc… which I hadn’t had for that entire time, either!</p>



<p>I went into some details surrounding my mental health background, having conquered my own battles in order to learn and grow and become more able to perceive and understand other people’s points of view — turning a ‘disadvantage’ into one of my greatest selling points.</p>



<p>I feel happy with how the interview went, and should hear back about the potential for a 2nd interview soon.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/39/0*hzSw3_bLNOiQsSz6?q=20" alt=""/></figure>



<h1 id="c570">The Pitch</h1>



<p>During the interview, one of the questions was ‘sometimes meeting metrics and showing up every day is tough. How would you motivate your team?’</p>



<p>I said something akin to ‘I’ve actually given this question a lot of thought before the interview. What it really boils down to is what’s allowed or what there’s a budget for: can I offer people gift certificates in a competition for hitting targets? If there’s no budget to do that, can I offer them up on my own? Maybe we could have a points system to redeem for merchandise, paid time off, or other financial incentives..’</p>



<p>Read that again, but in the terms crypto fans would appreciate: A Blockchain solution for immutable transactions recorded to a distributed system for persistence, redundancy, transparency and accountability.</p>



<p>In the interview process, I can’t really suggest a ground-breaking solution using new and novel tech to an internet giant company. While they might be reciprocal at a later stage to something like this, they’d probably look at me with eyes wide shut if I came up with something as absurd (and potentially as costly) as that.</p>



<p>This does, however, ‘plant the seed’ that could take over into a successful pitch in the not-so-distant-future.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/39/0*wSkt5SOyCQgiC5ci?q=20" alt=""/></figure>



<h1 id="8918">What Are the Actual Sunk Costs of Dev?</h1>



<p>$0.</p>



<p>As I’ve detailed in&nbsp;<a href="https://www.education-ecosystem.com/h3xadecimal/lMJPV-how-to-build-your-own-ethereum-network" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">a 3–4 hour video presentation on education-ecosystem</a>&nbsp;(that you might have to unfortunately pay to see), I’ve already forked and successfully recreated the Ethereum mainnet onto my own single-use block producing machine. What this means in layman’s is that I can do anything that the Ethereum blockchain can do — on my own computers or devices, with my own tokens or smart contracts, in an environment where I set my own difficulty and I’m the only one mining — meaning I have full control over the Ether token and full rewards from all mining.</p>



<p>What this means in a global organization with many thousands computers across datacenters already is that some of these machines can run an eth-fork node running this new blockchain, in their idle processing time, and confirm blocks — achieving distributed systems for our new and fledgling blockchain.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/39/0*DVffGwMC_uCmrjdS?q=20" alt=""/></figure>



<p>As I’ve taped myself elsewhere on education-ecosystem&nbsp;<a href="https://www.education-ecosystem.com/projects/?q=h3xadecimal" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">(give a project search for my username h3xadecimal)</a>, I’ve created DApps on Ether using Truffle.js or other frameworks. The next step would be a simple but beautiful templated website in static HTML that’s served, again, for free or near-0 costs that then integrates — via MetaMask — with the newly created blockchain and its nodes, using a custom endpoint for provider.</p>



<p>This website would then allow a whole bunch of different functions — without confusing users with Blockchain-ish terms — from transferring ‘points’ from your own account to your friend’s account, or (like I said in the interview) exchanging tokens for corporate merchandise, partner’s merchandise or other partner offerings, and even paid time off — even including gift cards or entry into contests for more financial rewards, more merch or more PTO. The ideas can stream from here and I wouldn’t be the only head in the mix at this point, and I’m sure we would have a ton of rewarding things that tokens can be sent to 0x0 (the originating address) for.</p>



<p>Insofar as the upkeep of nodes and the static site — all of this is easily documented in the same way I’ve documented other tech solutions, for complete newbies to consume and understand and replicate the success I’ve achieved — meaning the solution may well have longevity after I’ve gone.</p>



<h1 id="7ce6">Next Steps?</h1>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/39/0*t_CcjnO84tr8zDO_?q=20" alt=""/></figure>



<p>With 3500+ employees on LinkedIn, I could give a 0- or near-0 cost to incentivize first my team in a pilot and, later, more in the building — and more in the world.</p>



<p>This benefits the organization by allowing them an uncompromisable solution for employee rewards — and, if successful, one that could be packaged and resold to small- to medium-sized organizations. This is a pro I seem to think that one of the largest internet domain name registrars would appeal to, do you agree?</p>



<p>This benefits the employees by gamifying employee rewards, and allowing them to accumulate, share, compete with their tokens — potentially taking part in contests and other fun activities. I didn’t mention this in detail but people would acquire tokens for perceivably good behavior: good attendance, exemplary metrics, and other types of achievable objectives that benefit them and the greater whole.</p>



<p>This benefits blockchain by putting a real-world example into focus within a large IT organization, where the users themselves get direct exposure to the technology and then can learn more about it if they choose — and the organization itself can champion the acceptance of blockchain worldwide, if we prove we can achieve a net net positive result for everyone involved.</p>



<h1 id="3690">A Plug</h1>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization — where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;!!</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Decentralized Social Media</title>
		<link>/2019/12/30/decentralized-social-media/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 03:19:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coindex]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=155</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[**submitted to Hackernoon, submitted to GCNews.io** Incentive I’m not necessarily after $200, I’m after a voice. While published on Hackernoon]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>**submitted to Hackernoon, submitted to GCNews.io**</p>



<h2>Incentive</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-twitter wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Let&#39;s try an experiment: $200 BTC bounty for the best review of decentralized social media.<br><br>The ideal piece covers not just crypto efforts like Voice/Akasha, but allied tech like Mastodon, CRDT, Bittorrent, Git.<br><br>Reply to this tweet with your post! cc <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@cz_binance</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@VitalikButerin</a> <a href="https://t.co/hhS0TXU9fX">https://t.co/hhS0TXU9fX</a></p>&mdash; Balaji S. Srinivasan (@balajis) <a href="https://twitter.com/balajis/status/1210639705143951360?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 27, 2019</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>I’m not necessarily after $200, I’m after a voice. While <a href="https://hackernoon.com/@jare">published on Hackernoon many times</a> and having a <a href="https://github.com/dunncreativess">Github with 100+ repositories</a>, I’d thought it might be a good idea to take part in this competition and get the attention of <a href="https://twitter.com/balajis">https://twitter.com/balajis</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance">https://twitter.com/cz_binance</a> &#8211; maybe even <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin">https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin</a>.</p>



<h1>Preface: Censorship</h1>



<p>This most recent bit of news time saw YouTube censor many crypto-related voices, and a mail broadcast I received from LBRY mentioned a few (or a lot?) of them ended up there to promote their views and opinions. Moreover, we saw MetaMask removed from the Android Play Store (and also, consequently, my device), purportedly for mining crypto and more likely for offering a competing environment where people can consume the internet than the Play Store itself. This level of censorship creates a world where a few big players (aka. the ultra-rich) can dictate to us what content we can consume where, and leads the way to a dangerous version of the internet where all we can possibly consume is the ultra-rich’s agenda.<br></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1gypbqvU8CjCzicIgUaUFeVLX56b7Te7lREUwnDONBeR9DMGKZo5NmhRbJBZ4ZGP5wvN_Ze4cSy0XxFxZ0LcX5YxynExXuxQOQRXXrBQfrvJb7W-aVqSS6ybJrjbRCUkjmx16S-R" alt=""/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/4qwxvQORDVRn_oxTr_nuxml1XJZLFwyXCl8daa-l7-PRVzmaE2r4NGU9vv-AT-p6BU_CPQD7EQwsHA7XnOVhs6aWbxa9LZEeDawyXMMVqyPWFT_EvREpnsAOEt2UGl_I_WoxAPKp" alt=""/></figure>



<p>The answer is an open and vibrant decentralized community where censorship plays no part. Minds.com comes to mind, but there has to be other underlying mechanisms to preserve the rights and freedoms of people everywhere &#8211; even in a censorship-free arena, we shouldn’t be subjected to hate speech and other dark web reminiscent dark corners of the internet. This kind of content from supremacists and trolls alike would hurt the overall image and therein hurt adoption &#8211; which would kill our creation before it’s born.<br></p>



<p>SteemIt comes to mind &#8211; along with it’s various interfaces, (and in recent iterations allow an even more well-thought / which allow a) way for people to downvote ‘bad’ content. This is a great solution for the decentralized community to self-moderate it’s own content monstrosity, but by and large this creates a demand for labor that can’t easily be rewarded (cue Steem’s life-long battle trying to figure out how to balance inflationary rewards with the need to self-moderate &#8211; and their nearly Steem-killing problem with people using the reward structure to bribe rewards and over-reward themselves).<br></p>



<h1>Monetization and Reward Mechanisms</h1>



<p>At this point, it’s crucial to remind ourselves that Blockchain is not cryptocurrency. Read that again! The huge interest that the ICO craze pulled into Blockchain was equally as damaging to the image of Blockchain &#8211; if not more &#8211; than the dark web’s dependency on Bitcoin as an anonymous online currency was to the image of Bitcoin. A reward mechanism for users for a decentralized social platform is not required, but could benefit actual users &#8211; actual people &#8211; for their content and social interactions.<br></p>



<p>If there’s a reward mechanism built into a new decentralized social media, it should be one that allows users to reward their favorite users through micropayments and allows the generation of additional rewards through staking an amount of e-currency someone already has &#8211; showing a dedication to the network and allowing the network more buying pressure than selling pressure. Steem does this, but I’m guessing people would want to stake more if there were more perceived reward &#8211; ie. you could earn more from your social presence as a direct result of staking more.&nbsp;<br></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/tawIPlUa64-MNSJ2LPqEAZDmam5AF-HvZ_d_J6iFcNreeFphWd9CzwRG5AkMrSee2i2Op4R0ivoHrBSHYyu_88pT2YUmCX-oJw5io_LRWixstkez3Q74z8XVczk0mv-dE76LEFvk" alt=""/></figure>



<p>If I had a dime for each time I had this conversation &#8211; with some underemployed or unemployed, disenfranchised friend on the internet &#8211; if we had a way to monetize and reward engaging social content we could empower the unbanked worldwide.&nbsp;<br></p>



<h1>Moderation</h1>



<p>&#8212; Note this isn’t the original (or even unoriginal) purposes of this neural evolutionary AI project &#8211; I’m going out on a limb here, without consulting our AI devs on this &#8211; but I think that the given problem would be socially acceptable content, and one could train the proof of fitness to provide that goal. Why not? &#8212;</p>



<p>In projects in the past like Akasha or Mastadon, one key feature that’s perplexed developers is how to monitor and remove spam, plagiarism, hate speech, etc. In a world with increasingly smart AI, there’s no reason to put this labor onto individual users like in Steem &#8211; one could create a neural evolutionary AI that’s rewarded by achieving happier individuals through a ‘report’ mechanism on leftover content. If something’s reported, then that competing generation responsible for that post is hit with a ‘ding’ that keeps it from being the master genome in that set &#8211; and the master genome carries on to start a new generation of competing genomes to do a better job in the next set of posts that are all moderated.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The computational power required to run these competing and learning sets of problem-solving algos could be served by p2p nodes that are run by users around the world &#8211; with as little as a laptop, in another chain that rewards the users submitting to the champion net.&nbsp;</p>



<p><a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1VBJ0UoY7MjeIEX0ljPj6G35qqnSizTv-XgzCiAx04F8/edit?usp=sharing">Read more in OuroborosChain &#8211; a white paper detailing neural evolutionary AI</a>.</p>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;</em></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization – where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em> !!</em></p>



<h1>Disclaimer</h1>



<p>The author is Chief Liquidity Officer for Coindex Labs.<br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Benefits of Neomenia and Crypto Growth Hacker &#8211; Compound Your Crypto!</title>
		<link>/2019/12/23/benefits-of-neomenia-and-crypto-growth-hacker-compound-your-crypto/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 11:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=146</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Hi SteemIt! View this post in it&#8217;s original form on dunncreativess.github.io! View my other posts on Hackernoon. Yes I&#8217;m promoting]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hi SteemIt! View this post in it&#8217;s <a href="http://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/12/23/benefits-of-neomenia-and-crypto-growth-hacker-compound-your-crypto/">original form on dunncreativess.github.io</a>! View my <a href="https://hackernoon.com/@jare">other posts on Hackernoon.</a> Yes I&#8217;m promoting this post &#8211; I think I have some info you folks might appreciate!</p>



<p>With results among users ranging from 3-4%, and a total net returns for some users at 16-22+% over a few days, it looks as though Neomenia is here to make an improvement in people&#8217;s lives.</p>



<p>Trading on three exchanges simultaneously and hedging risk by altering strategies based on conditions on a given exchange, it looks like Crypto Growth Hacker is the one-stop-shop for crypto investment diversification.</p>



<p>Neomenia now supports trailing takeprofit, meaning the upwards potential of a good buy or sell has increased significantly with your configurable takeprofit. It also has a special feature where the stop size is reduced by the difference in price as a percent when it moves in the right direction, so that you can lock in your profits faster while having a larger stoploss in case sh#t hits the fan.</p>



<p>The win/lose ratio is 5:1&#8230; and <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/XBTUSD/FkIqJJcy-Introducing-Neomenia/">it backtested 10 000% on TradingView</a>.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s a price action observed in one spot confirmed in another confirmed again by a direcitonal indicator, and that&#8217;s all I&#8217;m allowed saying under NDA.. but if you want to know more, join the Neomenia chat on Telegram! <a href="https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A">https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-1024x408.png" alt="" class="wp-image-149" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-1024x408.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-300x119.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-768x306.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-1536x611.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1.png 1874w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Crypto Growth Hacker is indexing Bitmex, Deribit and Binance Futures now and using a complex market making strategy on the first two while employing Neomenia on the third. The result is a bot that&#8217;s incredibly resilient and doesn&#8217;t take very many hits that last too too long &#8211; and shows steady gains.</p>



<p>Want to know more? Join our Telegram! <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-148" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1.png 880w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1-300x163.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1-768x416.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 880px) 100vw, 880px" /></figure>



<p>What&#8217;s great about both offerings is the community. We have scores of new users &#8211; and scores of people supporting us through thick and thin &#8211; and that all starts with posts like these, to raise awareness.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4-498x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-150" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4-498x1024.png 498w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4-146x300.png 146w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4.png 622w" sizes="(max-width: 498px) 100vw, 498px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5-498x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-151" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5-498x1024.png 498w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5-146x300.png 146w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5.png 622w" sizes="(max-width: 498px) 100vw, 498px" /></figure>



<p>We&#8217;re helping each other, and helping ourselves. You&#8217;re more than welcome to join! We&#8217;d be happy to have you. Ask questions! Grow with us!</p>



<p>We also have attractive referral campaigns for those of you who have an audience or know the inner workings of the magical internet.. ask us how to get 10% of your referral&#8217;s profits, or a straight (and recurring.. ) fee!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-147" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1.png 899w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1-288x300.png 288w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1-768x800.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 899px) 100vw, 899px" /></figure>



<p><a href="https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A">Neomenia Telegram</a></p>



<p><a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">Crypto Growth Hacker Telegram</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Week of Neomenia LIVE Trading Binance Futures</title>
		<link>/2019/12/18/a-week-of-neomenia-live-trading-binance-futures/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=140</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Neomenia is currently running on 8 subscriber&#8217;s accounts, creating predictable yield in sideways or bullish or bearish markets! The strategy]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1024x635.png" alt="" class="wp-image-141" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1024x635.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-300x186.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-768x476.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1.png 1276w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Neomenia is currently running on 8 subscriber&#8217;s accounts, creating predictable yield in sideways or bullish or bearish markets! </p>



<p>The strategy itself is protected under NDA, but as much as I can say it finds price indication in one place confirms it in another then also confirms with directional indication. The result is magic!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1024x692.png" alt="" class="wp-image-142" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1024x692.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-300x203.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-768x519.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-120x80.png 120w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1.png 1224w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>I&#8217;ve created a web interface to launch bots on our own Google Cloud Compute account, taking the hassle and potential issues with configuring your own VPS with bot options straight off your shoulders.. and as it costs us a pretty penny a month, and saves you renting your own VPS, it&#8217;s basically a free VPS giveaway! Woot!</p>



<p>I&#8217;m writing an update predominantly to create FOMO, but the community results speak for themselves&#8230;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-143" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-1.png 626w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-1-300x124.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 626px) 100vw, 626px" /></figure>



<p>The price of the bot will increase from $49 or $59 (depending if you use our Binance Futures referral code) up to minimum $99 in the new year. The time to come onboard is now! Have no fear, our team and community moderators have your back through thick and thin.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn4.png" alt="" class="wp-image-144" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn4.png 606w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn4-300x137.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 606px) 100vw, 606px" /></figure>



<p>So &#8211; come on in, grab it while it&#8217;s cheap!</p>



<p>There are other monetization methods for people who otherwise have no access to futures, join <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> and check out the pin!</p>



<p>Interested in Neomenia? Join here! <a href="https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A">https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A</a></p>



<p><em>! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization – where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;!!</em>(<strong>Disclaimer</strong>:&nbsp;<em>The Author is the Chief Liquidity Officer at Coindex</em>) </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trade Smarter, Trade Together! Crypto Growth Hacker Crowdfunded Bot Tokens to Mint</title>
		<link>/2019/12/14/trade-smarter-trade-together-crypto-growth-hacker-crowdfunded-bot-tokens-to-mint/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 02:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=134</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;m offering my market maker bot one of two possible ways: 1. I provide you the source code and you]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1024x612.png" alt="" class="wp-image-135" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1024x612.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-300x179.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-768x459.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2.png 1452w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>I&#8217;m offering my market maker bot one of two possible ways: 1. I provide you the source code and you can configure your apikey and secret and review the code to make sure nothing malicious happens, on a profit-share scheme where you provide 40% of the earnings after every month &#8211; as confirmed by API. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3.png" alt="" class="wp-image-136" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3.png 1000w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-300x296.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-768x759.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></figure>



<p>2. I&#8217;m creating a dividend token for sale to the general public (including Americans) that I then pay monthly 70% of the profit (10% for me, 15% reinvested for compounding effect, 5% BNB holdings). The dividend trading fund would span multiple bots, with an initial spread of 25% Neomenia BTC 25% Neomenia ETH 25% Deribit arb + options BTC 25% Eth. The dividend token script I&#8217;m using doesn&#8217;t have voting, but we&#8217;ll vote on bot % holdings and bot strategies using an off-chain voting system enabled by etherscan reports on holding %, anything more than 5% gets a vote.</p>



<p>The benefits of option 1 is that you get to run one of my bots with a profit-share model, the benefits of option 2 are: a. if you&#8217;re an american citizen you can now kindof take part in leveraged futures trading, by way of the token. b. as our BNB accumulates, we pay less fees c. as our BNB accumulates, we get more % from our referrals d. the combined notional traded on Binance will allow us to further climb their fee ladder. You can also refer people to the crowdfunded bot, for every 100 tokens at $1 worth of Eth apiece minted you get 10 tokens. For every 100 tokens that a referral of your referral mints you get 5 tokens.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-imgur wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-imgur"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="imgur-embed-pub" lang="en" data-id="PBQZAB1"><a href="https://imgur.com/PBQZAB1">View post on imgur.com</a></blockquote><script async src="//s.imgur.com/min/embed.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<ol><li>Join Telegram https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</li><li>Fill out this form.</li><li>Send your Eth here: 0x9c33b574c8D013Ba501a897484E3b92a27A3FDB8</li><li>Fill the TXID in this form.</li><li>Tokens will be minted as often as possible, with the least often being once a month before dividends are paid.</li></ol>



<p>Form to fill: https://forms.gle/bDQmuUhQQ5FJPvgN6</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Our Next-Gen Crypto Trading Bot Neomenia Goes Live!</title>
		<link>/2019/12/05/our-next-gen-crypto-trading-bot-neomenia-goes-live/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 19:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=128</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Intro http://patbot1.duckdns.org/ Start: Sat Nov 30 2019 14:21:06 GMT+0000 (UTC) Now: Sun Dec 01 2019 05:17:39 GMT+0000 (UTC) BTC Notional]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>Intro</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-473x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-129" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-473x1024.png 473w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-139x300.png 139w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image.png 591w" sizes="(max-width: 473px) 100vw, 473px" /></figure>



<p>http://patbot1.duckdns.org/<br> Start: Sat Nov 30 2019 14:21:06 GMT+0000 (UTC)<br> Now: Sun Dec 01 2019 05:17:39 GMT+0000 (UTC)<br> BTC Notional traded recent memory: 38.44400000000188<br> Current position: -1.952<br> BTC % Delta: 31.89%<br> BTC % ROI / day projected: 51.22%<br> BTC % APR projected: 1.869e+4%</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-1-473x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-130" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-1-473x1024.png 473w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-1-139x300.png 139w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-1.png 591w" sizes="(max-width: 473px) 100vw, 473px" /></figure>



<h2>Steps to Reproduce</h2>



<p>Step 1. Join our Telegram https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A<br> Step 2. Create a net-new Binance account, and enable futures, and create an api key after enabling futures http://www.binance.com/en/register?ref=27039658, You&#8217;re allowed to have as many Binance accounts as you like, while only verifying one &#8211; the max daily withdrawal on an unverified account is still huge<br> Step 3: Sent the subscription fee to our wallet 0x55FC78F760fBeb15A8a14ce2B8e9DCfA4CE0f966<br> Step 4: Enter your transaction ID on this form.<br> Step 5: And the last 6 characters of your API key.<br> Step 6: The team will manually add you to the bot&#8217;s license, and send you the executable file and other directions.<br> Step 7: Run the appropriate exports or setx&#8217;s from within env.sh. DO NOT simply run env.sh, it won&#8217;t work, copy and paste the commands into a terminal/cmd window. On windows, open a net new cmd when finished.<br> Step 8: Run the executable for app for BTCUSDT, eth for ETHUSDT, and balance for a balance output graph like the ones you&#8217;re used to seeing.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-2-473x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-131" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-2-473x1024.png 473w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-2-139x300.png 139w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-2.png 591w" sizes="(max-width: 473px) 100vw, 473px" /></figure>



<h2>Neomenia FAQs</h2>



<h1>FAQ 1: Settings</h1>



<p>variables with ‘eth’ prepended are the same, for the ethusdt bot<br></p>



<p>delaybetweenorder, higher for more delay before a new limit order</p>



<p>takeProfit, in % what gains to lock in before market out</p>



<p>stopLoss, in % what losses to accept before market out</p>



<p>tgUser, your Telegram username for use with the Telegram bot</p>



<p>key, APIkey</p>



<p>secret, APIsecret<br></p>



<p>&#8212;-<br></p>



<p>Note that the key and secret are never communicated anywhere off the local machine, except in signed requests to the exchange (which hide your details). Wireshark sniffing can confirm this.<br></p>



<p>&#8212;-<br></p>



<p>site, the http or https address where your server is located. You can google curl ipify to find your address if you’re in a headless server, or google ‘what is my ip’ if you have an interface. You can set up DNS forwarding on duckdns.org or register your own spiffy shiny new domain if you like.</p>



<p>poirt, which port to run the balance server on. Use 80 for http 443 for https (which isn’t enabled anyhow) or a higher number like 8080 if you’re having permissions issues.</p>



<p>maxFreePerc, what maximum % of the wallet will be used before stopping ordering in the same direction. Note this doesn’t count existing limit orders, which could max our margin if your delay is too small.</p>



<p>orderSizeMult, for a $50 USDT account use 5, for $250 use 1, for $500 use 0.5. Etc.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-3-1024x549.png" alt="" class="wp-image-132" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-3-1024x549.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-3-300x161.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-3-768x412.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-3.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2>FAQ 2: Legal Mumbo Jumbo</h2>



<p>In no way are our team or any affiliated member responsible for any gains or losses you might experience. Previous action is no indication implied or assured of future performance. Risk only what you can afford to lose. This bot does not constitute financial advice by any means, and is meant to be used in an educational, communal, and fun format.</p>



<h2>Sign Up Now!</h2>



<p><a href="https://forms.gle/hWa7uzZFg9nD1khg8">https://forms.gle/hWa7uzZFg9nD1khg8</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blog Monetization on SteemIt.com and Dblog.io</title>
		<link>/2019/11/24/blog-monetization-on-steemit-com-and-dblog-io/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 22:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[steemit]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=119</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[See this post in it&#8217;s original form on dunncreativess.github.io! Awhile ago I installed Steempress on my WordPress blog on ,]]>/</description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/24/blog-monetization-on-steemit-com-and-dblog-io/">See this post in it&#8217;s original form on dunncreativess.github.io!</a></p>



<p>Awhile ago I installed Steempress on my WordPress blog on ,/ and Simply Static to export my WordPress site as a static site to local drive and the git commit it to my github.io repository.</p>



<p>Lo and behold, after originally thinking that Steempress wasn&#8217;t working, it appears it is!</p>



<p>I&#8217;ve even included the dblog.io dblog tag, which means they appear here:</p>



<p></p>



<p>The only issue is that I have to replace the images from localhost to dunncreativess.github.io. Small price to pay! If I were to instead host my WordPress somewhere in the cloud (even on a port other than 80/443), it would work.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-39-1024x155.png" alt="" class="wp-image-120" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-39-1024x155.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-39-300x45.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-39-768x116.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-39.png 1202w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-40-1024x189.png" alt="" class="wp-image-121" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-40-1024x189.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-40-300x55.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-40-768x142.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-40.png 1256w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Now, $0.06 USD in crypto over 7 posted articles might not sound like much &#8211; but in an adless presentation that solves the monetization-without-bugging-people sense, I&#8217;m now being rewarded by all these people voting on my content instead of a centralized force like Adsense and you&#8217;ll notice that my github.io and my hackernoon don&#8217;t share ads!</p>



<p>It&#8217;s also continuously improving.. that $0.04 is for the lastest article, meaning I&#8217;m gaining momentum.</p>



<p>I mentioned the benefits of DPoS at length to the folks at Hackernoon when they were dreaming up HN 2.0.</p>



<p>Monetization is key. Incentivization is what rules the internet and any publication platform should be centered around ‘how do we turn content into $.’</p>



<p>I’ve said it before and I’ll say it again that we need to consider tokenization and blockchain in order to put the ability to upvote/downvote content (self regulate and moderate) while also allowing shareholders and prolific content producers to have the most influence on the monetary rewards for contributing authors. While Steem appears to be failing because of a misbalance in currencies producing bidbots and scammy 115% returns on promotion budgets, there are alternative sidechains to consider that did away with the SBD concept and pay everything out as VESTed income, so that people are &#8211; in turn &#8211; vested into the success of the platform. Check <a href="http://smoke.io/">smoke.io</a> and <a href="http://whaleshares.io/">whaleshares.io</a>.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-42-1024x571.png" alt="" class="wp-image-123" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-42-1024x571.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-42-300x167.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-42-768x428.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-42-1536x857.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-42.png 1544w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-43-1024x559.png" alt="" class="wp-image-124" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-43-1024x559.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-43-300x164.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-43-768x419.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-43-1536x839.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-43.png 1617w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>I truly believe in DPoS as a technology &#8211; although with a few tweaks it could serve far better than it does on <a href="http://steemit.com/">steemit.com</a>.</p>



<p>When someone shares or upvotes a story, if it then becomes popular and earns a ton of rewards through the social algorithm % of inflation, that person who shared it to get it popular in the first place earns a % of that social % as a curator &#8211; as do all the other curators, weighted by when they expressed interest. This is important for a few reasons. .first, as your most prolific writers along with the team and the stakeholders would be the biggest currency holders, they can do a lot of good by spending time (or automation ways to) upvote posts they like, and get exposure to users or groups of users they think deserve it &#8211; you only get a certain number of upvotes/downvotes per day, which you can increase or decrease by increasing or decreasing the ‘strength’ of your vote (out of 100%). Second &#8211; these large token holders would also be paramount in fighting spam and self-regulating the environment. If there are people drawn to the site with the gleam in their eye of earning crypto by regurgitating content or plagiarizing, these highly vested people can ‘downvote’ said spammy posts and undo any earnings they may have accumulated &#8211; to the point that their post gets a negative up/downvote ratio and can be taken off of web + mobile + whatever UI interfaces to the chain. In short, you gain currency by sharing, creating, or upvoting content… . proportional to your VESTed interest in the platform.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-41-1024x607.png" alt="" class="wp-image-122" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-41-1024x607.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-41-300x178.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-41-768x455.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-41.png 1516w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Moreover, there can be other % uses for the inflation of the currency that can do a lot of good &#8211; one of the integral parts of DPoS is the ‘delegated’ part where there are many nodes hosted by many people, and they can acquire votes from users that are weighted based on how vested they are into the system as a whole. Some of these people (usually the top 21) will earn a % of the inflation pie just for helping produce blocks &#8211; but how they accumulate votes is the important part. They must continually deliver value and hold the network’s priorities at heart in order to outperform those other contenders &#8211; which is good for the network.</p>



<p>Lastly, there can be a ‘team’ or ‘reserve’ % of inflation that can be used to continually fundraise based on the current value of the coin. While everyone is earning via social algos or by being a witness, the team can have a source of continual income with which to spend on the project or improving various aspects to it.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://community.hackernoon.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" alt=":slight_smile:"/></figure>



<p><a href="https://community.hackernoon.com/u/david">@David</a>&nbsp;<a href="https://community.hackernoon.com/u/dane">@Dane</a>&nbsp;I know that HN in the past has said one of the advantages to HN 2.0 will be the ability to publish without the hassle of ads… and a DPoS-driven network is one way to ensure that HN will never have to sustain itself by running ads. If the team creates wealth through inflation and the community drives the value of that currency upwards (when really the token came from almost nowhere and represents no legal obligation) it’s basically free money… for everyone&nbsp;&nbsp;&#8211; while empowering those with faith and trust in the new platform to exert more influence by buying more and VESTing more.</p>



<p>It opens a whole lot of other doors, too. How do we add ‘real value’ to that coin? What sorts of services or products can we sell as a group or as the team that aligns the value of the coin to something? Can we create a distributed network of writers that are vouched by community consensus via a new kind of Blockchain reputation system that doesn’t yet exist in Blockchain content networks (aside from their exponential ‘rating’ applied to accounts which can be fabricated if you buy enough attention for your posts), and then pitch this new marketplace of content creators at brands and agencies for exposure and so everyone can win &#8211; while having them pay in the currency, which drives value? Swag stores? Can we set it up so that content creators on the network can hustle out communications to their subscriber list to these brands and agencies? What sort of services can we come up with that are ‘out of the box’ and apply to the hacker community?</p>



<p>I agree wholeheartedly the incentives need to be aligned. I think a good step in the right direction would be to move rewards from liquid to VESTed amounts, which means that those who are looking for a ‘quick buck’ will be less likely to spam up the ecosystem.</p>



<p>I really shouldn’t have said ‘free money,’ and you’re right that it’d have a huge impact on the project and the value of the coin could potentially devour what we’re trying to achieve &#8211; ‘Sure, the upside of a token is very high…but the downside is also very low.’ this is absolutely true!<br></p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
