<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>jare.cloud</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Jare&#039;s Cloud</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 19:14:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-CA</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.3.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Top 4 (And Bonuses!) Reasons You Should Always Prepare for the Worst</title>
		<link>/2020/01/17/top-4-and-bonuses-reasons-you-should-always-prepare-for-the-worst/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 19:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=230</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[#1: You&#8217;ll Always be Pleasantly Surprised This is actually a secret my mom taught me over and over again. If]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>#1: You&#8217;ll Always be Pleasantly Surprised</h2>



<p>This is actually a secret my mom taught me over and over again. If you expect the worst possible outcome in any given situation &#8211; love, relationships, family, work &#8211; then whatever does come to pass will certainly be better than your expectations!</p>



<p>In such a way, you&#8217;ll find little joys throughout your day and week. These little joys will create a sense of reward that you might not have had if you were constantly being let down by your own expectations.</p>



<p>Framing your world in a different light can have certain advantages &#8211; for those with very specific minds, you might lose touch with the &#8216;real reality&#8217; and become a concern for your own self&#8217;s well-being. Read an article I wrote on how <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/14/how-do-people-with-mental-health-illnesses-like-schizophrenia-or-other-psychoses-think/">people with schizophrenia and mental health can actually think</a> (from first-hand experience).</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://live.staticflickr.com/2118/2511788463_03d9281e2e_z.jpg" alt="Image result for pleasant surprise"/></figure>



<h2>#2: Emergency Preparedness Saves Lives</h2>



<p>In a much more literal sense, being prepared for the worst will mean that you create disaster recovery plans &#8211; be they for the zombie apocalypse, should your car die and need repairs you can&#8217;t immediately afford, or if the lights go out for a day or two &#8211; having a plan improves your chances of getting through the scenario measurably. </p>



<p>This is so true that a brief Google search returns many millions islands (results, in Google English Pirate language) for &#8217;emergency preparedness course,&#8217; <a href="https://www.googleadservices.com/pagead/aclk?sa=L&amp;ai=DChcSEwjL39ilpYvnAhVN1sAKHex_BzcYABAAGgJpbQ&amp;ohost=www.google.com&amp;cid=CAESQOD2M1X01icn_Ddsj9d_VtuSw2OJzkWb-hMqPuHbRQdhjHlW1fmxM4R73TFopbDePIk6WevtDEoZfVqZPTnors0&amp;sig=AOD64_0WZlRmA4DrGAF_Av58ZgcPrRp7aA&amp;q=&amp;ved=2ahUKEwixoc2lpYvnAhXFWc0KHTQqBxIQ0Qx6BAgQEAE&amp;adurl=">like this one at a Canadian university</a>.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-19-1024x696.png" alt="" class="wp-image-231" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-19-1024x696.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-19-300x204.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-19-768x522.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-19.png 1178w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2>#3: You&#8217;ll Be Ready for Anything</h2>



<p>Hand in hand with being prepared for the worst-case scenario, you&#8217;ll also be ready for all the other scenarios up and down the range of possible outcomes &#8211; from the best possible ones right down to what could potentially be the absolute worst. Because you have considered and somehow either counted or discounted each possible route, you will have a plan for accomplishing things regardless of how fate will twist your arm. </p>



<p>As you get more and more used to this mental exercise, you&#8217;ll notice that your breadth of perception will naturally expand &#8211; as you&#8217;ll be considering more &#8216;twists of fate,&#8217; having added personal experience and the nature of the universe as it tends towards infinity. What I mean to say, rather, is that as the Powers That Be (whatever you subscribe to) throw new and unexpected curveballs your way, your brain will naturally plan for even more possibilities and outcomes. This will expand your mind way better than the hippie in highschool promised you Lysergic Acid Diethylamide ever could have come close to.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://i.guim.co.uk/img/media/4e83b3f710949ba6d82614821d6d3f93dd1786b9/0_1020_3125_1875/master/3125.jpg?width=300&amp;quality=85&amp;auto=format&amp;fit=max&amp;s=7fd40712c4db8af6b93a0ab9580243a9" alt="Image result for lsd"/></figure>



<h2>#4: You&#8217;ll Achieve More Goals</h2>



<p>Well, #3 was a bit of a doublethink mindfuck. What does it translate to, practically? Why should it be encouraging, rather than something to be afraid of?</p>



<p>In reality, creating new and interesting ways to approach problems will give you new and novel ways of conquering those problems. Your new disaster emergency preparedness attitude &#8211; when applied to everything &#8211; will allow you to accomplish more and more of your goals, more and more frequently. </p>



<p>This has a fantastic effect on your mindset, and overall happiness. If you do end up doing the things you set out to do more often than you do now, or even in fashions you hadn&#8217;t considered before, then you&#8217;ll have more and more dopamine for your pleasure centers &#8211; which means a happier, healthier you!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://images.saba.com/uploads/blog/what-should-you-do-when-you-dont-accomplish-your-goals/what-should-you-do-when-you-dont-accomplish-your-goals.jpg?s=1696x900" alt="Image result for accomplish"/></figure>



<h2>Bonus: Win Friends and Influence Enemies</h2>



<p>With a happier, healthier you comes a number of bonus effects &#8211; like a boost in charisma, confidence, ability. This truly is a snowball effect of positive outcomes.</p>



<p>When you present yourself better &#8211; or at least, more confidently &#8211; it results in people taking you more seriously, or appreciating you (or at least, your opinions and voice) more and more. This will allow you to gain more traction at work, home, and play. </p>



<p>It will allow you to harness your new-found powers of persuasion in two important ways. First, you&#8217;ll be able to befriend more people more frequently &#8211; winning their approval and allowing them to become proponents of whatever causes or values you subscribe to. Second, you&#8217;ll be able to exert your newfound influence over people who might detract from your causes or values &#8211; allowing you to gain more of a say over the people who would do you ill or harm (even just on the theoretical, intellectual level).</p>



<p>Did I interest you already about the ways in which a segregated, compartmentalized mindset can be a blessing &#8211; and a curse? <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/why-schizophrenia-is-the-most-under-represented-of-all-the-death-sentences/">Read my other article here on how schizophrenia increases your chances of an early end to your mortal turmoil</a> (read again: it&#8217;s a fatal diagnosis. No, no joke!)</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/51Ad%2BUal74L.jpg" alt="Image result for win friends influence people"/></figure>



<h2>Bonus (Voice of Reason!) #2: This Is Actually a Lot of Work</h2>



<p>When you&#8217;re tasking your mind with so much data to consume and analyze, you&#8217;re actually spending a lot more time thinking about yourself and your surroundings, experiences and misconceptions an awful lot more than you are should you not be exercising this theory. This can translate to an awful lot of work &#8211; something that might end up tasking you to a point where it can do more harm than good.</p>



<p>Truly, if you become preoccupied by this exercise and it gets in the way of goals rather than helping them &#8211; or prevents you from performing at work, home, school, or anywhere &#8211; then it might not be worth the time that goes into it. As with anything, it&#8217;s good in moderation &#8211; and we should always exercise a good balance in our own minds.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="http://m.quickmeme.com/img/e3/e3a8e54d319943a447a88e1fc37c027eba0991c2af0bf7af9ea6822622db1c13.jpg" alt="Image result for everything in moderation meme"/></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>What are trade bots? Robot traders explained!</title>
		<link>/2020/01/17/what-are-trade-bots-robot-traders-explained/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 06:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=226</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Read this article in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud! Introduction There&#8217;s nothing more enjoyable than trading for a living. You]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/17/what-are-trade-bots-robot-traders-explained/">Read this article in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<h2>Introduction</h2>



<p>There&#8217;s nothing more enjoyable than trading for a living. You basically sit there, and exchange money for other things of value and then back again. Rinse wash  repeat, and you can certainly support yourself taking small profits every so often &#8211; or heavier ones, usually less often!</p>



<p>Eventually, all traders will settle into a routine they&#8217;re comfortable with. They&#8217;ll build up an overall strategy of smaller strategies ranging in complexity and different input variables &#8211; from indicators to position sizing, there&#8217;s a lot to consider!</p>



<p>What&#8217;s important is that it&#8217;s easy to make a day&#8217;s salary in one trade, with very little investment. It&#8217;s also easy &#8211; probably easier &#8211; to lose your entire nest egg in that same day. Remember, invest only what you can afford to lose!</p>



<p>Let&#8217;s discuss a bit about the history of consumer-level trade bots, how trade bots can be used by near-infinite amounts of money by institutions, and how we can make money today using trading bots!</p>



<h2>Historical Trade Bots: Expert Advisors</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://media.fxcm.com/fxpress/fxcmcom/base/page/metatrader-4/carousel-image-1.jpg?fit=cover&amp;auto=webp" alt="Image result for mt4"/></figure>



<p>Most consumer-level brokers over recent years have offered a universal integration for people to day-trade: it&#8217;s called MetaTrader, and most popular of the versions is MetaTrader 4. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://forexmt4ea.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/fdiamond_real_latest2.png" alt="Image result for mt4 ea"/></figure>



<p>It included all sorts of handy features, and could trade anything you could imagine &#8211; from stocks and deriviatives to commodities and forex, it was easy to win or lose quickly and with a laugh or a tear. </p>



<p>One of the most important features you could find was the Expert Advisor. What this was was a way for users &#8211; or developer shops &#8211; to program their own strategies into the machine, allowing it to trade automagically. Even when you were away to the Caribbean or when you were sleeping &#8211; and markets were open &#8211; the expert advisor code would be watching, and reacting to the markets. </p>



<p>You could use all sorts of indicators &#8211; like directional ones like RSI, price ones like VWAP, volatility ones like EWMA, and the list goes on &#8211; and your own variables to manipulate the info and act on your strategies.</p>



<p>This bred a whole new world where people could show off or even sell their Expert Advisors to other people. This marketplace was soon fraught with scams and genuine people trying to help out &#8211; like any other capitalist venue, it&#8217;s as important now as then to always Do Your Own Research before committing funds to anything.</p>



<p>One popular scam was to employ a version of the Martingale Betting System. What this means is that when you lose a bet (or a trade), you double (or increase) your risk so then when you win the next bet (or trade) you earn back everything you lost plus a little extra that you&#8217;ve just now won. Then, when you bet again you start with the base amount again (or less, anyhow) and repeat the process.</p>



<p>This sounds genius &#8211; you&#8217;ll never lose!</p>



<p>In reality, probability works against you and the longer you play this game the more likely it is that you&#8217;ll see a large enough streak of losses to wipe out all your earnings. Neigh, even nations would lose when playing Martingale strategies &#8211; in roulette or in trading. <br><br>Eventually.</p>



<p>Probably.</p>



<p>What this looks like is a smooth chart with minimum drawdown right up until the end event where everything is lost. What this means for an expert advisor developer is that they can have a fantastic, promising looking chart &#8211; even when tested in real-time, with live funds &#8211; and they can promote that using their marketing budget to get many new subscribers. </p>



<p>End event!</p>



<p>I lost my money this way once with an expert advisor&#8230; I learned to not trust backtests, not trust test accounts and only trust my own forward tests &#8211; and remember the first rule: Only invest what you can afford to lose!</p>



<p>Anyways, loads of people earned great money on forex robot trades. Many people still do. You can, too, if you have a good strategy that can&#8217;t easily be duplicated and you maintain your edge over the market. Many more will make money on Expert Advisors, or other forms of trading automation.  </p>



<p>Hooah!</p>



<h2>Robot Traders at Scale: Wall Street</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://timeentertainment.files.wordpress.com/2013/12/twows-02401r.jpg?w=720&amp;h=480&amp;crop=1" alt="Image result for wolf of wall street"/></figure>



<p>Movie theatrics and fiction aside, The Wolf of Wallstreet made all his money by manipulating IPOs that he then controlled a relatively large stake in at arm&#8217;s length. </p>



<p>How does one manipulate IPO prices? One trades. Using many accounts. One trades back and forth, and loses a bit on the fees and the spread but encourages other parties on the market to trade more and more and even influence the price &#8211; at just the right times in just the right increments &#8211; and voila, you&#8217;ve committed securities fraud but you&#8217;re mad rich!</p>



<p>In reality, most of Wall St probably aren&#8217;t committing securities fraud. Probably.</p>



<p>In reality, all of Wall St are using some form of trading automation and high-frequency trading to achieve their goals. Definitely.</p>



<p>By the time any sort of opportunity exists long enough to be traded against, 10s 1000s other parties employing your same or a very like strategy have noticed that opportunity and already traded it. In traditional markets.</p>



<p>How do you react? Be the first. Be the fastest. Poor tens millions dollars into developing faster infrastructure, faster code, and faster trades. Automation and delegation are the keys to success, no?</p>



<p>What this boils down to is that the consumer with their expert advisors and trading terminals on $500 computers instead of $500 000 supercomputers are beaten to the punch by Wall St at every turn.</p>



<p>Darn! All is lost!</p>



<p>No&#8230; Read on!</p>



<h2>Most Profitable Automated Trades: Cryptocurrency</h2>



<p>Where Wall St haven&#8217;t yet conquered the markets &#8211; even better: new markets are introduced daily &#8211; and where market discrepencies even across exchanges offer up opportunities for arbitrage (sure-bet, guaranteed profit.. look into it! Do your own research&#8230; or <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/16/amazon-ebay-aliexpress-retail-arbitrage-as-a-service/">read this article I wrote, it&#8217;s about a retail arbitrage business </a>&#8211; same idea! Buy low sell high!) and the execution times and volumes of big players don&#8217;t necessarily &#8216;own&#8217; the markets?</p>



<p>Bitcoin and cryptocurrency.</p>



<p>Everyone has a fair chance in crypto to earn a dollar &#8211; even though the big boys still spend millions on their trading bots, the little guys control much more of the market share than vs Wall St and traditional markets.</p>



<p>Things like sentiment &#8211; feelings expressed on Twitter &#8211; have a massive, predictable effect on smaller-volume coins. <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/automated-crypto-trading-bot-to-buy-pump-and-dump-sentiment-signals-from-twitter/">Read about my Twitter sentiment bot I&#8217;m presently creating here</a> (it&#8217;s fairly technical &#8211; but gives a good overview!)</p>



<p>All in all, it&#8217;s easier to make a quick buck with less capital on crypto &#8211; reliably, predictably &#8211; than it is in traditional markets.</p>



<h2>Conclusion</h2>



<p>You, too, can earn with automation! You, too can create or hire someone to create your own trading bots &#8211; for traditional markets, or for cryptocurrencies! You, too, can feel that little joy and hit of dopamine when your trades exit in the green!</p>



<p>Go for it!</p>



<h2>A Plug</h2>



<p>Want to learn about&nbsp;new articles&nbsp;in tech and being a madman? Subscribe to my mailing list here:&nbsp;<a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL">http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</a><br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Ebay Aliexpress Retail-Arbitrage-As-A-Service</title>
		<link>/2020/01/16/amazon-ebay-aliexpress-retail-arbitrage-as-a-service/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 04:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insanely Marketable Business Ideas]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=222</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[As I detailed in this recent article surrounding Twitter automation to buy cryptocurrency during pumps and in this way-old Hackernoon]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As I detailed in this recent article surrounding <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/automated-crypto-trading-bot-to-buy-pump-and-dump-sentiment-signals-from-twitter/">Twitter automation to buy cryptocurrency during pumps</a> and in this way-old Hackernoon and Medium discussing how I once <a href="https://medium.com/@jarettdunn/i-1000th-idea-to-make-money-online-via-python-chained-sqlmaps-8acb25cc9ad8?source=your_stories_page---------------------------">toyed with the morality of ethical hacking for profit</a> &#8211; it&#8217;s obvious that I often have ideas for tech businesses that don&#8217;t really get off the ground. I lack the marketing chops to execute these things, so I&#8217;m going to continue letting you guys know how my Proof of Concepts go and maybe one day some of you can make a living with one of my ideas!</p>



<p>This is another entry in Insanely Marketable Business Ideas. Hooah!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/606522166166421534/667572917105590282/unknown.png" alt=""/><figcaption>Source: My code just a minute ago</figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/606522166166421534/667573207414341633/unknown.png" alt=""/><figcaption>Source: My code a minute after that</figcaption></figure>



<p>What you might notice about these two images is the insanely obvious: if someone were to buy one of these generic handhold consoles on Aliexpress and then sell it on Ebay they could pocket the difference in costs. This is called &#8216;retail arbitrage,&#8217; where retail is what we&#8217;re trading and arbitrage is the act of buying low and immediately selling high. It&#8217;s preferable to sell before you have to buy &#8211; which you can effectively do selling on these marketplaces.</p>



<p>You&#8217;ll notice that I&#8217;m lacking a corresponding Amazon screenshot &#8211; their Product Advertising API requires you to have 3 sales in a certain amount of time as an affiliate before you can have access to the API. D&#8217;oh! I&#8217;ve sent them a message saying I&#8217;m creating a shopping comparison engine &#8211; it might be unwise to say we&#8217;re propagating the arbitrage &#8216;problem.&#8217; Sometimes, people that buy an item on Ebay and receive a package wrapped up by Amazon Fulfillment will become irate they&#8217;ve been the victim of not knowing they can search more than one site, and they might kick up a customer service complaint&#8230;</p>



<p>Either way, there&#8217;s money to be made!</p>



<p>But, that&#8217;s not my idea. That idea&#8217;s been tried and done effectively by many, and you can google for more info. My idea is buried in those screenshots, above, and in my explanation of the Amazon part too &#8211; these are affiliate links. If someone were to visit Aliexpress or Ebay after clicking my link and place an order within a month or a few months, I get a little % kickback from that sale. </p>



<p>In the case of providing this as a service, the model would be that I create a beautiful and effective comparison tool to find the highest potential margins for search results or by the best possible margins in a given category and finding exact (or near-exact by text compare) title matches, then display them in easy-to-organize lists for arbitrageurs to peruse, click the links, buy a bulk order of many items or maybe just an item or two, and as I build my network &#8211; and community &#8211; of arbitrageurs, my income from the % of a % of each initial sale will exponentially increase above and beyond the potential returns from the actual arbitraging. </p>



<p>Retail arbitrage is fraught with potential pitfalls: from max. orders or max. sales, all the way to the customer service burden &#8211; and potential returns, restocking fees or concerns &#8211; it is easy to lose some or all of your profits in a second with retail arbitraging if you&#8217;re not careful. When building a service that provides instant comparisons for the potential arbitrageur &#8211; and a supportive, helpful community of arbitraging friends &#8211; we can ensure the overall success and growth of the operation.</p>



<p>Sunk costs?</p>



<p>Upkeep of servers, initial dev and MARKETING.</p>



<p>Potential upside?</p>



<p>We&#8217;d run the site for free. Everyone can come in and discuss the opportunities of Retail Arbitrage, and use the tool to their heart&#8217;s content. In return, our marketing efforts will reflect the fact that other arbitraging tools require a monthly or yearly subscription &#8211; putting ours leagues ahead of the competition.</p>



<p>Ebay Partner Network pays 1-6% per sale depending on geo, if the sale happens within 24hrs of clicking the link. Aliexpress up to 9%, and Amazon pays up to a walloping 10%! When someone wants to arbitrage again, they&#8217;d certainly want to find a new-and-improved arbitrage deal &#8211; they&#8217;d return to our platform, find a new killer deal, place another order and boombingbang more affiliate income!</p>



<p>NOW, for the win, let&#8217;s review some code.</p>



<p>First, after running npm install for the required packages, we&#8217;ll require them in the code:</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>let eBay = require('ebay-node-api')
var request = require('request')</code></pre>



<p>Next we&#8217;ll instantiate our eBay object, like so:</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>let ebay = new eBay({
    clientID: '',
    env: 'PRODUCTION', // optional default = 'PRODUCTION'
    headers:{ // optional
        'X-EBAY-C-MARKETPLACE-ID': 'EBAY_US' // For Great Britain https://www.ebay.co.uk/
    }
})</code></pre>



<p>Now, I found out that I could use eBay&#8217;s affiliate tools to build an affiliate URL using my account and campaign. Afterwards, I hijack the &amp;mpre= field and replace the item URL with my URL for any given item, to build a new-and-improved eBay aff link for any given URL.</p>



<p>For fun and profit, we set our eBay affiliate URL &#8216;template&#8217; as well as our hard-coded search term:</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>var template = 'http://rover.ebay.com/rover/1/706-53473-19255-0/1?ff3=4&amp;pub=5575480811&amp;toolid=10001&amp;campid=5338476385&amp;customid=&amp;mpre='
var search = '500in1 nes'</code></pre>



<p>In our ebaydo function, we search eBay products using the eBay node package and loop over the resulting json. The url for the item is parsed then encoded, and we create our affiliate URL by joining our template from above with this new encoded item&#8217;s url. </p>



<p>Voila! Paydirt!</p>



<p>We log to console the network, affiliate URL, title, and price object for fun and profit. If there&#8217;s an error, let&#8217;s also log the error! Debugging is fun, right?</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>function ebaydo(keywords) {

    ebay.findItemsByKeywords({
        keywords: keywords
    }).then((data) => {
        for (var item in data[0].searchResult[0].item) {
            url = encodeURIComponent(data[0].searchResult[0].item[item].viewItemURL[0])
            url = template + url
            console.log('ebay:')
            console.log('affiliate url: ' + url)
            console.log(data[0].searchResult[0].item[item].title[0])
            console.log(data[0].searchResult[0].item[item].sellingStatus[0].currentPrice[0])
            console.log(' ')
        }
    }, (error) => {
        console.log(error);
    });
}</code></pre>



<p>The ali function is more complicated. First, we&#8217;ll get and parse the current time into url-encoded string. Phew, that took a lot of Googling to figure out&#8230;</p>



<p>Next, we&#8217;ll encode our keywords. That probably means some handy %20s (spaces). Then, we load a list of products based on those keywords from Alibaba&#8217;s API, parse the result into json, loop over the products and save some useful info to vars for later. We&#8217;ll take note of the price, product url, image url (why not? Should have done this for eBay too! People can compare the images when finding their like products&#8230;) and product title. Next, we send some of these vars off to a separate function.</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>function ali(keywords) {
    var time = new Date();
    var time2 = (time.getHours().toString() + "%20" + time.getMinutes().toString() + "%20" + time.getSeconds().toString());
    keywords = encodeURIComponent(keywords)

    var url = "http://gw.api.alibaba.com/openapi/param2/2/portals.open/api.listPromotionProduct/76080?sort=volumeDown&amp;fields=salePrice,productTitle,volume,imageUrl,productUrl&amp;keywords=" + keywords;
    console.log('keywords?: ' + url);
    var responses = new Array();
    try {
        var result2 = request.get(url, function(e, r, result2) {
            var json = JSON.parse(result2)
            if (json.result != null) {
                for (var i in json.result.products) {
                    console.log(json.result.products[i]);
                    var price = json.result.products[i].salePrice;
                    var id = json.result.products[i].productUrl;
                    var img = json.result.products[i].imageUrl;
                    var title = json.result.products[i].productTitle;

                    
                    dosearchurl(id, title, img, price)
                }
            } 
        })
    } catch (e) {
        console.log('exception: ' + e.toString());
    }
}
</code></pre>



<p>In dosearchurl, this genius technique allows me to have the variables persistent over the next request.get call, which returns a promise, meaning that if we did request.get inside a for loop then tried to access our old variables (like title in this case, for example) it would only find the variable value at the state in the new point in time when the promise has resolved (ie. the request completes) &#8211; meaning all our results would output the same data as the for loop has completed and it executes the console.log code with the for loops final value, instead of each incremented value.</p>



<p>So, by taking the for loop and feeding it the variables in a different scope, the variables remain persistent even though there&#8217;s a time delay for the promise &#8211; and we can output the variables in their proper sequence, instead of only the final one over and over again.</p>



<p>In here, we load the product id on another alibaba api endpoint &#8211; this one to create an affiliate url for our product we&#8217;ve found. Then, we output to console all the juicey details about our potential arbitrageur&#8217;s opportunity &#8211; and our potential affiliate income.</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>function dosearchurl(id, title, img, price) {
    var url2 = "http://gw.api.alibaba.com/openapi/param2/2/portals.open/api.getPromotionLinks/76080?fields=promotionUrl&amp;trackingId=4632&amp;urls=" + id;
    var responses = new Array();
    try {
        var result3 = request.get(url2, function(e, r, result3) {

            var json = JSON.parse(result3)
            console.log('aliexpress:')
            console.log('title: ' + title.replace(/&lt;[^>]*>?/gm, ''))
            console.log('affiliate url: ' + json.result.promotionUrls[0].promotionUrl);
            console.log('img: ' + img)
            console.log('price: ' + price)
            console.log(' ')

        });

    } catch (e) {
        console.log('exception: ' + e.toString());
    }
}</code></pre>



<p>It&#8217;s a win-win-win: goldmoney for the arbitrageur who earns surebet money, paydirt for me as I gain a tiny percent of those sales over and over again, and of course it&#8217;s a good thing &#8211; big bucks &#8211; for the retail marketplace. Hooah!</p>



<p>I hope you&#8217;re as excited about my POC as I was creating it then describing it here. Someone will surely bet some time and effort and marketing chops to execute this vision.. will it be me?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Better Web: Brave Rewards Your Content! Make money monetizing Twitter!</title>
		<link>/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 04:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Github]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=213</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this post in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud! Folks welcome to Web 3.0. Not only does Brave pay me]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/">View this post in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<p>Folks welcome to Web 3.0.</p>



<p>Not only does Brave pay me in $BAT for browsing the internet by serving me ads I enjoy watching based on my interests, it literally allows people to tip and automatically contribute to those Twitter users using Brave. </p>



<p>It also allows me to monetize my YouTube &#8211; I have 344 viewers watching my old ass YouTubes for 9.5hrs/month. I can now monetize some of those…</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-14-1024x410.png" alt="" class="wp-image-214" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-14-1024x410.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-14-300x120.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-14-768x308.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-14.png 1231w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Admittedly, my one true passion is finding a way to create evergreen and passive income for myself &#8211; now people viewing my YouTube videos will automagically share some of their $BAT with me. People that like me even more might opt to share more %, or even tip me one-time or repeatedly&#8230;.</p>



<p>I&#8217;ve been aware of BAT as a project and Brave as a browser for a long, long time, being a crypto enthusiast all these years. I resisted doing a tiny 5-second Google search because I assumed it was a new-fangled low-functioning browser that would disappoint. I wasn&#8217;t aware it&#8217;s literally built on chrome, can import my bookmarks and I can use all my favorite extensions!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-15-1024x518.png" alt="" class="wp-image-215" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-15-1024x518.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-15-300x152.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-15-768x389.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-15-1536x777.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-15.png 1804w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>On top of all that, it&#8217;s actively blocking unwanted ads across sites and ad networks while also keeping my private browsing information like cookie data or personally identifiable information from being transmitted from my machine.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-16-1024x682.png" alt="" class="wp-image-216" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-16-1024x682.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-16-300x200.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-16-768x512.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-16-120x80.png 120w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-16.png 1031w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>As <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2016/aug/31/personal-data-corporate-use-google-amazon">an article on theguardian quotes</a>: &#8216;Data appropriation is a form of exploitation because companies use data to create value without providing people with comparable compensation.&#8217;</p>



<p>What&#8217;s the solution? Limit the data you send! Be compensated for the data you do choose to share!</p>



<p>Within a few seconds of having the browser opened, I&#8217;d already earned a penny as they showed me an ad from BlockFi.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-17-1024x629.png" alt="" class="wp-image-217" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-17-1024x629.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-17-300x184.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-17-768x472.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-17.png 1083w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Another ad, advertising BAT&#8217;s community forums, turned out to be incredibly informative: as it turns out, the content creators signup page had more options than just Website, Twitch, YouTube. I had connected all three of these already but on the community forum I found a <a href="https://forum.batcommunity.org/t/use-twitter-to-receive-brave-rewards/5987/12">thread talking about tipping people on Twitter</a> &#8211; I thought: I must have this.</p>



<p>On further clicking I found Brave had loads more options for me to earn as a content creator! It&#8217;s probably just my desktop settings &#8211; at 175% zoom because I&#8217;m blind! </p>



<p>Also, in the interface of their Chrome-based browser, they&#8217;ve very cleverly integrated a &#8216;tip&#8217; button on Twitter tweets &#8211; right there in the UI.  </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-18-1024x663.png" alt="" class="wp-image-218" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-18-1024x663.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-18-300x194.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-18-768x497.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-18-850x550.png 850w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-18.png 1037w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>When I visit a content creator of any kind &#8211; including Github profiles, where I receive 100s more evergreen, passive views than I do on YouTube or even your reddit profile which might be (pardon the pun) more prolific than your Twitter &#8211; they&#8217;re automagically added to my pool of content creators that I&#8217;m going to automagically share some tokens with at the end of the month. I get to set totals, %s for each creator, and every other granular little detail.</p>



<p>Essentially, Brave gives the advertising revenue to the end-user who then chooses which publishers they want to reward with how much tokens &#8211; and they get to up the ante for those publishers they&#8217;re truly fans of. It&#8217;s a brilliant idea!</p>



<p><a href="https://brave.com/jar444">Download the Brave browser on your computer or mobile</a> phone here. You&#8217;ll be earning in a jiffy!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Automated Crypto Trading Bot to Buy Pump and Dump Sentiment Signals from Twitter</title>
		<link>/2020/01/15/automated-crypto-trading-bot-to-buy-pump-and-dump-sentiment-signals-from-twitter/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 21:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Github]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=202</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View This Article in it&#8217;s Original Form on Jare.Cloud! Strategy We follow Twitter accounts we trust: exchanges, coins, Twitter crypto]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="/2020/01/15/automated-crypto-trading-bot-to-buy-pump-and-dump-sentiment-signals-from-twitter/">View This Article in it&#8217;s Original Form on Jare.Cloud</a>!</p>



<h2>Strategy</h2>



<ol><li>We follow Twitter accounts we trust: exchanges, coins, Twitter crypto influencers</li><li>We wait around until someone tweets a coin name or coin ticker</li><li>We measure the sentiment of the message: is it buy or sell?</li><li>On strong buys, or multiple instances of buys in a period of time, we execute a market buy order on Binance Spot</li><li>We wait around until our exits are hit</li><li>1 out of every 3-4 signals we act on the crowd will also act on&#8230; </li><li>&#8230;meaning there&#8217;s upwards potential for everyone</li><li>and we can net 100s 1000s% gains!</li></ol>



<p>In practice:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-10.png" alt="" class="wp-image-205" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-10.png 862w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-10-300x289.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-10-768x739.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 862px) 100vw, 862px" /><figcaption> <br></figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://media.discordapp.net/attachments/666371834102677565/667093503817547794/tempFileForShare_20200115-205117.jpg?width=340&amp;height=659" alt=""/></figure>



<h2>NLTK &amp; New Words</h2>



<p>The Python programming language has a package called Natural Language Tool Kit, or NLTK. Inside NLTK are lexicons that you can use to accomplish different goals &#8211; in our project, the Vader Lexicon is useful because we can rank all sorts of English words on a scale of -1 to 1 based on how strongly they express good or bad emotions. This is called &#8216;sentiment analysis.&#8217;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-8.png" alt="" class="wp-image-203" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-8.png 451w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-8-300x199.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-8-120x80.png 120w" sizes="(max-width: 451px) 100vw, 451px" /></figure>



<p>We add some new words to the mix.. given our very specific scenario.</p>



<h2>Weighted Twitter Accounts and Tiers</h2>



<p>Of the accounts in our followed list, we&#8217;ll have exchanges, coins and crypto influencers. Of these, exchanges have the highest amount of influence when they make an announcement about an alt, the coins themselves have a medium amount and the influencers have a variable but usually less amount.</p>



<p>We organize each account we follow (or simply have in a static list) into a list with corresponding ratios for how they affect our sentiment scores. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-9.png" alt="" class="wp-image-204" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-9.png 304w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-9-300x128.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 304px) 100vw, 304px" /></figure>



<h2>Parsing and Referencing All the Binance Spot Coins</h2>



<p>Here&#8217;s what Binance&#8217;s 24hr ticker endpoint looks like:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-11.png" alt="" class="wp-image-206" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-11.png 649w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-11-217x300.png 217w" sizes="(max-width: 649px) 100vw, 649px" /></figure>



<p>We loop through all these results, look for ones that end in BTC and then replace the BTC out of the symbol string &#8211; leaving the coin. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12-1024x172.png" alt="" class="wp-image-207" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12-1024x172.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12-300x50.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12-768x129.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12-1536x258.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12.png 1890w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>We now have a list of coins!</p>



<h2>Get Twitter Followed, 100 Recent Tweets Within Last Hour</h2>



<p>This is optional and I may replace the followed list with a flat and static file or coded list, but presently the bot will read the followed list and then loop through it, grabbing everyone&#8217;s 100 most recent tweets (and and/or and not retweets &#8211; optional) and then cycle through those to see which occurred in the last (given timeframe). These are the goldmoney&#8230; we save tweets we&#8217;ve previously indexed to an array so as to not re-index them.</p>



<h2>Find Potential Coinnames, Compare to Our Binance List and Tweeter List</h2>



<p>We split the text of the tweets up by &#8216; &#8216; (space) and &#8216;\n&#8217; (newline). We then look at each resulting word or hashtag, capitalize them and compare them (or $ + the word, like $MANA or $mana or mana or Mana) against our list of tickers from the Binance API. We also then compare against a list of tickers that correspond to specific Twitter accounts, in the event of something like the MANA tweet above that didn&#8217;t mention &#8216;MANA.&#8217; So we can tell that decentraland tweets are, usually, unless otherwise specified, for MANA.</p>



<h2>For High Sentiment Scores, Buy</h2>



<p>On Binance we market buy with a % of our holdings. The % is configurable, and depends on someone&#8217;s aversion to risk.</p>



<h2>For Repeat Occurrences, Buy Again</h2>



<p>If another one of our trusted tweeters tweets another signal confirming the same trend, we &#8216;double down&#8217; and buy another % of remaining balance worth of the coin.</p>



<h2>1% Trailing Take Profit</h2>



<p>If the price immediately drops 1%, we gracefully exit as a stoploss and count our losses. If the price goes up 2% and then down 1%, we exit the trade at 1% gains less fees. If, however, the coin goes up 10% 40% 100% before dropping 1% &#8211; as it might do with mass hysteria &#8211; then we laugh all the way to the bank! 1%, of course, is configurable.</p>



<h2>Rinse, Wash, Repeat</h2>



<p>Another signal another coin another potential 100%!</p>



<h2>Considerations</h2>



<p>We want to use a custom list of crypto influencers because most of the people calling out signals on twitter are actually doing so in their own vested interest &#8211; having posted a buy signal in their private Pump &amp; Dump discords, their private group buys up the coin and then &#8211; 5 minutes later &#8211; they all post signals to their twitters and bought &#8216;influencer&#8217; twitters as tweets that seem to double, triply, quadruply confirm each other. In reality, these folks are dumping by the time anyone else starts to buy in &#8211; meaning that you&#8217;d likely face losses if you used a twitter-wide sentiment analysis and automated trading tool. This is where all existing tools &#8211; including AI-driven ones &#8211; fail in this space, and why my bot has a considerable edge on the competition.</p>



<h2>Next Steps</h2>



<p>I&#8217;d like the bot to keep track of the win/lose rate and severity of wins/losses from specific tweeters, so that it can potentially modify the sentiment score by a previous success factor &#8211; so if someone was right about a buy signal 2/5 times it&#8217;s worth more than someone with 1/5 times. If someone is right 1/10 times, though, and their signal does 25x better than the first two in these examples &#8211; that one is worth considerably more.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-13-1024x629.png" alt="" class="wp-image-208" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-13-1024x629.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-13-300x184.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-13-768x471.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-13.png 1471w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>It&#8217;d be nice to incorporate a python django webserver like a hackathon starter so I can take advantage of their Twitter oauth2 sign-in scheme. This way I can potentially have accounts log in without supplying their own twitter API credentials &#8211; which require an application process now &#8211; and more accounts can work with my bot. This would increase the amount of actionable data and win/loss rates and severities that can be used to package tailored lists of tweeters to know.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Schizophrenia is the Most Under-Represented of All the Death Sentences</title>
		<link>/2020/01/15/why-schizophrenia-is-the-most-under-represented-of-all-the-death-sentences/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 08:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=192</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View This Article in it&#8217;s Original Form on Jare.Cloud! With June estimates at 7000+ authors, 69 other Hackernoon contributors might]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/why-schizophrenia-is-the-most-under-represented-of-all-the-death-sentences/">View This Article in it&#8217;s Original Form on Jare.Cloud</a>!</p>



<p>With <a href="https://learn.onemonth.com/hacker-noon/">June estimates at 7000+ authors</a>, 69 other Hackernoon contributors might also be a victim of schizophrenia, along with me. This article serves to demonstrate why these people are facing tougher-than-average odds to live to a ripe old age, and how society isn&#8217;t doing them justice in helping or finding a permanent solution.</p>



<h2>Schizophrenia</h2>



<p>Schizophrenia is the psychotic disorder that&#8217;s defined by losing control over your reality. If you start to slip into beliefs or experiences &#8211; auditory, visual &#8211; that others don&#8217;t perceive, you&#8217;re schizophrenic! There&#8217;s other qualifiers to the disorder, like having a certain frequency and total number occurrences of these thoughts &#8211; as well as a lack of other conditions which may otherwise explain these often terrifying and traumatizing thoughts.</p>



<p>What counts as an hallucination or delusion? A hallucination is an effect on your senses that others can&#8217;t perceive. You might see something that isn&#8217;t there, hear something in the distance that only you can hear &#8211; you might even perceive other people perceiving your hallucinations, which is a trap on it&#8217;s own because now your hallucinations are covering your other hallucinations. You can see how easy it would be to lose touch with reality when your own human mind makes up its mind to revolt!</p>



<p>A delusion is a belief in something, some thought or idea or pattern that nobody else can perceive. You might think the media is talking to you, telling you to do things in secret code. You might think that you are somehow special, be it superpowers or the fact that you&#8217;re President &#8211; these delusions can vary in strength and severity, and may even go unnoticed in some for years and years before causing any issues.</p>



<p>There are negative symptoms of schizophrenia, too &#8211; where the positive symptoms are qualities you&#8217;ve gained or acquired from the illness, like hallucinations or delusions &#8211; the negative symptoms are things that you&#8217;ve lost with the new mental state. These could be habits or behaviours like caring about one&#8217;s well-being (cooking, cleaning, self-care) or curtailing one&#8217;s hobbies due to lack of interest.</p>



<h2>Prevalence</h2>



<p><a href="https://www.mentalhelp.net/schizophrenia/statistics/">Schizophrenia affects 1% of the population, 1.5% of Americans and 1.5 million people were diagnosed with it this year.</a> This translates to 300 000 Canadians, nearly 5 million Americans &#8211; verily, 105 million people around the world. Indeed, someone you know &#8211; more than one person you know &#8211; could very well be suffering.</p>



<h2>Concurrent Disorders &amp; Overdoses</h2>



<p><a href="https://www.addictioncenter.com/addiction/schizophrenia/">Nearly half of people suffering from schizophrenia abuse drugs and alcohol</a>. We call this a &#8216;concurrent disorder&#8217; &#8211; meaning that drugs and alcohol abuse are occurring at the same time as the psychological symptoms that lead a professional to diagnose schizophrenia.</p>



<p>I bid you welcome to the first reason schizophrenia is a death sentence: <a href="https://www.drugabuse.gov/related-topics/trends-statistics/overdose-death-rates">0.216% of the American population died from overdoses</a> from 1999-2017 (with a noticeable trend upwards in deaths/year). Given that <a href="https://www.drugabuse.gov/publications/drugfacts/nationwide-trends">9.4% of the population reported using illicit drugs</a> in the last month:</p>



<p>Americans: 300 000 000<br>
Drug abusers: 28 200 000 (9.4%)<br>
Deaths / 18 years: 648 000 (0.216%)<br>
Deaths / abusers: 2.3%<br>
Abusers / schizophrenics: 50%<br>
Schizophrenics: 5 000 000 (1.5%)<br>
Abusers that are schizophrenics: 2 500 000 (0.75%)<br>
Deaths / abusers that are schizophrenics: 57 500 (1.15% of # schizophrenic)<br>
Deaths schizophrenics / deaths abusers: 8.88%</p>



<p>8.88/2.3: you are 3.86 times as likely to die from an overdose than the average drug abuser if you&#8217;re schizophrenic.<br> 1.15/0.216: you are 5.32 times as likely to die from an overdose than the average person if you&#8217;re schizophrenic. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-5-1024x543.png" alt="" class="wp-image-194" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-5-1024x543.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-5-300x159.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-5-768x407.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-5.png 1418w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2>Suicides</h2>



<p>The <a href="https://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;rct=j&amp;q=&amp;esrc=s&amp;source=web&amp;cd=3&amp;cad=rja&amp;uact=8&amp;ved=2ahUKEwj9lIGGiYXnAhXKl-AKHVlcA-kQFjACegQIAxAB&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fafsp.org%2Fabout-suicide%2Fsuicide-statistics%2F&amp;usg=AOvVaw2pQbS5wgQ6GOwg_6X9pNYI">suicide rate for Americans is 0.014%</a> when &#8216;adjusted.&#8217;</p>



<p>The <a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC2951591/">&#8216;lifetime risk of suicide&#8217; for people with schizophrenia is 4.9%</a>.</p>



<p>Americans: 300 000 000<br>
Suicides: 4 200 000 (0.014%)<br>
Suicides / schizophrenics: 4.9%<br>
Schizophrenics: 5 000 000 (1.5%)<br>
Suicides that are schizophrenics: 245 000 (0.08%)</p>



<p>4.9/0.014: you are 350 times as likely to die from suicide than the average person if you&#8217;re schizophrenic.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-6-1024x418.png" alt="" class="wp-image-195" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-6-1024x418.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-6-300x122.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-6-768x313.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-6.png 1064w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>I&#8217;ll let the numbers speak for themselves in this section.</p>



<h2>Smoking Cigarettes</h2>



<p>According to the CDC, <a href="https://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;rct=j&amp;q=&amp;esrc=s&amp;source=web&amp;cd=1&amp;cad=rja&amp;uact=8&amp;ved=2ahUKEwi2nbLEioXnAhVlmeAKHYs-AM4QFjAAegQIARAB&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cdc.gov%2Ftobacco%2Fdata_statistics%2Ffact_sheets%2Fadult_data%2Fcig_smoking%2Findex.htm&amp;usg=AOvVaw1lrsmaMLcnUe3I1S6iAF4g">34 000 000 Americans smoke</a>. <a href="http://www.schizophrenia.com/smokereport.htm#">90% of schizophrenics smoke</a>. <a href="https://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;rct=j&amp;q=&amp;esrc=s&amp;source=web&amp;cd=5&amp;cad=rja&amp;uact=8&amp;ved=2ahUKEwjIgLz6ioXnAhXSmOAKHUO6CMEQFjAEegQIDBAU&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.washingtonpost.com%2Fnews%2Fwonk%2Fwp%2F2015%2F02%2F26%2Fthe-terrifying-rate-at-which-smokers-die-from-smoking%2F&amp;usg=AOvVaw0z4xmvDAkNBTEm8aQAQVMf">67% of smokers die from smoking</a>, 474500 a year. Excuse the changing numbers here, in the previous calculation the 1.5% of schizophrenics was from the stat &#8211; and in this second calculation it&#8217;s divided into my guesstimation of total Americans, so 1.666%.</p>



<p>Americans: 300 000 000<br>
Smokers: 34 000 000 (11.33%)<br>
Smokers that die from smoking: 387600 (0.1292%)<br>
Deaths / smokers: 1.14%<br>
Deaths / population: 2 193 000 (0.731%)<br>
Dead smokers / deaths: 17.67%<br>
Smokers / schizophrenics: 90%<br>
Schizophrenics: 5 000 000 (1.666%)<br>
Smokers that are schizophrenics: 4 500 000 (1.5%)<br>
Smokers that are schizophrenics that die: 63 000 <br>
Deaths schizophrenic smokers: 1.26%</p>



<p>You are 11% more likely to die if you smoke while schizophrenic than the average smoker.<br> You are 1.72x as likely to die in a given year if you smoke while schizophrenic than the  average population.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-7-1024x463.png" alt="" class="wp-image-196" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-7-1024x463.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-7-300x136.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-7-768x347.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-7-1536x694.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-7.png 1614w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2>Research</h2>



<p><a href="https://www.hiv.gov/federal-response/funding/budget">0.856 billion is spent on HIV/AIDS efforts a year</a>, affecting <a href="https://www.hiv.gov/hiv-basics/overview/data-and-trends/statistics">1.1 million Americans</a> and <a href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/how-many-people-die-from-aids-each-year-49053">26 000 Americans die from HIV/AIDS each year</a>. $<a href="https://www.cancer.gov/about-cancer/understanding/statistics">147 000 000 000 is spent on cancer research</a> a year and <a href="https://www.cancer.gov/about-cancer/understanding/statistics">609 000 Americans will die from cancer every year</a> &#8211; 38.4% of people will or have had or do have cancer.</p>



<p><a href="http://www.schizophrenia.com/szfacts.htm">$74.65 is spent on research per person diagnosed with schizophrenia</a>, <a href="https://www.hiv.gov/federal-response/funding/budget">$788.70 for HIV/AIDS per person</a> and $1276.04 for cancer per person. </p>



<p>Seems a bit strange, no?</p>



<h2>A Plug</h2>



<p>Want to learn about new articles in tech and being a madman? Subscribe to my mailing list here: <a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL">http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Monetization Blog Part 1: How Long Does Adsense Approval Take &#038;&#038; What Does AdSense &#8216;No Content&#8217; Mean? &#038;&#038; Hackernoon is King of Views</title>
		<link>/2020/01/15/monetization-blog-part-1-how-long-does-adsense-approval-take-what-does-adsense-no-content-mean-hackernoon-is-king-of-views/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 06:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=184</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this article in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud! Overview Since the dawn of my adult life I&#8217;ve always wanted]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/monetization-blog-part-1-how-long-does-adsense-approval-take-what-does-adsense-no-content-mean-hackernoon-is-king-of-views/">View this article in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<h2>Overview</h2>



<p>Since the dawn of my adult life I&#8217;ve always wanted to blog for a living. What could be better than sharing details about my day and accomplishments, helping others in their pursuits &#8211; with work and life? Alas, monetizing your efforts for blogging is a tireless pursuit. As a small publisher, I&#8217;ve created a plan of attack that I&#8217;ve been following relatively closely for the past few weeks, and it appears to be working&#8230; in the future, it&#8217;ll work better! </p>



<h2>Step 1: Publish on My Own Blog + Steemit + Include Mail Plug</h2>



<p>Over on jare.cloud, we have a wordpress installation on my localhost that I use the Simply Static plugin to generate a flat site. I then upload these files to github, which puts my content on dunncreativess.github.io, and then I pull github files down to jare.cloud. During this process, the SteemPress WordPress plugin has published the work on SteemIt&#8230; albeit without the supporting images, who think they should be located on ./ D&#8217;oh!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-1-1024x307.png" alt="" class="wp-image-186" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-1-1024x307.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-1-300x90.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-1-768x230.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-1-1536x460.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-1.png 1679w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>While the revenues are small, it&#8217;s 0-effort revenues &#8211; the best kind!</p>



<p>Now, I&#8217;ve been attempting to get onto Google AdSense to serve ads on my site. All told, a niche blog (or a few niches&#8230;) should earn anywhere from $2.50-$10 / 1000 impressions, and my goal is to keep creating return visitors through all these efforts. I applied sometime over the holidays and was rejected on the 3rd of Jan, and I didn&#8217;t really understand the reason for rejection: &#8216;No Content.&#8217; After searching high and low for an explaination (as they don&#8217;t have a support team &#8211; just a community forum, yuck), either they didn&#8217;t like the fact there were only a half dozen blog entries or they didn&#8217;t like the fact that the blog was hosted on a subdomain of github.io. To solve these issues I&#8217;ve been pushing regular content while my application is reassessed on the new domain: jare.cloud.</p>



<h2>Step 2: Import  (Canonical&#8230;) to Medium Behind Paywall</h2>



<p>The post includes the link at the top to see the original on my site, and we head over to Medium to &#8216;Import Story.&#8217; Because people are encouraged to visit the original site those people without Medium Member accounts can view the content because they can follow the link at the top, and potentially drive revenues from AdSense when I have it. </p>



<p>The best news? Those people with Medium Memberships will drive their own little bucket of revenue to add to the total balance&#8230; and all told, until now, the best performing source of revenues.</p>



<p>My only story to get syndicated by Medium (so far&#8230; stay tuned!) and my best-performing non-Hackernoon post there earned around $5. While this seems trivial, it&#8217;s important to think: 25.4% of the revenues from that article were sourced in the months after the month in which it was published (and the initial rush of traffic was through). If you were to have an article get syndicated every so often &#8211; which is a matter of views, reads and claps in the review period as well as quality &#8211; it would drive the bottom line in a compounding way. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-2-1024x496.png" alt="" class="wp-image-187" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-2-1024x496.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-2-300x145.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-2-768x372.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-2-1536x745.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-2.png 1650w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Your old content continues to earn: it&#8217;s evergreen, and passive.</p>



<p>While the revenues are small, they&#8217;re passive after the post is imported &#8211; and continually creating income!</p>



<h3>Wait, what does canonical mean? Why was it important enough to mention in the subheading?</h3>



<p>A link can point to the original source of the information, allowing the secret powers behind the internet to build the SEO of that original site rather than give all the SEO juices to the new site. In such a way, content creators can leverage accounts on very high-ranking sites (like Hackernoon, Medium, CoinTelegraph (who I&#8217;m still waiting to hear back from about authoring content&#8230;)) and the eventual rankings for keywords and traffic for evermore that is sourced from the depths of Google, Bing et. al. will point to your original source&#8230; not the new one. As Google and search engines punish sites for repeat content, adding a canonical link back to the original source will allow you to rank and build your backlinks with high-grade sites.</p>



<p>Importing to Medium and Hackernoon&#8217;s &#8216;originally seen on&#8230;&#8217; will automatically generate these kinds of links. Voila! Internet magic!</p>



<h2>Step 3: Mail Blast, Twitter Blast, Telegram&#8230; etc</h2>



<p>Mark 15 Jan 2020 (for reference in future editions of this blog series), Mailchimp subscriber count is 44, Twitter follower count is 116, Telegram member count in the group is 126&#8230;</p>



<p>While these are rookie numbers, I can easily syndicate my content across social channels and generate free traffic &#8211; enticing new and engaging repeat interactions. I was thinking to myself as my Medium story on my new account reached 100 views: would I be happier with 1000? Or at the 1000 mark would I just aspire for 10 000? I think part of the human condition is never being satisfied&#8230; so although I feel like these are &#8216;rookie numbers,&#8217; they&#8217;re a measurable improvement from where I was or where I started from. *Pats self on back*</p>



<p>Case in point, this story reflects a common theme among the others: a fair number of views are from referrals from Twitter, where a simple tweet can be retweeted and seen by many &#8211; including people at Hackernoon or Good Audience (a Medium publication) who can give me further exposure!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-3.png" alt="" class="wp-image-188" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-3.png 732w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-3-300x214.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 732px) 100vw, 732px" /></figure>



<h2>Step 4: Re-create on Hackernoon with Canonical Link</h2>



<p>SEO juices&#8230; work like magic! Hackernoon is by far my biggest winner insofar as traffic goes, with over 12k pageviews in total and nearly 11 days worth of reading!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-4-1024x439.png" alt="" class="wp-image-189" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-4-1024x439.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-4-300x129.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-4-768x330.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-4.png 1515w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>What this means is that the views I get from being published and advertised and syndicated on Hackernoon will naturally drive traffic to the original blog, both through the link in the article itself directly as well as with the canonical link building search engine results that&#8217;ll continue driving traffic long after the initial surge has died down. </p>



<p>Hackernoon team tweets my articles more than once to their followers, and each time I see I&#8217;m earning likes, retweets and followers on Twitter, as well as views on all my viewcounters whenever Hackernoon tweets.</p>



<p>Moreover, my Telegram room joins directly correlate to the days in which I publish Hackernoon articles&#8230;</p>



<h2>Step 5: Rinse, Wash, Repeat</h2>



<p>&#8230;which in turn means I should publish more often! Each guide you read to &#8216;earning more on Medium&#8217; or &#8216;earn more blogging&#8217; will tell you that the most sure-fire way to earn more is to write consistently, and produce regular content. This will increase your readership, follows, mail signups.. which in turn powers your next pieces readership. This is how we get the ball rolling&#8230;</p>



<h2>Conclusion</h2>



<p>While the income from my blogging might be marginal, it&#8217;s worth noting that I wouldn&#8217;t prefer doing anything else in the world &#8211; and, in some countries, marginal income is all you need to survive &amp; thrive. The solution is to build out the searchable, indexable content that drives additional traffic over time &#8211; and keep generating content. Today I made a promise to myself to blog whenever I&#8217;m bored&#8230; this is my second &#8216;I&#8217;m bored&#8217; piece today!</p>



<p>In the next piece of this series we&#8217;ll look at the start of AdSense income on my wee, little blog&#8230; whenever they get around to approving me!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Simple Terms: Risk-Free (Free Money!) Futures Trading by Leveraging Options Strategy</title>
		<link>/2020/01/14/in-simple-terms-risk-free-free-money-futures-trading-by-leveraging-options-strategy/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 01:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=176</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this content in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud! Introduction In short: using an options strategy, we can trade any]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1575/1*wQN_FGI4ff7a26rJBS45Og.jpeg" alt=""/></figure>



<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/14/in-simple-terms-risk-free-free-money-futures-trading-by-leveraging-options-strategy/">View this content in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<h1 id="4def">Introduction</h1>



<p>In short: using an options strategy, we can trade any sideways futures strategy with absolutely 0 risk. Price movements up, down, or sideways all yield profitable results. Markets go bullish, bearish, sideways or do a dance — you win no matter what!</p>



<p>Awhile ago, on my Hackernoon, I penned this technical article on&nbsp;<a href="https://hackernoon.com/risk-free-futures-market-making-by-hedging-long-straddle-options-pc1236bl" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Risk-Free Futures Market Making by Hedging Long Straddle Options</a>. In this article I will strive to deliver the points discussed in that first article to a less technical audience — who might be left scratching their heads.</p>



<p>What I mean by ‘sideways’ is that the futures strategy wants to earn the best it can when the markets are neither upwards (bullish) or downwards (bearish).</p>



<h1 id="3b67">Options Strategy</h1>



<p>Places like Deribit via&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/c1bc81c4789b?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Deribit</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/c1bc81c4789b?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Deribit</a>&nbsp;(yes, two separate accounts) and Binance’s JEX platform via&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/57600910a883?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Binance</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/590e572dc6e7?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Miko Ilas</a>&nbsp;allow you to buy and sell BTC (and other coins…) options. An option is a deriviative, meaning that it’s value is derived from the underlying asset but not necessarily correlated — there’s loads of other ‘deriviatives,’ like futures, and that’s why we can trade with so much more leverage on options and futures — they’re not representing the actual asset, but an ‘derived’ idea.</p>



<p>When you buy a call and a put you’re buying the right or ability to buy or sell (respectively) an underlying asset for the specified quantity and price sometime in the future. In European options, this point in the future is only on the day the options expire — or when they run out of time. Note that I’m not obligated to buy or sell — I simply have the right to, should I want to (or it makes financial sense). This means that (if I pay enough money, and someone is there to sell me this option) I should be able to buy the ABILITY to buy BTC for $1 sometime within the next month. That’s probably going to be a very lucrative deal, right? That’s why this option would be worth A LOT of money, and probably astronomically expensive to buy. The price at which you may buy or sell the underlying in the future is called ‘the strike.’</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/2118/1*_Ox5mK27cfvVSMM-VMvZhA.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>In the above screenshot, we see the calls and puts for BTC should the underlying index reach a price of $6750 on expiry or $6500 on expiry. Not that the price of the calls — the right to buy the asset — increases as the strike price decreases, while the cost of puts is decreasing along with it.</p>



<p>On the other side of potential prices for BTC on 24 Jan 2020 (the date the options expire, or end), we see the opposite effect.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/2128/1*90q1y2_UhEPPSN60AfcKew.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Calls are cheaper, puts are more expensive.</p>



<p>Anyways, to get to my point — if you buy both a call and a put with two different strike prices at the same expiry, then you can do so for&nbsp;<em>VERY&nbsp;</em>cheap.</p>



<p>What happens if the price remains around the same? The value of both the call and the put will reduce over time (as their distance to expiry is one of the things that gives them value — the uncertainty and possibility of volatility in this case means that they’re worth more now than they are tomorrow). Eventually, by expiry, they expire worthless.</p>



<p>What happens if the price goes up? The value of the put goes down, and the call goes up. The more the price moves upwards, the less the put is worth — all the way down to worthless — while the call increases in value&nbsp;<em>EXPONENTIALLY</em>.</p>



<p>What happens if the price goes down? The&nbsp;<em>OPPOSITE</em>. One $0 and the other gains value&nbsp;<em>EXPONENTIALLY</em>.</p>



<p>This options strategy is called a ‘long straddle,’ and it essentially means you’re betting on the price moving up or down by a large amount. It’s handy in markets you expect to be volatile — like stocks on days they report earnings or, much less likely in practice, you’re aware of someone’s unannounced merger and acquisition. What this also means is that cryptocurrencies — arguably the most volatile of the assets — allow an options trader to reap in the benefits of a highly volatile market.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1680/1*YnzM0Mta90lpGCtm-wzjKg.jpeg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>For instance, we know that Bitcoin’s mining yields will be half what they have been for awhile sometime in the not-so-distant future. We can surely bet that the price will either go up or down&nbsp;<em>drastically</em>&nbsp;in a short period of time. Take out a long straddle!</p>



<p>Anyways, the above article I wrote on Hackernoon goes on to say that you can use some smart guys math to guesstimate the potential future ‘fair value’ for these long straddles. There’s a few smart guys to choose from, I chose Black Scholes. Now we have a programmatic way to say ‘hey if price moves 5% then I can expect my long straddle to be worth x% more,’ their math model solves for x.</p>



<p>Now, where long straddles lose money is when the markets are sideways. I actually found this strategy when I was dreaming up ways to have less risk with my sideways market trading strategies — be they market makers, for instance, they lose money when the markets go up and down and they’re caught holding a bag of $$ that takes away all my yields.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/974/1*OeEhtZQFJ88ZqAvFzTlVjQ.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>These Market Makers make $$ when the markets are sideways, by earning on $ fees and $ spread. On Deribit,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/94b52ae5502e?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">BitMEX</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/b7ff9821c710?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bybit</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/724240b60d22?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bitfinex</a>&nbsp;Kraken and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/316a1a75d708?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinFLEX</a>&nbsp;they give you REBATES on fees you can earn when people trade against your orders. When you add liquidity to their exchanges, they split their earnings with you — sometimes 50/50!</p>



<p>This means that if I was to know that my max exposure is (how many positions of what sizes I might hold if the markets go one way or another) in $$ and if the market moves y% at 6x leverage, I then liquidate at y%. This is normally bad, but…</p>



<p>I can buy the exact (or almost exact) number puts/calls I need to make sure that if price goes up OR down by any % all the way up to liquidation % then I’m making money on my long straddle when I’m losing money on my Market Maker.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1096/1*f-8ikqYVWMFzCSgXAEthng.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>This applies to any strategy that generates yield when sideways, not just market makers. Say price goes up 5% in a day and my sideways strategy liquidates, and out of my puts and calls one of them is $0 and the other one increased in value&nbsp;<em>A WHOLE HECK OF A LOT.</em></p>



<p>The only way this doesn’t work is if your sideways strategy doesn’t earn more than what you lose when you hold onto the long straddles and their value goes down over time…</p>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization — where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;!!</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Money-Making Decentralized Finance #DeFi Applications</title>
		<link>/2020/01/14/top-money-making-decentralized-finance-defi-applications/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 01:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Github]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=172</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this content in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud! Preface Today we’ll discuss some of the top Decentralized Finance (DeFi)]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1134/0*6V4x3aCeDeW4pZJ9.jpeg" alt=""/></figure>



<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/14/top-money-making-decentralized-finance-defi-applications/">View this content in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<h1 id="cfa9">Preface</h1>



<p>Today we’ll discuss some of the top Decentralized Finance (DeFi) applications that exist, serving people in a trustless manner around the world.</p>



<p>What do I mean by trustless? Given Ether’s immutable (cannot change) smart contracts, the behavior of the money moved around DeFi is such that it cannot be stolen, hacked, lost or misappropriated. Moreover, to earn the word ‘trustless,’ I don’t have to put my trust into a given person or organization — instead, I trust the underlying technology of the contracts they’ve devised. It’s trustless!</p>



<p>I’ve separated the following doc into four sections, comparing the platforms in each: Trading, Borrowing, WBTC Borrowing, and Lending.</p>



<h1 id="f070">Trading</h1>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image.png" alt="" class="wp-image-180" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image.png 892w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-300x139.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-768x356.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 892px) 100vw, 892px" /></figure>



<p>With up to 5x leverage available to traders, dydxprotocol at&nbsp;<a href="http://dydx.exchange/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">dydx.exchange</a>&nbsp;and folks like&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/b3d17ffd3219?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Antonio Juliano</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/67f0a6970a7c?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Zhuoxun Yin</a>&nbsp;bring you a beautiful night-mode interface that allows you to trade some of your favorite assets. Some people — especially those burned by Mt. Gox or other exit scams — are risk-averse to what we call ‘counterparty risk.’ What this means is that some people would much rather have less single points of failure when it comes to the custody of their money — and now we can even trade with leverage on platforms like dydx, so who needs centralized exchanges and their bankster owners?</p>



<p>Dydx lets you borrow, too, but we’ll discuss that more in detail in a future section of this article.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1358/1*b6kUKIB8rLIy9QBa_KE7hw.png" alt=""/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1264/1*Bb6NKV_XMMXdEZkAw1_cfQ.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>I do like how the people at <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://fulcrum.trade/" target="_blank">fulcrum.trade</a> (their parent org: bZx) separated their trading interface from their borrowing interface. We’ll have a closer look at their not-for-margin-trading borrowing interface in a later section, but the fulcrum.trade interface lacks some of the leverage available to dydx — although that negative is helped by having a broader selection of coins.</p>



<h1 id="2015">Borrowing</h1>



<p>With a resounding set of achieved milestones and growth,&nbsp;<a href="http://compound.finance/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">compound.finance</a>&nbsp;and some of the team&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/54f6f223cd12?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Robert Leshner</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/8808a762900f?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Calvin Liu</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/42c8b7010550?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Jayson Hobby</a>&nbsp;have been building another Ether unicorn to add to our growing list.</p>



<p>With millions under management, and a wide variety of coins to choose from to use as collateral, Compound provides a unique opportunity in traditional financial history. It’s apparent that we can over-collateralize loans in crypto against stablecoins and be long those cryptos while getting spending money for the time being — the bullish attitude we have towards these cryptos says that their underlying growth in equity value will outperform the interest rates we’re paying on our stablecoin loans. Boom, we’ve just earned ‘free-ish’ crypto!</p>



<p>Wait, though, this really only applies to Ether and the Ethereum tokens listed on Compound At Time of Writing, and doesn’t appear to apply to WBTC? I really had hoped to diversify my collateral I’m holding to maximize the upwards potential of both DeFi and The King of Coins, $BTC!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/2019/1*ar7ch_ZSKslofPWRdvGJQg.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>(See, a ‘Collateral Factor’ of 0% means we can’t use Wrapped BTC as a collateral coin).</p>



<p>Whatever are we to do?</p>



<h1 id="1990">Borrowing Against WBTC</h1>



<p>Like I’d mentioned above,&nbsp;<a href="http://bzx.network/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">bzx.network</a>&nbsp;has the tools&nbsp;<a href="http://fulcrum.trade/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">fulcrum.trade</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="http://torque.loans/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">torque.loans</a>, and some of the people working wonders like&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/e65fe39afe1d?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Nick Sawinyh</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/7c5899852965?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Kyle J Kistner</a>&nbsp;or their team account here&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/c84b634c7ca3?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">bZx Team</a>. We discussed fulcrum.trade above and hinted at the existence of torque.loans — as a flipside of the same coin, instead of lending and borrowing under-collateralized loans for the purpose of margin trading (a la dydx) we can lend and borrow over-collateralized loans for the purpose of hedging, or whatever other purpose you had in mind (a la compound)!</p>



<p>Simply load up your MetaMask or other wallet, select the token to receive, change your collateral to WBTC and — oh, spoke too soon! Found an error among all tokens when selecting WBTC as collateral.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/2489/1*7FQA5lzB_AAtgsnIVkEJsg.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Wonder if there’s a bug bounty…</p>



<p><em>Soon</em>! You’ll be able to achieve all that diversification and goodness I was speaking about earlier.</p>



<p>EDIT: 15 minutes after my Tweet to bZx and everyone else, at some ungodly hour in the morning that it is right now:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1104/1*APv0pSO6xIE8ozzlL9sNvA.png" alt=""/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1134/1*AGRk-fkbzxjZQ2RZ7dhrsw.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>When was the last time your banks answered the phone that quick?</p>



<p>EDIT AGAIN: It looks as though the bug was on my side, and it’s working fine now that I’ve restarted my machine trying to take a screencast for their team — all is good in the hood, and likely no cause for alarm! I’m going to leave this little diversion in here about the bug-that-could-have-been, because it illustrats how prompt, friendly and helpful bZx’s team are.</p>



<p><a href="https://twitter.com/jarettdunn/status/1216982964233437185" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Check Out the Chat and Follow My Twitter</a>!</p>



<h1 id="85de">Lending</h1>



<p>What do diversified assets and Albert Einstein have in common?</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1181/1*KlOBylBk6AmLAj9PNKQO1w.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Einstein knew that being on the winning side of compound interest would free people — and diversifying your portfolio is step #1 to earning consistent returns. All our moms (or indeed dads, or indeed people-y people) told us ‘don’t put all your eggs in one basket,’ right?</p>



<p>Here’s where stuff gets interesting. Because the three solutions noted above are all open-source and allow and encourage people to develop tools to add to their utility,&nbsp;<a href="http://staked.us/?pid=fr5BC09Vgc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">staked.us</a>&nbsp;of course at&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/2e226f754735?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Staked</a>&nbsp;developed their tool&nbsp;<a href="https://staked.us/v/robo-advisor-yield/?pid=fr5BC09Vgc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Robo Advisor for Yield</a>. Edit: Shoutout to their man&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/94138e7bc2b8?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Devan Purhar</a>, who handles all my support tickets I’ve had on their GitHub (one example link and ensuing conversation to follow). Much appreciated!</p>



<p>What’s it do?</p>



<p>At present, it indexes Compound, dydx, and fulcrum.trade and gives you the best rate among each of them — meaning that if you were to have Robo Advisors for Eth, USDC, DAI and SAI, you’d be earning the best yields for four different assets (one might moon! And: eth staking, coming soon!) — maybe more different assets in the future:&nbsp;<a href="https://github.com/Stakedllc/robo-advisor-yield/issues/5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://github.com/Stakedllc/robo-advisor-yield/issues/5</a>&nbsp;at any given point.</p>



<p>They’ve used on-chain, open-source solutions in the keeping with crypto spirit and in order to bolster the offerings of the participant protocols. This means that they add a layer to the tech without adding a party to be considered when thinking about counterparty risk — the trust is still in the tech (which has all been thoroughly audited, be sure)!</p>



<h1 id="050e">Conclusion</h1>



<p>So head on over to&nbsp;<a href="http://staked.us/?pid=fr5BC09Vgc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">staked.us</a>, check out their platform where you can earn returns on staking PoS coins, but more importantly check out their&nbsp;<a href="https://staked.us/v/robo-advisor-yield/?pid=fr5BC09Vgc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Robo Advisor for Yield</a>&nbsp;today. You can mint your own RAYs and begin the journey to doubling your crypto, too!</p>



<p>Looking to trade undercollateralized loans, on the blockchain and without a third party? Check out some of the other solutions, like dydx.exchange and fulcrum.trade.</p>



<p>Looking to borrow funds against your crypto? I’d recommend compound.finance or torque.loans.</p>



<p>DeFi is here to stay — banking the unbanked — let the games commence!</p>



<h1 id="0d3a">Bonus 1: Nuo.Network</h1>



<p>Nuo.network (with an encouring team including team account&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/d834ca07a5ac?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Nuo Network</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/29f0b8f49104?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Varun Deshpande</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/2e63d860a40d?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Siddharth Verma</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/a48f2610a12d?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Praneet Sinha</a>&nbsp;allows you to lend and borrow — including WBTC — and margin trade using non-custodial addresses, like the other contenders in this list.</p>



<p>Why didn’t Nuo make the original list?</p>



<p>Their smart contracts aren’t public — meaning that&nbsp;the interface to build on nuo.network is controlled by their team, and doesn’t allow folks to create additional value by plugging pieces together and offering something brand new — like&nbsp;<a href="https://staked.us/v/robo-advisor-yield/?pid=fr5BC09Vgc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">staked.us’s Robo Advisor for Yield</a>&nbsp;does.</p>



<p>However, the Staked team reassures us that they’ve been in touch with Nuo’s and that — pending an upcoming update — the code will be public and the joys of Nuo can be introduced into the Robo Advisor for Yield.</p>



<p>Check more details on this post I made outlining Nuo as a possible way to earn yield (and earn yield on WBTC) on Staked’s RAY:&nbsp;<a href="https://github.com/Stakedllc/robo-advisor-yield/issues/5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://github.com/Stakedllc/robo-advisor-yield/issues/5</a></p>



<h1 id="3258">Bonus 2: Uniswap</h1>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1389/1*h9q1b-UntQQAeNW0MQfWMw.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>People like&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/5b6f44a990f8?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Callil Capuozzo</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/ec7001b3c11f?source=post_page-----75a757dc6408----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hayden Adams</a>&nbsp;have been building Uniswap: Heralded as Ethereum’s unicorn — Uniswap allows a whole bunch of interesting features. These include swapping Ether tokens and paying a small fee all the way up to submitting your own new exchange (token) to the network and having all your friends increase your token’s liquidity.</p>



<p>What happens (as far as I know, and in Laymen’s) is, as I undertand it, a liquidity pool I can put funds into so that market makers and other parties can execute trades at leverage or for ‘free-ish.’ These funds then produce yield as the market makers have paid fees which gets added to the pot, then available for the liquidity providers to later withdraw. I may be incorrect in my understanding or I may have forgotten something.</p>



<p>Check out an idea I had to generate yield by COMBINING Compound and Uniswap (I know, insane) here:&nbsp;<a href="https://github.com/Stakedllc/robo-advisor-yield/issues/3" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://github.com/Stakedllc/robo-advisor-yield/issues/3</a></p>



<p>And see an idea of mine for integrating Uniswap in their own traditional sense into Staked.us’s RAY here:&nbsp;<a href="https://github.com/Stakedllc/robo-advisor-yield/issues/6" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://github.com/Stakedllc/robo-advisor-yield/issues/6</a></p>



<h1 id="524f">Disclaimer</h1>



<p>No, I don’t work for Staked.</p>



<p>Yes, I am an affiliate and will earn affiliate commissions if you sign up using my links.</p>



<p>No, there are no other affiliate links in this doc — I gave an honest and unbiased opinion here, not affiliate spam <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/1f642.png" alt="🙂" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>



<p>You can be Staked.us affiliated, too!</p>



<p>After signing up for Staked.us (here’s the full url of my affiliate link:&nbsp;<a href="https://staked.us/?pid=fr5BC09Vgc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://staked.us/?pid=fr5BC09Vgc</a>) , you’ll have access to the Partners area:&nbsp;<a href="https://staked.us/stake/partners/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://staked.us/stake/partners/</a></p>



<p>The author is, however, employed by Coindex Labs — leading us nicely into a plug:</p>



<h1 id="cfd7">A Plug</h1>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization — where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;!!</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>How do people with mental health illnesses like schizophrenia or other psychoses think?</title>
		<link>/2020/01/14/how-do-people-with-mental-health-illnesses-like-schizophrenia-or-other-psychoses-think/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 01:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=168</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this article in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud! He stared out from behind his eyes wide shut. In front]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/722/0*xYsewcQ1HGRJq-Us" alt=""/></figure>



<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/14/how-do-people-with-mental-health-illnesses-like-schizophrenia-or-other-psychoses-think/">View this article in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud!</a></p>



<p>He stared out from behind his eyes wide shut. In front of him, displayed like countless myriad millions television screens laid one next to each other, were the lives of everyone he’d ever lived — partially, completely, not at all or fully.</p>



<p>He focused on one where he was little Jane being picked up and twirled by her dad. In ecstasy, Jane laughed in joy and giggled in fear as she twirled higher and faster. These are the moments she would remember with elation for the rest of her life, years after her father died in a tragic motorbike accident that could have been avoided — years after Jane has her own kids, twirling them with the same gusto every opportunity she’d had.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/591/0*qdoq097kM6cGT8MP.jpg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Focusing again, James was Ira being raped by four men in a back alley. The pain, anguish, fear and feel of the knife built anxiety and pain, paranoia and shame for a lifetime — never to be forgiven, forgotten, and never to be repaired.</p>



<p>He was the rapists, exacting dominance. Both the shameful and the shameless.</p>



<p>He was the onlooker, too scared to intervene. Coward. Dastardly.</p>



<p>He was the doctor, the father, the stillborn.</p>



<p>James’ eyes shifted and saw 100s more ‘screens,’ 100s more entries into the days, moments, lifetimes of people around the world — billions of people he was doomed to relive the lives of, over and over, backwards and forwards throughout time and back again.</p>



<p>There was no escape.</p>



<p>He is God, having only ever wanted to sacrifice immortality and — as is the only Godly pursuit — die and be forgotten.</p>



<p>He is Jane.</p>



<p>He is Ira.</p>



<p>He will wake up tomorrow and be Josh for a day.</p>



<p>A moment, Alex.</p>



<p>An infinity, Gods long dead and forgotten by history. Contrived and devised, planned and propagated by people — propagated to subjugate, control, extract money and exact dominance — immortal by design, infinite in the eyes of those who can’t plausibly conceive infinity.</p>



<p>Eyes wide shut.</p>



<p>Countless more animals, rocks, alien worlds — dissociation is a scary, scary thing. One loses one’s senses and knowledge of one’s self, one loses one’s memories and sense of humanity. As a rock on Mars, what do we remember of the Holocaust? What do we remember of Christianity? What do we remember of James? As a rock on Neptune, what do we remember of the rock on Mars?</p>



<p>Being God, how could he refute God?</p>



<p>He’d long since felt the panic leave his body. He’d long since laid there, catatonic, wishing for a sanity he remembered in his childhood. Drifting in and out of consciousness, drifting in and out of the conscience of others. He was all of his ex lovers, he was every side of every argument he’d ever had. He was the ultra-rich. He was the ultra-poor. He was puppy, squid, house. Woman, house, fish, bee. Acceleration, deceleration. Up, down.</p>



<p>As his mind entered the all-familiar mantra of dichotomies, a part of him wondered if he were stuck like this — forever lost between perceptions and realities, forever without a name, legacy, or history. A part of him chimed in that this is what happens every time, and like the Beatles said the sun will come out tomorrow.. There will always be another day, another dawn, another lapse of time where he was he and he wasn’t Jane, Ira, or God. These two parts argued — there were other voices that chimed in — the voices argued, and took bets amongst themselves about whether or not this was the last time, the final straw that broke that camel’s back and landed him forever lost. The voices took bets whether or not he would commit suicide today, tomorrow, die by arrow or die by plane engines falling from the sky — the voices argued…</p>



<p>The dichotomies grew louder to keep them from taking over. To keep them at bay: ocean, sky. Arrow, wound. Nothingness, everything. Quantum. Three states. On, off, both and neither. 1, 0,…</p>



<p>Catatonic. Not moving. Not interacting. Fearing the next day, fearing the chances the voices won and saw him off himself with a bottle of bleach. Fearing God’s revenge. Fearing Ira’s rapists. Fearing Jane’s dad’s drunk driver hit-and-run. Panic sets in…</p>



<p>The heart feels on fire, the heart feels as though it’ll give out. The breathing speeds up. The thoughts continue, and the feedback cycle sets in — faster heart, faster breathing, more psychosis, faster heart, faster breathing.. In the past, James had called emergency services fearing the physical symptoms. Now, having learned how his body tricks his mind tricks his body — a tango nobody wants to endure — he endures it. He sits through it. Looking out from eyes wide shut, he’s aware of the room around him behind closed eyes. Open eyes? He can’t tell anymore. They’re shutting and opening, he can see through them when shut. He is infinite. He is God.</p>



<p>He wouldn’t wish this fate on his worst enemies.</p>



<p>He is patient zero.</p>



<p>He wants to start support groups. He wants to help. He wants to educate, lift stigma, teach, and help others find a peace within themselves they can’t find on their own. He wants to be a voice for those without a voice.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/827/0*FUcYxeuEueSWPZ0J" alt=""/></figure>



<p>He can’t.</p>



<p>He’s disabled.</p>



<p>He’s destroyed — inwardly, outwardly — he lays there each night on the brink of madness and puts on a smile each day for friends and family. He turns to drugs and alcohol to turn down the mantra, turn down the voices, and takes his medication knowing that The Man’s pharmaceutical agenda is to keep his voice from being heard. He’s dangerous. He threatens the status quo.</p>



<p>He’s not alone.</p>



<p>Squelched by the drugs — prescribed and not — he’s silenced by a system that didn’t give him a chance. The trade is a fair one — lose your autonomy for a series of time that goes by without hallucinations or delusions. Keep yourself in the ‘real’ reality, take these pills, we’ve supplied loads of cocaine on the street to keep you in check.</p>



<p>He is your cousin, your son, your friend, your lover.</p>



<p>As much as he’s everyone, everyone is him.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
