<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>jare &#8211; DunnCreativeSS</title>
	<atom:link href="/author/jare/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Get Your Git Here!</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 03:20:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-CA</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.3.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Decentralized Social Media</title>
		<link>/2019/12/30/decentralized-social-media/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 03:19:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=155</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[**submitted to Hackernoon, submitted to GCNews.io** Incentive I’m not necessarily after $200, I’m after a voice. While published on Hackernoon]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>**submitted to Hackernoon, submitted to GCNews.io**</p>



<h2>Incentive</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-twitter wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Let&#39;s try an experiment: $200 BTC bounty for the best review of decentralized social media.<br><br>The ideal piece covers not just crypto efforts like Voice/Akasha, but allied tech like Mastodon, CRDT, Bittorrent, Git.<br><br>Reply to this tweet with your post! cc <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@cz_binance</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@VitalikButerin</a> <a href="https://t.co/hhS0TXU9fX">https://t.co/hhS0TXU9fX</a></p>&mdash; Balaji S. Srinivasan (@balajis) <a href="https://twitter.com/balajis/status/1210639705143951360?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 27, 2019</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>I’m not necessarily after $200, I’m after a voice. While <a href="https://hackernoon.com/@jare">published on Hackernoon many times</a> and having a <a href="https://github.com/dunncreativess">Github with 100+ repositories</a>, I’d thought it might be a good idea to take part in this competition and get the attention of <a href="https://twitter.com/balajis">https://twitter.com/balajis</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance">https://twitter.com/cz_binance</a> &#8211; maybe even <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin">https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin</a>.</p>



<h1>Preface: Censorship</h1>



<p>This most recent bit of news time saw YouTube censor many crypto-related voices, and a mail broadcast I received from LBRY mentioned a few (or a lot?) of them ended up there to promote their views and opinions. Moreover, we saw MetaMask removed from the Android Play Store (and also, consequently, my device), purportedly for mining crypto and more likely for offering a competing environment where people can consume the internet than the Play Store itself. This level of censorship creates a world where a few big players (aka. the ultra-rich) can dictate to us what content we can consume where, and leads the way to a dangerous version of the internet where all we can possibly consume is the ultra-rich’s agenda.<br></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1gypbqvU8CjCzicIgUaUFeVLX56b7Te7lREUwnDONBeR9DMGKZo5NmhRbJBZ4ZGP5wvN_Ze4cSy0XxFxZ0LcX5YxynExXuxQOQRXXrBQfrvJb7W-aVqSS6ybJrjbRCUkjmx16S-R" alt=""/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/4qwxvQORDVRn_oxTr_nuxml1XJZLFwyXCl8daa-l7-PRVzmaE2r4NGU9vv-AT-p6BU_CPQD7EQwsHA7XnOVhs6aWbxa9LZEeDawyXMMVqyPWFT_EvREpnsAOEt2UGl_I_WoxAPKp" alt=""/></figure>



<p>The answer is an open and vibrant decentralized community where censorship plays no part. Minds.com comes to mind, but there has to be other underlying mechanisms to preserve the rights and freedoms of people everywhere &#8211; even in a censorship-free arena, we shouldn’t be subjected to hate speech and other dark web reminiscent dark corners of the internet. This kind of content from supremacists and trolls alike would hurt the overall image and therein hurt adoption &#8211; which would kill our creation before it’s born.<br></p>



<p>SteemIt comes to mind &#8211; along with it’s various interfaces, (and in recent iterations allow an even more well-thought / which allow a) way for people to downvote ‘bad’ content. This is a great solution for the decentralized community to self-moderate it’s own content monstrosity, but by and large this creates a demand for labor that can’t easily be rewarded (cue Steem’s life-long battle trying to figure out how to balance inflationary rewards with the need to self-moderate &#8211; and their nearly Steem-killing problem with people using the reward structure to bribe rewards and over-reward themselves).<br></p>



<h1>Monetization and Reward Mechanisms</h1>



<p>At this point, it’s crucial to remind ourselves that Blockchain is not cryptocurrency. Read that again! The huge interest that the ICO craze pulled into Blockchain was equally as damaging to the image of Blockchain &#8211; if not more &#8211; than the dark web’s dependency on Bitcoin as an anonymous online currency was to the image of Bitcoin. A reward mechanism for users for a decentralized social platform is not required, but could benefit actual users &#8211; actual people &#8211; for their content and social interactions.<br></p>



<p>If there’s a reward mechanism built into a new decentralized social media, it should be one that allows users to reward their favorite users through micropayments and allows the generation of additional rewards through staking an amount of e-currency someone already has &#8211; showing a dedication to the network and allowing the network more buying pressure than selling pressure. Steem does this, but I’m guessing people would want to stake more if there were more perceived reward &#8211; ie. you could earn more from your social presence as a direct result of staking more.&nbsp;<br></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/tawIPlUa64-MNSJ2LPqEAZDmam5AF-HvZ_d_J6iFcNreeFphWd9CzwRG5AkMrSee2i2Op4R0ivoHrBSHYyu_88pT2YUmCX-oJw5io_LRWixstkez3Q74z8XVczk0mv-dE76LEFvk" alt=""/></figure>



<p>If I had a dime for each time I had this conversation &#8211; with some underemployed or unemployed, disenfranchised friend on the internet &#8211; if we had a way to monetize and reward engaging social content we could empower the unbanked worldwide.&nbsp;<br></p>



<h1>Moderation</h1>



<p>&#8212; Note this isn’t the original (or even unoriginal) purposes of this neural evolutionary AI project &#8211; I’m going out on a limb here, without consulting our AI devs on this &#8211; but I think that the given problem would be socially acceptable content, and one could train the proof of fitness to provide that goal. Why not? &#8212;</p>



<p>In projects in the past like Akasha or Mastadon, one key feature that’s perplexed developers is how to monitor and remove spam, plagiarism, hate speech, etc. In a world with increasingly smart AI, there’s no reason to put this labor onto individual users like in Steem &#8211; one could create a neural evolutionary AI that’s rewarded by achieving happier individuals through a ‘report’ mechanism on leftover content. If something’s reported, then that competing generation responsible for that post is hit with a ‘ding’ that keeps it from being the master genome in that set &#8211; and the master genome carries on to start a new generation of competing genomes to do a better job in the next set of posts that are all moderated.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The computational power required to run these competing and learning sets of problem-solving algos could be served by p2p nodes that are run by users around the world &#8211; with as little as a laptop, in another chain that rewards the users submitting to the champion net.&nbsp;</p>



<p><a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1VBJ0UoY7MjeIEX0ljPj6G35qqnSizTv-XgzCiAx04F8/edit?usp=sharing">Read more in OuroborosChain &#8211; a white paper detailing neural evolutionary AI</a>.</p>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;</em></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization – where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em> !!</em></p>



<h1>Disclaimer</h1>



<p>The author is Chief Liquidity Officer for Coindex Labs.<br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Benefits of Neomenia and Crypto Growth Hacker &#8211; Compound Your Crypto!</title>
		<link>/2019/12/23/benefits-of-neomenia-and-crypto-growth-hacker-compound-your-crypto/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 11:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=146</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Hi SteemIt! View this post in it&#8217;s original form on dunncreativess.github.io! View my other posts on Hackernoon. Yes I&#8217;m promoting]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hi SteemIt! View this post in it&#8217;s <a href="http://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/12/23/benefits-of-neomenia-and-crypto-growth-hacker-compound-your-crypto/">original form on dunncreativess.github.io</a>! View my <a href="https://hackernoon.com/@jare">other posts on Hackernoon.</a> Yes I&#8217;m promoting this post &#8211; I think I have some info you folks might appreciate!</p>



<p>With results among users ranging from 3-4%, and a total net returns for some users at 16-22+% over a few days, it looks as though Neomenia is here to make an improvement in people&#8217;s lives.</p>



<p>Trading on three exchanges simultaneously and hedging risk by altering strategies based on conditions on a given exchange, it looks like Crypto Growth Hacker is the one-stop-shop for crypto investment diversification.</p>



<p>Neomenia now supports trailing takeprofit, meaning the upwards potential of a good buy or sell has increased significantly with your configurable takeprofit. It also has a special feature where the stop size is reduced by the difference in price as a percent when it moves in the right direction, so that you can lock in your profits faster while having a larger stoploss in case sh#t hits the fan.</p>



<p>The win/lose ratio is 5:1&#8230; and <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/XBTUSD/FkIqJJcy-Introducing-Neomenia/">it backtested 10 000% on TradingView</a>.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s a price action observed in one spot confirmed in another confirmed again by a direcitonal indicator, and that&#8217;s all I&#8217;m allowed saying under NDA.. but if you want to know more, join the Neomenia chat on Telegram! <a href="https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A">https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-1024x408.png" alt="" class="wp-image-149" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-1024x408.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-300x119.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-768x306.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-1536x611.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1.png 1874w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Crypto Growth Hacker is indexing Bitmex, Deribit and Binance Futures now and using a complex market making strategy on the first two while employing Neomenia on the third. The result is a bot that&#8217;s incredibly resilient and doesn&#8217;t take very many hits that last too too long &#8211; and shows steady gains.</p>



<p>Want to know more? Join our Telegram! <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-148" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1.png 880w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1-300x163.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1-768x416.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 880px) 100vw, 880px" /></figure>



<p>What&#8217;s great about both offerings is the community. We have scores of new users &#8211; and scores of people supporting us through thick and thin &#8211; and that all starts with posts like these, to raise awareness.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4-498x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-150" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4-498x1024.png 498w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4-146x300.png 146w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4.png 622w" sizes="(max-width: 498px) 100vw, 498px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5-498x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-151" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5-498x1024.png 498w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5-146x300.png 146w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5.png 622w" sizes="(max-width: 498px) 100vw, 498px" /></figure>



<p>We&#8217;re helping each other, and helping ourselves. You&#8217;re more than welcome to join! We&#8217;d be happy to have you. Ask questions! Grow with us!</p>



<p>We also have attractive referral campaigns for those of you who have an audience or know the inner workings of the magical internet.. ask us how to get 10% of your referral&#8217;s profits, or a straight (and recurring.. ) fee!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-147" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1.png 899w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1-288x300.png 288w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1-768x800.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 899px) 100vw, 899px" /></figure>



<p><a href="https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A">Neomenia Telegram</a></p>



<p><a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">Crypto Growth Hacker Telegram</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Week of Neomenia LIVE Trading Binance Futures</title>
		<link>/2019/12/18/a-week-of-neomenia-live-trading-binance-futures/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=140</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Neomenia is currently running on 8 subscriber&#8217;s accounts, creating predictable yield in sideways or bullish or bearish markets! The strategy]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1024x635.png" alt="" class="wp-image-141" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1024x635.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-300x186.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-768x476.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1.png 1276w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Neomenia is currently running on 8 subscriber&#8217;s accounts, creating predictable yield in sideways or bullish or bearish markets! </p>



<p>The strategy itself is protected under NDA, but as much as I can say it finds price indication in one place confirms it in another then also confirms with directional indication. The result is magic!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1024x692.png" alt="" class="wp-image-142" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1024x692.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-300x203.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-768x519.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-120x80.png 120w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1.png 1224w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>I&#8217;ve created a web interface to launch bots on our own Google Cloud Compute account, taking the hassle and potential issues with configuring your own VPS with bot options straight off your shoulders.. and as it costs us a pretty penny a month, and saves you renting your own VPS, it&#8217;s basically a free VPS giveaway! Woot!</p>



<p>I&#8217;m writing an update predominantly to create FOMO, but the community results speak for themselves&#8230;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-143" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-1.png 626w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-1-300x124.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 626px) 100vw, 626px" /></figure>



<p>The price of the bot will increase from $49 or $59 (depending if you use our Binance Futures referral code) up to minimum $99 in the new year. The time to come onboard is now! Have no fear, our team and community moderators have your back through thick and thin.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn4.png" alt="" class="wp-image-144" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn4.png 606w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn4-300x137.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 606px) 100vw, 606px" /></figure>



<p>So &#8211; come on in, grab it while it&#8217;s cheap!</p>



<p>There are other monetization methods for people who otherwise have no access to futures, join <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> and check out the pin!</p>



<p>Interested in Neomenia? Join here! <a href="https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A">https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A</a></p>



<p><em>! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization – where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em> !!</em>(<strong>Disclaimer</strong>: <em>The Author is the Chief Liquidity Officer at Coindex</em>) </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trade Smarter, Trade Together! Crypto Growth Hacker Crowdfunded Bot Tokens to Mint</title>
		<link>/2019/12/14/trade-smarter-trade-together-crypto-growth-hacker-crowdfunded-bot-tokens-to-mint/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 02:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=134</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;m offering my market maker bot one of two possible ways: 1. I provide you the source code and you]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1024x612.png" alt="" class="wp-image-135" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1024x612.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-300x179.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-768x459.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2.png 1452w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>I&#8217;m offering my market maker bot one of two possible ways: 1. I provide you the source code and you can configure your apikey and secret and review the code to make sure nothing malicious happens, on a profit-share scheme where you provide 40% of the earnings after every month &#8211; as confirmed by API. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3.png" alt="" class="wp-image-136" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3.png 1000w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-300x296.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-768x759.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></figure>



<p>2. I&#8217;m creating a dividend token for sale to the general public (including Americans) that I then pay monthly 70% of the profit (10% for me, 15% reinvested for compounding effect, 5% BNB holdings). The dividend trading fund would span multiple bots, with an initial spread of 25% Neomenia BTC 25% Neomenia ETH 25% Deribit arb + options BTC 25% Eth. The dividend token script I&#8217;m using doesn&#8217;t have voting, but we&#8217;ll vote on bot % holdings and bot strategies using an off-chain voting system enabled by etherscan reports on holding %, anything more than 5% gets a vote.</p>



<p>The benefits of option 1 is that you get to run one of my bots with a profit-share model, the benefits of option 2 are: a. if you&#8217;re an american citizen you can now kindof take part in leveraged futures trading, by way of the token. b. as our BNB accumulates, we pay less fees c. as our BNB accumulates, we get more % from our referrals d. the combined notional traded on Binance will allow us to further climb their fee ladder. You can also refer people to the crowdfunded bot, for every 100 tokens at $1 worth of Eth apiece minted you get 10 tokens. For every 100 tokens that a referral of your referral mints you get 5 tokens.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-imgur wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-imgur"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="imgur-embed-pub" lang="en" data-id="PBQZAB1"><a href="https://imgur.com/PBQZAB1">View post on imgur.com</a></blockquote><script async src="//s.imgur.com/min/embed.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<ol><li>Join Telegram https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</li><li>Fill out this form.</li><li>Send your Eth here: 0x9c33b574c8D013Ba501a897484E3b92a27A3FDB8</li><li>Fill the TXID in this form.</li><li>Tokens will be minted as often as possible, with the least often being once a month before dividends are paid.</li></ol>



<p>Form to fill: https://forms.gle/bDQmuUhQQ5FJPvgN6</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Our Next-Gen Crypto Trading Bot Neomenia Goes Live!</title>
		<link>/2019/12/05/our-next-gen-crypto-trading-bot-neomenia-goes-live/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 19:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=128</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Intro http://patbot1.duckdns.org/ Start: Sat Nov 30 2019 14:21:06 GMT+0000 (UTC) Now: Sun Dec 01 2019 05:17:39 GMT+0000 (UTC) BTC Notional]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>Intro</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-473x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-129" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-473x1024.png 473w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-139x300.png 139w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image.png 591w" sizes="(max-width: 473px) 100vw, 473px" /></figure>



<p>http://patbot1.duckdns.org/<br> Start: Sat Nov 30 2019 14:21:06 GMT+0000 (UTC)<br> Now: Sun Dec 01 2019 05:17:39 GMT+0000 (UTC)<br> BTC Notional traded recent memory: 38.44400000000188<br> Current position: -1.952<br> BTC % Delta: 31.89%<br> BTC % ROI / day projected: 51.22%<br> BTC % APR projected: 1.869e+4%</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-1-473x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-130" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-1-473x1024.png 473w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-1-139x300.png 139w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-1.png 591w" sizes="(max-width: 473px) 100vw, 473px" /></figure>



<h2>Steps to Reproduce</h2>



<p>Step 1. Join our Telegram https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A<br> Step 2. Create a net-new Binance account, and enable futures, and create an api key after enabling futures http://www.binance.com/en/register?ref=27039658, You&#8217;re allowed to have as many Binance accounts as you like, while only verifying one &#8211; the max daily withdrawal on an unverified account is still huge<br> Step 3: Sent the subscription fee to our wallet 0x55FC78F760fBeb15A8a14ce2B8e9DCfA4CE0f966<br> Step 4: Enter your transaction ID on this form.<br> Step 5: And the last 6 characters of your API key.<br> Step 6: The team will manually add you to the bot&#8217;s license, and send you the executable file and other directions.<br> Step 7: Run the appropriate exports or setx&#8217;s from within env.sh. DO NOT simply run env.sh, it won&#8217;t work, copy and paste the commands into a terminal/cmd window. On windows, open a net new cmd when finished.<br> Step 8: Run the executable for app for BTCUSDT, eth for ETHUSDT, and balance for a balance output graph like the ones you&#8217;re used to seeing.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-2-473x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-131" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-2-473x1024.png 473w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-2-139x300.png 139w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-2.png 591w" sizes="(max-width: 473px) 100vw, 473px" /></figure>



<h2>Neomenia FAQs</h2>



<h1>FAQ 1: Settings</h1>



<p>variables with ‘eth’ prepended are the same, for the ethusdt bot<br></p>



<p>delaybetweenorder, higher for more delay before a new limit order</p>



<p>takeProfit, in % what gains to lock in before market out</p>



<p>stopLoss, in % what losses to accept before market out</p>



<p>tgUser, your Telegram username for use with the Telegram bot</p>



<p>key, APIkey</p>



<p>secret, APIsecret<br></p>



<p>&#8212;-<br></p>



<p>Note that the key and secret are never communicated anywhere off the local machine, except in signed requests to the exchange (which hide your details). Wireshark sniffing can confirm this.<br></p>



<p>&#8212;-<br></p>



<p>site, the http or https address where your server is located. You can google curl ipify to find your address if you’re in a headless server, or google ‘what is my ip’ if you have an interface. You can set up DNS forwarding on duckdns.org or register your own spiffy shiny new domain if you like.</p>



<p>poirt, which port to run the balance server on. Use 80 for http 443 for https (which isn’t enabled anyhow) or a higher number like 8080 if you’re having permissions issues.</p>



<p>maxFreePerc, what maximum % of the wallet will be used before stopping ordering in the same direction. Note this doesn’t count existing limit orders, which could max our margin if your delay is too small.</p>



<p>orderSizeMult, for a $50 USDT account use 5, for $250 use 1, for $500 use 0.5. Etc.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-3-1024x549.png" alt="" class="wp-image-132" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-3-1024x549.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-3-300x161.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-3-768x412.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-3.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2>FAQ 2: Legal Mumbo Jumbo</h2>



<p>In no way are our team or any affiliated member responsible for any gains or losses you might experience. Previous action is no indication implied or assured of future performance. Risk only what you can afford to lose. This bot does not constitute financial advice by any means, and is meant to be used in an educational, communal, and fun format.</p>



<h2>Sign Up Now!</h2>



<p><a href="https://forms.gle/hWa7uzZFg9nD1khg8">https://forms.gle/hWa7uzZFg9nD1khg8</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blog Monetization on SteemIt.com and Dblog.io</title>
		<link>/2019/11/24/blog-monetization-on-steemit-com-and-dblog-io/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 22:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[steemit]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=119</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[See this post in it&#8217;s original form on dunncreativess.github.io! Awhile ago I installed Steempress on my WordPress blog on ,]]>/</description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/24/blog-monetization-on-steemit-com-and-dblog-io/">See this post in it&#8217;s original form on dunncreativess.github.io!</a></p>



<p>Awhile ago I installed Steempress on my WordPress blog on ,/ and Simply Static to export my WordPress site as a static site to local drive and the git commit it to my github.io repository.</p>



<p>Lo and behold, after originally thinking that Steempress wasn&#8217;t working, it appears it is!</p>



<p>I&#8217;ve even included the dblog.io dblog tag, which means they appear here:</p>



<p></p>



<p>The only issue is that I have to replace the images from localhost to dunncreativess.github.io. Small price to pay! If I were to instead host my WordPress somewhere in the cloud (even on a port other than 80/443), it would work.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-39-1024x155.png" alt="" class="wp-image-120" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-39-1024x155.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-39-300x45.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-39-768x116.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-39.png 1202w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-40-1024x189.png" alt="" class="wp-image-121" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-40-1024x189.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-40-300x55.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-40-768x142.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-40.png 1256w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Now, $0.06 USD in crypto over 7 posted articles might not sound like much &#8211; but in an adless presentation that solves the monetization-without-bugging-people sense, I&#8217;m now being rewarded by all these people voting on my content instead of a centralized force like Adsense and you&#8217;ll notice that my github.io and my hackernoon don&#8217;t share ads!</p>



<p>It&#8217;s also continuously improving.. that $0.04 is for the lastest article, meaning I&#8217;m gaining momentum.</p>



<p>I mentioned the benefits of DPoS at length to the folks at Hackernoon when they were dreaming up HN 2.0.</p>



<p>Monetization is key. Incentivization is what rules the internet and any publication platform should be centered around ‘how do we turn content into $.’</p>



<p>I’ve said it before and I’ll say it again that we need to consider tokenization and blockchain in order to put the ability to upvote/downvote content (self regulate and moderate) while also allowing shareholders and prolific content producers to have the most influence on the monetary rewards for contributing authors. While Steem appears to be failing because of a misbalance in currencies producing bidbots and scammy 115% returns on promotion budgets, there are alternative sidechains to consider that did away with the SBD concept and pay everything out as VESTed income, so that people are &#8211; in turn &#8211; vested into the success of the platform. Check <a href="http://smoke.io/">smoke.io</a> and <a href="http://whaleshares.io/">whaleshares.io</a>.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-42-1024x571.png" alt="" class="wp-image-123" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-42-1024x571.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-42-300x167.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-42-768x428.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-42-1536x857.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-42.png 1544w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-43-1024x559.png" alt="" class="wp-image-124" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-43-1024x559.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-43-300x164.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-43-768x419.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-43-1536x839.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-43.png 1617w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>I truly believe in DPoS as a technology &#8211; although with a few tweaks it could serve far better than it does on <a href="http://steemit.com/">steemit.com</a>.</p>



<p>When someone shares or upvotes a story, if it then becomes popular and earns a ton of rewards through the social algorithm % of inflation, that person who shared it to get it popular in the first place earns a % of that social % as a curator &#8211; as do all the other curators, weighted by when they expressed interest. This is important for a few reasons. .first, as your most prolific writers along with the team and the stakeholders would be the biggest currency holders, they can do a lot of good by spending time (or automation ways to) upvote posts they like, and get exposure to users or groups of users they think deserve it &#8211; you only get a certain number of upvotes/downvotes per day, which you can increase or decrease by increasing or decreasing the ‘strength’ of your vote (out of 100%). Second &#8211; these large token holders would also be paramount in fighting spam and self-regulating the environment. If there are people drawn to the site with the gleam in their eye of earning crypto by regurgitating content or plagiarizing, these highly vested people can ‘downvote’ said spammy posts and undo any earnings they may have accumulated &#8211; to the point that their post gets a negative up/downvote ratio and can be taken off of web + mobile + whatever UI interfaces to the chain. In short, you gain currency by sharing, creating, or upvoting content… . proportional to your VESTed interest in the platform.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-41-1024x607.png" alt="" class="wp-image-122" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-41-1024x607.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-41-300x178.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-41-768x455.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-41.png 1516w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Moreover, there can be other % uses for the inflation of the currency that can do a lot of good &#8211; one of the integral parts of DPoS is the ‘delegated’ part where there are many nodes hosted by many people, and they can acquire votes from users that are weighted based on how vested they are into the system as a whole. Some of these people (usually the top 21) will earn a % of the inflation pie just for helping produce blocks &#8211; but how they accumulate votes is the important part. They must continually deliver value and hold the network’s priorities at heart in order to outperform those other contenders &#8211; which is good for the network.</p>



<p>Lastly, there can be a ‘team’ or ‘reserve’ % of inflation that can be used to continually fundraise based on the current value of the coin. While everyone is earning via social algos or by being a witness, the team can have a source of continual income with which to spend on the project or improving various aspects to it.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://community.hackernoon.com/images/emoji/twitter/slight_smile.png?v=6" alt=":slight_smile:"/></figure>



<p><a href="https://community.hackernoon.com/u/david">@David</a>&nbsp;<a href="https://community.hackernoon.com/u/dane">@Dane</a>&nbsp;I know that HN in the past has said one of the advantages to HN 2.0 will be the ability to publish without the hassle of ads… and a DPoS-driven network is one way to ensure that HN will never have to sustain itself by running ads. If the team creates wealth through inflation and the community drives the value of that currency upwards (when really the token came from almost nowhere and represents no legal obligation) it’s basically free money… for everyone&nbsp;&nbsp;&#8211; while empowering those with faith and trust in the new platform to exert more influence by buying more and VESTing more.</p>



<p>It opens a whole lot of other doors, too. How do we add ‘real value’ to that coin? What sorts of services or products can we sell as a group or as the team that aligns the value of the coin to something? Can we create a distributed network of writers that are vouched by community consensus via a new kind of Blockchain reputation system that doesn’t yet exist in Blockchain content networks (aside from their exponential ‘rating’ applied to accounts which can be fabricated if you buy enough attention for your posts), and then pitch this new marketplace of content creators at brands and agencies for exposure and so everyone can win &#8211; while having them pay in the currency, which drives value? Swag stores? Can we set it up so that content creators on the network can hustle out communications to their subscriber list to these brands and agencies? What sort of services can we come up with that are ‘out of the box’ and apply to the hacker community?</p>



<p>I agree wholeheartedly the incentives need to be aligned. I think a good step in the right direction would be to move rewards from liquid to VESTed amounts, which means that those who are looking for a ‘quick buck’ will be less likely to spam up the ecosystem.</p>



<p>I really shouldn’t have said ‘free money,’ and you’re right that it’d have a huge impact on the project and the value of the coin could potentially devour what we’re trying to achieve &#8211; ‘Sure, the upside of a token is very high…but the downside is also very low.’ this is absolutely true!<br></p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Skip the SSL w/ Serverless Telegram Bot via Now.js</title>
		<link>/2019/11/24/skip-the-ssl-w-serverless-telegram-bot-via-now-js/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=109</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[See this article in it&#8217;s original form on dunncreativess.github.io! Try this bot on Telegram! https://t.me/JareBotBot! Sponsor my opensource efforts on]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/24/skip-the-ssl-w-serverless-telegram-bot-via-now-js/">See this article in it&#8217;s original form on dunncreativess.github.io!</a></p>



<p>Try this bot on Telegram! <a href="https://t.me/JareBotBot">https://t.me/JareBotBot</a>!</p>



<p><a href="https://github.com/sponsors/dunncreativess">Sponsor my opensource efforts on GitHub</a>!</p>



<p>Note: these directions come without much conversation, let the hacking begin!</p>



<p>Set up a Bot with @BotFather<br> </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-34.png" alt="" class="wp-image-110" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-34.png 641w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-34-289x300.png 289w" sizes="(max-width: 641px) 100vw, 641px" /></figure>



<p>Create a package.json</p>



<p><code>{<br>   "name": "tg-bot-now",<br>   "version": "0.2.0",<br>   "description": "A sample Telegram bot via now.js",<br>   "main": "app.js",<br>   "scripts": {<br>     "start": "node app.js"<br>   },<br>   "dependencies": {<br>     "axios": "<em>",     "body-parser": "</em>",<br>     "express": "*",<br>     "request": "^2.88.0",<br>     "requests": "^0.3.0"<br>   },<br>   "license": "MIT"<br> }</code></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-35.png" alt="" class="wp-image-111" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-35.png 827w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-35-300x150.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-35-768x384.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 827px) 100vw, 827px" /></figure>



<p>Create a now.json</p>



<p><code>{<br>   "version": 2,<br>   "builds": [<br>     { "src": "app.js", "use": "@now/node-server" }<br>   ],<br>   "routes": [<br>     { "src": "/(.*)", "dest": "app.js" }<br>   ]<br> }</code></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-36.png" alt="" class="wp-image-112" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-36.png 606w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-36-300x139.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 606px) 100vw, 606px" /></figure>



<p>Create an app.js</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>var express = require("express");
 var app = express();
 var request = require('request');
 var bodyParser = require("body-parser");
 const axios = require("axios");
 app.use(bodyParser.json());
 app.use(
     bodyParser.urlencoded({
         extended: true
     })
 );
 console.log("run"); 
function sendMessage(url, message, reply, res) {
axios.post(url, {
    chat_id: message.chat.id,
    text: reply
}).then(response => {
    console.log("Message posted");
    res.end("ok");
}).catch(error => {
    console.log(error);
});
}
 app.get('/', function(req, res) {
     res.send('hello');
 })
 var bots = &#91;"http://patbot1.duckdns.org/update", "http://coindexbot.duckdns.org:8080/update"]
 app.post("/startbot", function(req, res) {
     console.log("startbot");
     const {
         message
     } = req.body;
     let reply = "Welcome to Jare's bot bot";
     if (message.text != undefined) {
         if (message.text.toLowerCase().indexOf("statusupdate") != -1) {
             reply = ""
             for (var b in bots) {
 r = request.get(bots&#91;b], function(e, r, d) {

                j = JSON.parse(d)
                start = j.btc&#91;0]&#91;0]
                btc = j.btc&#91;j.btc.length - 1]&#91;1]
                end = j.btc&#91;j.btc.length - 1]&#91;0]
                diff = end - start
                var s = diff / 1000
                var m = s / 60
                var h = m / 60
                var d = h / 24
                var y = d / 365
                var apr = (j.btc&#91;j.btc.length - 1]&#91;1] - j.btc&#91;0]&#91;1]) / y
                reply += r.request.uri.href.substring(0, r.request.uri.href.length - 7) + '\n'
                reply += "Start: " + new Date(start) + '\n'
                reply += "Now: " + new Date(end) + "\n"
                reply += "BTC Notional traded recent memory: " + j.qty + "\n"
                reply += "Current position: " + j.pos + "\n"
                reply += "BTC % Delta: " + btc.toPrecision(4) + '%\n'
                reply += "BTC % ROI / day projected: " + (apr / 365).toPrecision(4) + '%\n'
                reply += "BTC % APR projected: " + (apr).toPrecision(4) + '%\n\n'
            })
        }
        setTimeout(function() {
            sendMessage(telegram_url, message, reply, res);
        }, 2000);
    } else {
        res.end("ok");
    }
}
});
 let telegram_url = "https://api.telegram.org/bot" + process.env.key + "/sendMessage";
 app.listen(8000, () => console.log("Telegram bot is listening on port 8000!"));</code></pre>



<p>Note: it&#8217;s important to send a res.end in every case, or else your bot will get hung up on old messages it couldn&#8217;t process and no res.end was sent &#8211; putting it in a forever loop of never sending a response!</p>



<p>set your env key</p>



<p><code>export key="whateverbotfathergaveyou"</code></p>



<p>npm i</p>



<p><code>npm i</code></p>



<p>install now</p>



<p><code>npm i -g now</code></p>



<p>run now</p>



<p><code>now</code></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-37.png" alt="" class="wp-image-113" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-37.png 902w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-37-300x58.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-37-768x148.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 902px) 100vw, 902px" /></figure>



<p>Register your POST callback wtih Telegram&#8217;s grandmasters</p>



<p><code>curl -F "url=https://URL_FROM_NOW/startbot" https://api.telegram.org/botYOUR_TELEGRAM_API_TOKEN/setWebhook</code></p>



<p>Congrats!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-38.png" alt="" class="wp-image-114" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-38.png 655w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-38-300x298.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-38-150x150.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 655px) 100vw, 655px" /></figure>



<p><a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">Join Us on Telegram</a></p>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization – where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;!!</em></p>



<p>(<strong>Disclaimer</strong>:&nbsp;<em>The Author is the Chief Liquidity Officer at Coindex</em>)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Risk-Free Futures Market Making by Hedging Long Straddle Options</title>
		<link>/2019/11/22/risk-free-futures-market-making-by-hedging-long-straddle-options/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 08:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coindex]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=100</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[See This Article in It&#8217;s Original Form on dunncreativess.github.io! Want to See And Play With The Code? Here it Is]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="http://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/22/risk-free-futures-market-making-by-hedging-long-straddle-options/">See This Article in It&#8217;s Original Form on dunncreativess.github.io!</a></p>



<p><a href="https://github.com/DunnCreativeSS/CryptoFuturesHedgingWithBlackScholesOptions">Want to See And Play With The Code? Here it Is On Github! </a></p>



<p><a href="https://github.com/sponsors/dunncreativess">Sponsor Me On Github!</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-30-1024x130.png" alt="" class="wp-image-101" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-30-1024x130.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-30-300x38.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-30-768x97.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-30.png 1255w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>In the quantitative finance world, there are some holy grails: you can decrease the risk of an exposed position generally by doing something in the opposite direction.</p>



<p>In the simplest form, we can both long and short in two opposite positions on exchanges that use the long-short model like OkEx. In doing so, a price movement up or down will have the exact same effect on your position &#8211; where you&#8217;re losing fees and only fees.</p>



<p>In reality, that&#8217;s no good because we don&#8217;t want to be losing on every trade <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/1f642.png" alt="🙂" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>



<p>What I&#8217;ve decided to try my hand at is something called a &#8216;long straddle.&#8217; This was mentioned during my interview with Coindex Labs a long time ago &#8211; but basically, if you buy a put option and buy a call option &#8216;out of the money&#8217; it&#8217;s relatively cheap &#8211; if the price doesn&#8217;t move at all, they both expire worthless. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-31.png" alt="" class="wp-image-102" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-31.png 741w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-31-300x178.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 741px) 100vw, 741px" /></figure>



<p>But: if the price increases OR decreases a significant amount, one of those options expires in the money.. meaning it gianed value from potentially nothing into potentially something!</p>



<p>What this means is that, while the market maker is performing within specifications and earning money from low price volatility and volumes on the bid/ask, these options can expire worthless and our income from market making pays for the expired options &#8211; and then more!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32-1024x161.png" alt="" class="wp-image-103" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32-1024x161.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32-300x47.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32-768x121.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32-1536x241.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32.png 1649w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>If the market moves too much in one direction, we&#8217;re risking liquidating our funds if we hold market making positions that go sour.</p>



<p>If this happens &#8211; one of our long straddle options expires &#8216;in the money&#8217; enough for us to cover our losses. What this means is risk-free trading &#8211; so long as the assumption holds true that the market making earns more than the cost of the options.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-33-1024x108.png" alt="" class="wp-image-104" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-33-1024x108.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-33-300x32.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-33-768x81.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-33.png 1247w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>In my code, we loop through all the expiries and all the strikes for all the options, and then find the one whose ratio of cost vs. profits for a 15% movement in price (which is 100% liquidated at 6.66x leverage) yields the minimum threshold we need to cover $15 000 in exposed futures ($99 900 notional). In our example output, the Dec 6 options straddle for $6250 put and $9750 call would cost a total of 0.017 BTC for both the long put and long call, and each would earn $342 profit if the underlying price moved 15% and all else remained the same. This means that spending 0.54 BTC would completely cover the risk of liquidating 2 BTC exposed at 6.66x leverage &#8211; at least until implied volatilities change significantly or time value declines as we approach expiry! When these situations occur, the hedging bot would just create new orders in real-time to hedge the risk. Hooah!</p>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization – where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;!!</em></p>



<p>(<strong>Disclaimer</strong>:&nbsp;<em>The Author is the Chief Liquidity Officer at Coindex</em>) </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Verdict is In: I&#8217;ve Got a Vested Stake of a Hedgefund! Best News? You Can Be, Too!</title>
		<link>/2019/11/21/the-verdict-is-in-ive-got-a-vested-stake-of-a-hedgefund-best-news-you-can-be-too/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 20:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coindex]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=95</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View This Article in it&#8217;s Original Form on dunncreativess.github.io! Today Coindex Lab&#8217;s CEO had a sitdown with a capital markets]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/21/the-verdict-is-in-ive-got-a-vested-stake-of-a-hedgefund-best-news-you-can-be-too/">View This Article in it&#8217;s Original Form on dunncreativess.github.io!</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://scontent.fyhz1-1.fna.fbcdn.net/v/t1.15752-9/76702405_2533273790105081_4583222162055233536_n.png?_nc_cat=108&amp;_nc_ohc=4Vbyg5W14HwAQkZ8wLiECu10yKgvGxixDMyWU4xvTgW1tmhU24esQj0Cg&amp;_nc_ht=scontent.fyhz1-1.fna&amp;oh=418a76a2031e74a257d7ae938573091e&amp;oe=5E405713" alt=""/><figcaption><br></figcaption></figure>



<p>Today Coindex Lab&#8217;s CEO had a sitdown with a capital markets guy and then later Two Sigma Ventures &#8211; with the goal of making Coindex a fighting force in quantitative finance.</p>



<p>The good news? Capital markets guy wanted us to start a hedgefund. A random guy from the other coast approached the conversation out of nowhere asking to be connected.</p>



<p>Later, the conversation with TSV yielded &#8216;Good news and bad news:&#8217;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-28.png" alt="" class="wp-image-96" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-28.png 1011w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-28-300x229.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-28-768x587.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1011px) 100vw, 1011px" /></figure>



<p>So we have two &#8211; maybe three! &#8211; pledges for funds when we figure out the legalize of doing so.</p>



<p>The good news for me is that I get both equity share and a cut of the vig (gangster term for the take).</p>



<p>The good news for my readers is that we have the opportunity to get capital into Coindex at ground floor, and start earning on crypto and traditional markets with our patented edge over any given set of market conditions.</p>



<p>You might ask yourself, then ask me, &#8216;but I&#8217;m not a high net worth individual &#8211; how can I contribute to a hedgefund?&#8217;</p>



<p>Well, in keeping with crypto tradition&#8230;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-29.png" alt="" class="wp-image-97" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-29.png 938w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-29-300x137.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-29-768x350.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 938px) 100vw, 938px" /></figure>



<p>We very well might crowdfund in an STO!</p>



<p>While this is still a gleam in the back of my eye and ultimately a rumor &#8211; what this means is that you &#8211; your friends, coworkers, acquaintances, grandma &#8211; can capitalize on <strong><a href="https://hackernoon.com/coindex-labs-novel-search-applied-via-evolutionary-ai-creating-a-money-making-machine-n62j2gei">our value proposition</a></strong>, and learn from my years of experience <a href="https://hackernoon.com/what-ive-learned-from-years-of-arbitrage-and-market-making-975w38rs"><strong>making markets and doing arbitrage trading</strong></a> and <strong><a href="https://hackernoon.com/porting-a-bot-to-binance-futures-market-making-competition-6v6a31qh">derive alphas from our bots</a></strong>!</p>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization – where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p>R<em>emember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em> !!</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Complaint About BitMex&#8217;s WebSocket API, and Update On Profitable Market Makers</title>
		<link>/2019/11/20/complaint-about-bitmexs-websocket-api-and-update-on-profitable-market-makers/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coindex]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=86</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[See this article in it&#8217;s original form, on dunncreativess.github.io! BitMex Taking Away From Their API In BitMex&#8217;s official nodejs websocket]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/20/complaint-about-bitmexs-websocket-api-and-update-on-profitable-market-makers/">See this article in it&#8217;s original form, on dunncreativess.github.io</a>!</p>



<h2>BitMex Taking Away From Their API</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-23-1024x278.png" alt="" class="wp-image-87" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-23-1024x278.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-23-300x81.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-23-768x209.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-23.png 1443w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>In BitMex&#8217;s official nodejs websocket api connector README.md, they mention &#8216;order creation&#8217; via authenticated websocket.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-24.png" alt="" class="wp-image-88" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-24.png 981w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-24-300x111.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-24-768x283.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 981px) 100vw, 981px" /></figure>



<p>Lo and behold, their web hosted websocket docs removed that functionality.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-25-1024x808.png" alt="" class="wp-image-89" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-25-1024x808.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-25-300x237.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-25-768x606.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-25.png 1076w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Common knowledge says their sample market maker they have on GitHub was set up to do websocket orders, but lo! behold! Their market maker has been updated to do all POST-style commands via REST.</p>



<p>:'(</p>



<p>The result is that our Market Making bot template with Coindex Labs hits rate limits incredibly fast when creating or editing orders, and when we enable our rate limiter we see loop times approaching 1min over 4 instruments (BTC perp, ETH perp, BTC futures) and 3 max orders for bid/ask each. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-26.png" alt="" class="wp-image-90" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-26.png 861w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-26-300x202.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-26-768x517.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-26-120x80.png 120w" sizes="(max-width: 861px) 100vw, 861px" /></figure>



<p>Woe is me!</p>



<p>With high-frequency trading one of the key aspects is &#8216;high frequency,&#8217; (no.. no joke!)</p>



<p>The bot, however, is showing net net positive deltas:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-27-1024x387.png" alt="" class="wp-image-91" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-27-1024x387.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-27-300x113.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-27-768x290.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-27.png 1386w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>This brings us to our next section: </p>



<h2>Profitable Market Making Bots!</h2>



<p>Our deribit testnet bot is up nearly 500% on equity, while livenet broke it&#8217;s 10% gains and sits happily around 15%.. in less than a week!</p>



<p>Binance Futures Market Maker will be in play in the coming weeks.. but their 0% fees after a once-a-day rebate might kill the strategy. Woe!</p>



<p>BitMex has much, much more taker volume on their high-volume instruments.. so gains should be more quick to realize! Time will tell!</p>



<h2>Look! A plug!</h2>



<p>Some of these market makers could easily be made available for sale, while there are two READ: two whole bots coming available for sale by people who&#8217;ve hired me in Telegram.</p>



<p><a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">Join Us On Telegram for Updates</a>!</p>



<h2>Look! Another plug!</h2>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization – where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em> !!</em></p>



<h2>Make Markets Across Markets!</h2>



<p>Market making is an art. Like pure arbitrage, the math behind making markets in high- or low-frequency trading makes it very unlikely to lose big &#8211; while the small, incremental gains over time mean that you&#8217;ll receive predictable and measurable gains.</p>



<p>This is made possible, for the most part, by having an edge over a market or a combination of markets &#8211; like market maker rebates, or reduced fees. When your trades have an advantage over the average trader or algorithm, you&#8217;ve got a sure-bet to win <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/1f642.png" alt="🙂" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>



<p>In lamen&#8217;s terms we automate both sides of the bid/ask spread, until such time as we&#8217;re too far exposed in one side of the equation and then we wait to settle those positions. The % amounts of balance we&#8217;re exposed the trigger this safety behavior are configurable in these bots &#8211; all of the input variables are!</p>



<p>And while we&#8217;ve seen ~10% net ROI in less than a week and $hundreds thousands notional ETH and $millions notional BTC traded on one exchange, we&#8217;d like to get people churning deltas, alphas and notionals with subscriptions!</p>



<p>The exchanges we&#8217;re looking to support at first are those with market making fee rebates or a fee structure that&#8217;s condusive to a better trading experience &#8211; ie. Okex has a tiered fee structure that decreases with volume, which is superior to Binance&#8217;s fee tiers that decrease with volume but also require holding illiquid BNB.</p>



<p><a href="https://hackernoon.com/porting-a-bot-to-binance-futures-market-making-competition-6v6a31qh">https://hackernoon.com/porting-a-bot-to-binance-futures-market-making-competition-6v6a31qh</a></p>



<p><a href="https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/20/complaint-about-bitmexs-websocket-api-and-update-on-profitable-market-makers/">https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/20/complaint-about-bitmexs-websocket-api-and-update-on-profitable-market-makers/</a></p>



<p><a href="https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/20/complaint-about-bitmexs-websocket-api-and-update-on-profitable-market-makers/">https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/20/complaint-about-bitmexs-websocket-api-and-update-on-profitable-market-makers/</a></p>



<p>——</p>



<p>To sign up:</p>



<p>Fill out this Google Form:  <a href="https://forms.gle/WVF2SMomanKwLupY9"><strong>https://forms.gle/WVF2SMomanKwLupY9</strong></a> </p>



<p>——</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
