<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Brave &#8211; jare.cloud</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/brave/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Jare&#039;s Cloud</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:33:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-CA</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.3.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>A Non-Technical Intro to How Brave Browser Protects You, Your Data, and Your Privacy!</title>
		<link>/2020/01/23/a-non-technical-intro-to-how-brave-browser-protects-you-your-data-and-your-privacy/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brave]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=433</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this post in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud! Ready to make the change, to become a more private and]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-60.png" alt="" class="wp-image-434" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-60.png 778w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-60-300x168.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-60-768x429.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 778px) 100vw, 778px" /></figure>



<p><a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/23/a-non-technical-intro-to-how-brave-browser-protects-you-your-data-and-your-privacy/">View this post in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<p>Ready to make the change, to become a more private and safe person on the entangled corners of the internet? <a href="https://brave.com/jar444">Download the Brave browser now</a>!</p>



<p>Does anyone else get horrified when the manipulation by the richest 1% is more obvious than not? An ad that implies your family will happily sit around a table and be cordial if you buy the right product for thanksgiving dinner? There&#8217;s literally rooms of people comparing the most effective ways to prey on your insecurities, win your trust and position things at you. Your worst enemies are indeed the products and services you recommend to your friends.</p>



<p>Are you new to Brave and the BAT ecosystem? Did you know you can earn &#8211; up to $100s US Dollars a month &#8211; using the Brave browser instead of your other alternatives? <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/21/the-insane-earning-potential-of-the-brave-browser-in-bat-and-how-to-turn-it-into-a-business/">Learn how much Brave can generate for you by browsing ads that don&#8217;t abuse your privacy or personally identifiable information</a>!</p>



<p>The obvious methods of influence and manipulation aside, it&#8217;s important to consider the less noticeable ways that an internet marketing company &#8211; like GOOGL, FB &#8211; track you, consume and potentially sell your data. There&#8217;s not only the giants to worry about, but countless smaller and more boutique agencies or government entities whose aims vary &#8211; both in their ends and in their means.</p>



<p>When you visit a website or a mobile app, they usually use some form of cookie or other internet trickery to track you beyond your stay on that site. These internet trackers will follow your browsing history, and your habits to assess new and better ways to target ads at you &#8211; to increase their effectiveness when someone tries to sell you something, increasing their overall Return On Investment for the advertiser. Should some companies see you browsing certain content, they&#8217;ll employ a strategy known as consumer re targeting to show you their ads again &#8211; more frequently &#8211; on other locations, like on your Facebook news feed. They&#8217;ve found you to be previously interested to some (measurable&#8230;) degree, and it&#8217;s far cheaper to acquire or keep you as a customer now than the average internet population.</p>



<p>The Brave browser automagically blocks all of these trackers around the internet. Now, as you&#8217;re browsing on your desktop or mobile, big marketing and small marketing companies can no longer exploit you for your personal data and habits. What&#8217;s more is that the more nefarious of these actors will actively sell or give away your information to the highest bidder (and all the other bidders), meaning you get all those spam and other marketing emails we&#8217;re used to receiving from people we never subscribed to when we gave our info to a site, platform or app &#8211; even when we&#8217;re trying to do the world some good and donate to a charitable cause, for instance.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-61.png" alt="" class="wp-image-436" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-61.png 1005w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-61-300x194.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-61-768x497.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-61-850x550.png 850w" sizes="(max-width: 1005px) 100vw, 1005px" /></figure>



<p>What&#8217;s more is that the Brave browser &#8211; by default &#8211; blocks all third-party ads around the internet. We&#8217;ve all witnessed them &#8211; when a site or platform shows you an ad from an online marketing strategy that isn&#8217;t from that same, original party, and redirects you off-site when you click the ad. What&#8217;s &#8216;bad&#8217; here isn&#8217;t necessarily the ad itself &#8211; after all, money makes the world go round &#8211; but it&#8217;s the way in which the ads and the clicks track your data and your personally identifiable info. For instance, when you click an ad off of Facebook (or Twitter, etc&#8230;) they&#8217;ll take on a variable to your request. This variable identifies you as an individual clicker on the internet, for these social giants to further use and abuse you and your data &#8211; selling to you better, more effectively, and with more of a winrate. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-62.png" alt="" class="wp-image-438" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-62.png 977w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-62-300x47.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-62-768x121.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 977px) 100vw, 977px" /></figure>



<p><a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/">Read the details of the Brave browser</a> and how they&#8217;re restructuring the rewards ecosystem of the internet into a Better Web &#8211; in my first-hand initial experience!</p>



<p>All in all, when marketing techniques are obvious they&#8217;re easier to ignore or approach reasonably. When these strategies are subliminal and behind-the-scenes, they&#8217;re much more easily affecting you and those close to you. The answer is to upgrade your browsing experience.. now!</p>



<p>Want to learn about new articles in tech and being a madman? Subscribe to my mailing list here: <a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL">http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</a>  </p>



<p> <br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Insane Earning Potential of the Brave Browser in BAT, and How to Turn it Into a Business</title>
		<link>/2020/01/21/the-insane-earning-potential-of-the-brave-browser-in-bat-and-how-to-turn-it-into-a-business/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 20:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brave]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=353</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[New to BAT and Brave? Here&#8217;s an article I wrote describing the Brave ecosystem&#8217;s value proposition &#8211; how you can]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-embed-reddit wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-reddit"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
    <blockquote class="reddit-card" >      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/er28xp/i_havent_sent_any_bat_but_theres_a_disconnect/?ref_source=embed&amp;ref=share">I haven&#8217;t sent any BAT, but there&#8217;s a disconnect from what&#8217;s in my wallet and what I&#8217;ve earned. Where do I find my missing BAT?</a> from      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/">BATProject</a>    </blockquote>    <script async src="https://embed.redditmedia.com/widgets/platform.js" charset="UTF-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-354" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1.jpg 378w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-300x259.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 378px) 100vw, 378px" /></figure>



<p>New to BAT and Brave? Here&#8217;s an article I wrote describing the Brave ecosystem&#8217;s value proposition &#8211; <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/">how you can earn money by browsing with a safer, more private browser</a>!</p>



<p>As highlighted in the above article, some users in the US are earning as much as $107 USD / month / browser for their BAT-enabled Brave browser. </p>



<p>This led me to DuckDuckGo some prices for low-tier Chromebooks and Android devices:</p>



<p> <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/er653q/has_anyone_thought_about_brave_hardware/">https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/er653q/has_anyone_thought_about_brave_hardware/</a>  </p>



<h1>Has anyone thought about Brave hardware?</h1>



<p>I think a Chromebook series running Brave&#8217;s Chromium wouldn&#8217;t be too difficult to create &#8211; legalities aside, all you need to do is enable dev mode and replace the browser, or boot it into a Linux crouton build with Brave as the default browser in a Linux build&#8230; with DDG as default search, to boot&#8230; if you figure in Brave Rewards over a year (or 5yr) the price of a given chromebook line becomes almost negligible, or 0.</p>



<p>Wouldn&#8217;t businesses die over the opportunity for 0-cost or revenue-generating hardware?<strong> </strong></p>



<p>$155.99 CAD Chromebooks galore:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.shopbot.ca/m/portable-devices-laptops?q=chromebook&amp;sort=price" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank">https://www.shopbot.ca/m/portable-devices-laptops?q=chromebook&amp;sort=price</a></p>



<p>My 3-day BAT earnings: 0.24 USD, 0.314 CAD</p>



<p>1-day average: 0.1046 CAD<br>365 days/yr: $38.21<br>Break-even: 4.08 yr</p>



<p>&#8230;. that&#8217;s infinite money to these people that underwrite machines&#8230;</p>



<p>The community had some thoughts about a link between Eich and KaiOS, and even linked to a method for <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/unixporn/comments/eqkx5g/lxde_summer_is_coming_d/">removing Chrome from Chromebooks</a>.</p>



<p>What I think this allows the tech-savvy entrepreneur to do is a few things:</p>



<ol><li>You can buy a line of Chromebooks at a discount price<br>For as cheap as $156, and even cheaper in bulk, Chromebooks are the most interesting subject for this idea as all of their activity happens within the browser inside the device. There are no desktop apps.</li><li>Set their browser to use Brave Chromium<br>This is fairly technical, but someone can replace the browser on Chromebook with Brave-flavored Chromium.</li><li>Resell these laptops to any person that uses the internet<br>The logic is in the money&#8230;</li><li>Along with their new, lightweight and cost-effective machine is the Brave Browser<br>It&#8217;s faster, more private, and more secure!</li><li>Which will earn them BAT for viewing ads as Brave Rewards<br>Within the first day, the investment will start paying itself off&#8230;.</li><li>And so, over time, their investment in the hardware goes down<br>Each month there&#8217;s a new Brave Rewards payment that &#8211; if you apply it to the cost of acquisition &#8211; lowers the barrier to entry for computing!</li><li>If the case is true of certain geos earning >$100 per month in BAT, then the ROI for your new machine is &lt;2 months<br>If I told you you could have a new computer every 2 months, wouldn&#8217;t you be interested? Wouldn&#8217;t you become a return customer??</li><li>In the case of larger organizations that require many dozens, hundreds of machines, they can get a loan for a working web browsing device (or even larger, heftier Windows-based machines) and after a few months start earning income on top of the cost of the machine<br>This is where the big money is. If an organization can acquire net-free pr net-earning hardware in their regular line of business, that would have otherwise been a cost, wouldn&#8217;t they be inclined to?</li><li>This allows a huge advancement in the way people look at equipment financing<br>Net-free or net-revenue generating equipment = $$$.</li><li>Which, in turn, helps the adoption of BAT and Brave<br>More users, more ads, more creators and publishers!</li></ol>



<p>The real questions are how do we create a version of Brave that allows a small- medium-sized organization limit the use of the Chromium browser, ie. block certain sites &#8211; or those other than a whitelist? I&#8217;m sure they can achieve this effect on the network level, though! Also, how do we create institutional-level Brave rewards accounts, so that the individual user on the individual browser isn&#8217;t able to redeem or move around Brave tokens &#8211; rather, they&#8217;re sent to one larger chest?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Some Recent Reddit Posts of Mine: Microtipping, the Future of Social Rewards, Driving Crypto Adoption, and Code for a 1st Party Ad Rotator</title>
		<link>/2020/01/21/some-recent-reddit-posts-of-mine-microtipping-the-future-of-social-rewards-driving-crypto-adoption-and-code-for-a-1st-party-ad-rotator/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 19:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brave]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=350</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Microtipping: Future of Social Rewards? With a minimum BAT tip of 1 BAT, there&#8217;s been some discussion around the interwebs]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-embed-reddit wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-reddit"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
    <blockquote class="reddit-card" >      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/eryy2e/microtipping_future_of_social_rewards/?ref_source=embed&amp;ref=share">Microtipping: Future of Social Rewards?</a> from      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/">BATProject</a>    </blockquote>    <script async src="https://embed.redditmedia.com/widgets/platform.js" charset="UTF-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<h1>Microtipping: Future of Social Rewards?</h1>



<p>With a minimum BAT tip of 1 BAT, there&#8217;s been some discussion around the interwebs of instituting a custom # BAT tip.</p>



<p>This would allow, as one user mentioned, the ability to microtip a fraction of a BAT at the same time they save a tweet for later &#8211; which would benefit everyone. Whereas, at present, a whole BAT might not be sustainable for each time I&#8217;d want to share some love &#8211; a fraction of a BAT would.</p>



<p>With Uphold as the present custodial license for holding and transferring BAT and BAT rewards around the Brave ecosystem, does this work super easily &#8211; comparing it to microtipping BAT on the Ether blockchain? Is Uphold off-chain, allowing any number of smaller transactions? Would future custodial solutions that aren&#8217;t requiring KYC allowing us to also microtip in this fashion?</p>



<p>Microtipping (along with the ease of use of the Tip function on social sites that Brave allows) would restructure the way people use (and think about) social interaction online.</p>



<p>+1</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-reddit wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-reddit"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
    <blockquote class="reddit-card" >      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/erx4j4/example_of_driving_bat_and_crypto_adoption_thru/?ref_source=embed&amp;ref=share">Example of Driving BAT and Crypto Adoption thru Responding to LinkedIn Promotion</a> from      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/">BATProject</a>    </blockquote>    <script async src="https://embed.redditmedia.com/widgets/platform.js" charset="UTF-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<h1>Example of Driving BAT and Crypto Adoption thru Responding to LinkedIn Promotion (since removed by mods)</h1>



<p>Preface: Lisa was an outstanding connection request on LinkedIn I confirmed maybe 24 hrs ago. She has 10 mutual connections, and 500+ total.</p>



<ul><li>Hi, I am Lisa, Web Development Manager and I work with experienced IT professionals who are into: * Create a New Website * Redesign a website? * Website Design and Development * Update Your Existing Website * E-Commerce Solutions If you are interested, then I can send you our Price list, company information and an affordable quotation with the best offer. Sincerely, Lisa</li><li><strong>TODAY</strong>&nbsp;1:33 AM</li><li>We are really looking forward to receiving your answer so that we can get to any final conclusion Best Lisa<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/1f4f7.png" alt="📷" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></li><li>Jarett Dunn 12:30 PM</li><li>Hey, no thanks!</li><li><strong>Jarett Dunn</strong>&nbsp;12:34 PM</li><li>To drive revenues, you should let your website proprietors know above Brave browser and BAT:&nbsp;<a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank"><strong>https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter</strong></a>/ Since verifying myself as a Brave publisher a/o 4 days ago I&#8217;ve earned ~11 BAT ($2.20 USD) in donations to my different platforms. That might not seem like much, but for someone with a larger audience or following it can serve as an additional revenue stream. This is compared to my&nbsp;<a href="http://medium.com/" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank"><strong>Medium.com</strong></a>&nbsp;earnings for the last ~12 days, at $1.80 USD.&nbsp; As a Brave affiliate you can also earn up to $7.50 USD for browser installations that remain installed after 30 days. Since putting up that Brave article that I linked you to, I have 7 downloads and 4 installs &#8211; this could yield up to $30 USD in affiliate income, over 4 days of referrals so far.</li></ul>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-reddit wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-reddit"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<div class="reddit-embed" data-embed-media="www.redditmedia.com" data-embed-parent="false" data-embed-live="false" data-embed-uuid="ea01df20-3c87-11ea-892c-0e5220be9fd7" data-embed-created="2020-01-21T19:55:03.246117+00:00"><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/ers2v6/interesting_data_about_medium_writer_earnings_and/ff6ar36/">Comment</a> from discussion <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/ers2v6/interesting_data_about_medium_writer_earnings_and/">h3xadecimal2&#8217;s comment from discussion &quot;Interesting data about Medium, writer earnings and usage &#8211; I&#8217;m convinced BAT would be way better if we had 250MAU&quot;</a>.</div><script async src="https://www.redditstatic.com/comment-embed.js"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Comment: I agree with <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.reddit.com/u/O1O1O1O/" target="_blank">u/O1O1O1O</a> &#8211; because Brave rewards users with advertiser&#8217;s funds to then pay (or not..) their favorite content producers, then every user eventually has a BAT or a few to redistribute &#8211; and everyone wins. Brave also allows content creators/publishers of many times &#8211; theoretically any platform that includes an API where we can decide if one user&#8217;s view on a profile is for a specific other user. This discounts sites like Facebook, Minds, but is already beautifully connected on Twitter and here on Reddit. This is potentially far more views, far more publishers and far more ad spend than Medium.<br></p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-reddit wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-reddit"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
    <blockquote class="reddit-card" >      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/erapuj/1st_party_ad_rotator/?ref_source=embed&amp;ref=share">1st Party Ad Rotator</a> from      <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/">BATProject</a>    </blockquote>    <script async src="https://embed.redditmedia.com/widgets/platform.js" charset="UTF-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>In the next iteration of my 1st party ad service, I created Javascript code that randomly chooses one of two ads to display in the header of each of the pages on my blog. This Brave-friendly ad displays content about Brave or Publish0x. It also detects mobile displays and gives a smaller banner for mobile.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s genius in it&#8217;s simplicity. . . I half want to re-package this into a WordPress plugin for other Brave content creators on WP.</p>



<p>Here&#8217;s some code:</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>if (/Android|webOS|iPhone|iPad|iPod|BlackBerry|BB|PlayBook|IEMobile|Windows Phone|Kindle|Silk|Opera Mini/i.test(navigator.userAgent)) {

	var random = Math.random(1)

	if (random &lt; 0.5){

	$('#masthead').prepend('&lt;a href="&#91;https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/](https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/)">&lt;img src="&#91;https://jare.cloud/468.png](https://jare.cloud/468.png)" />&lt;/a>')


}
	else {

$('#masthead').prepend('&lt;a href="&#91;https://jare.cloud/2020/01/20/publish0x-allowing-rewards-for-content-with-their-own-funds-re-distribution-of-wealth-defined/](https://jare.cloud/2020/01/20/publish0x-allowing-rewards-for-content-with-their-own-funds-re-distribution-of-wealth-defined/)">&lt;img src="&#91;https://jare.cloud/468-2.png](https://jare.cloud/468-2.png)" />&lt;/a>')	
}

}

else {

	var random = Math.random(1)

	if (random &lt; 0.5){

	$('#masthead').prepend('&lt;a href="&#91;https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/](https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/)">&lt;img src="&#91;https://jare.cloud/728.png](https://jare.cloud/728.png)" />&lt;/a>')

}



	else {
$('#masthead').prepend('&lt;a href="&#91;https://jare.cloud/2020/01/20/publish0x-allowing-rewards-for-content-with-their-own-funds-re-distribution-of-wealth-defined/](https://jare.cloud/2020/01/20/publish0x-allowing-rewards-for-content-with-their-own-funds-re-distribution-of-wealth-defined/)">&lt;img src="&#91;https://jare.cloud/728-2.png](https://jare.cloud/728-2.png)" />&lt;/a>')
	}

}

})
</code></pre>



<p>Check it out: <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://jare.cloud/" target="_blank">https://jare.cloud/</a></p>



<p>Check out this fellow Redditor&#8217;s extension of this idea:   <a href="https://gist.github.com/thefallofbecause/26022a05836a2990d99df80b94494e34">https://gist.github.com/thefallofbecause/26022a05836a2990d99df80b94494e34</a> <br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>7 Days Creating a Twitter Growth Service</title>
		<link>/2020/01/21/7-days-creating-a-twitter-growth-service/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 17:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brave]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=234</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[See this post in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud! Interested in a way to utilize Crypto Pump n Dump tweets]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/21/7-days-creating-a-twitter-growth-service/">See this post in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<p>Interested in a way to utilize Crypto Pump n Dump tweets &#8211; for fun &amp; profit? <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/automated-crypto-trading-bot-to-buy-pump-and-dump-sentiment-signals-from-twitter/">Check out this article I wrote on making mad stacks on Twitter sentiment</a>!</p>



<h2>Day 1</h2>



<p>I had a thought: if some of my traffic comes from Twitter to Medium and my blog, wouldn&#8217;t I want to maximize this &#8211; in a hands-free fashion? I&#8217;ve done this before &#8211; some of my accounts had 5k+ followers in a few months. I had bought a Google sheets templated sheet doc with Twitter integrations, and bam it flew. I later created a Github repo for a hackathon starter fork where I put in all these juicey follow, retweet, favorite logics into a prettier UI.</p>



<p>The benefit of the hackathon starter is that I can login via oauth &#8211; meaning the app has api keys, but the user does not. We&#8217;re all used to oauth login &#8211; do you want to login using gmail/facebook/twitter? Redirect to platform, redirect to site, success!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-21.png" alt="" class="wp-image-236" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-21.png 876w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-21-300x245.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-21-768x627.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 876px) 100vw, 876px" /></figure>



<p>I resurrected my gsheet today and started the magic. I made some edits to the code: specifically we want to follow, retweet and favorite. Hooah!</p>



<p>Let&#8217;s set our benchmark&#8230;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-20-1024x303.png" alt="" class="wp-image-235" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-20-1024x303.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-20-300x89.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-20-768x227.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-20.png 1032w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2>Day 2</h2>



<p>Well, we have some initial results! Twitter app on my phone has been blowing up. Let&#8217;s analyze the results so far&#8230;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-22.png" alt="" class="wp-image-237" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-22.png 1009w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-22-300x98.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-22-768x250.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1009px) 100vw, 1009px" /></figure>



<p>We&#8217;ve gained 13 followers in 24 hours! That might not sound like much, but it&#8217;s a full 10.8% increase over where we were. Even better than that, the amount of followers vs the amount of people I&#8217;ve followed &#8211; an important metric on Twitter &#8211; has actually increased! </p>



<p>I did notice that the UI on Twitter wouldn&#8217;t let me follow people. This is dangerous, as if we try to follow too many people and get errors because our account is limited, Twitter may ban the account. We remove the follow directives, and increase retweets and likes.</p>



<h2>Day 3</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-23-1024x364.png" alt="" class="wp-image-238" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-23-1024x364.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-23-300x107.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-23-768x273.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-23.png 1048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Wow! A further 12% increase in followers! Our ratio increased again, too. That&#8217;s fantastic news&#8230; I&#8217;m greedy now, and so I&#8217;m going to increase the retweets and favorites from one per search term per hour up to 3. This should accelerate this monster&#8230; let&#8217;s wait and find out!</p>



<p>UPDATE: 3/4 the way through Day 3, let&#8217;s take a look at results. Just because I hate waiting. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-24.png" alt="" class="wp-image-239" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-24.png 977w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-24-300x119.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-24-768x306.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 977px) 100vw, 977px" /></figure>



<p>Well, that strategy appears to be working! No longer is my account limited, and also my followers increased a further 12% on top of the last 12% and 10% &#8211; an increase in rate. When we check in in another 6ish hours we&#8217;ll hopefully see that the data for the 18th reflect a massive increase.</p>



<p>What&#8217;s even better is that my follower vs followed ratio is increasing SIGNIFICANTLY. Because I&#8217;m no longer following people using the bot &#8211; although I did some manually, messing up stats &#8211; this ratio is now EXPLODING. </p>



<p>Twitter limits your ability to follow new people after you follow 5k, and if this ratio is too too deep then everyone will assume you&#8217;re digging for followers and your rate of follow backs will decrease. D&#8217;oh!</p>



<h2>Day 4</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-33-1024x761.png" alt="" class="wp-image-295" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-33-1024x761.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-33-300x223.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-33-768x571.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-33.png 1045w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption>Twitter: Free Money</figcaption></figure>



<p>Social traffic and engagements are literally free money if you monetize your visitors in any way, or put a dollar value on them.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-48-1024x249.png" alt="" class="wp-image-339" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-48-1024x249.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-48-300x73.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-48-768x187.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-48.png 1050w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Plus &#8211; we&#8217;ve seen a massive increase in both followers and the ratio! Booya!</p>



<h2>Day 5</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-49-1024x259.png" alt="" class="wp-image-340" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-49-1024x259.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-49-300x76.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-49-768x194.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-49.png 1035w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>The followers and ratio continue their upwards trend, although slowing down&#8230;</p>



<h2>Day 6</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-50-1024x285.png" alt="" class="wp-image-341" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-50-1024x285.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-50-300x84.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-50-768x214.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-50.png 1041w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Oh! I know why my followed is still trending up. My code had a hard-coded &#8216;followback&#8217; feature. Let&#8217;s turn that off!</p>



<h2>Day 7</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51-1024x680.png" alt="" class="wp-image-342" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51-1024x680.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51-300x199.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51-768x510.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51-120x80.png 120w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51.png 1035w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Looking good&#8230;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-52.png" alt="" class="wp-image-343" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-52.png 1022w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-52-300x97.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-52-768x248.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1022px) 100vw, 1022px" /></figure>



<p>We&#8217;ve now accomplished the 2nd-highest daily increase in % follower/followed ratio. Hooah!</p>



<p>That concludes our 7-day adventure into automating Twitter engagements, for fun and profit. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-53.png" alt="" class="wp-image-344" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-53.png 337w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-53-300x87.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 337px) 100vw, 337px" /></figure>



<p>We&#8217;ve seen an 85% increase &#8211; nearly double! In followers over 7 days, and 30% increase in follower/followed ratio. These are huge numbers, indicative of a healthy and growing Twitter following.</p>



<p><a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/">Learn how to monetize your new Twitter following with Brave Browser and BAT tokens</a>! Better yet? It blocks all third-party ads! AND protects your privacy!</p>



<h2>A Plug (or Two)</h2>



<p>Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<p>Want to learn about new articles in tech and being a madman? Subscribe to my mailing list here:&nbsp;<a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL">http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</a> </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Publish0x: Allowing Rewards for Content With Their Own Funds! Re-Distribution of Wealth, Defined!</title>
		<link>/2020/01/20/publish0x-allowing-rewards-for-content-with-their-own-funds-re-distribution-of-wealth-defined/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 08:19:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Brave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Publish0x]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=327</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this article in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud! Sign up for Publish0x and start rewarding your favorite content &#8211;]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p> <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/20/publish0x-allowing-rewards-for-content-with-their-own-funds-re-distribution-of-wealth-defined/">View this article in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud</a>! </p>



<p><a href="https://www.publish0x.com/?a=olejNWvejN">Sign up for Publish0x and start rewarding your favorite content</a> &#8211; without paying a cent! You also get paid!</p>



<p>As one of my first ads delivered through the Brave browser was for Publish0x, I had originally been quick to dismiss it. On later inspection &#8211; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/BATProject/comments/er28xp/i_havent_sent_any_bat_but_theres_a_disconnect/">when I figured out I could 2.5x my BAT rewards by switching my Brave Rewards from 2 ads/hr to 5</a> &#8211; I found I could earn BAT and DAI for blogging&#8230; or reading!&#8230; my favorite content on their platform.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-43.png" alt="" class="wp-image-328" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-43.png 965w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-43-300x160.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-43-768x411.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 965px) 100vw, 965px" /></figure>



<p>This, together with syndication for my blog and juicey backlinks, allowed me to quickly sign up and find that indeed &#8211; I was able to tip every few minutes and choose what % of that tip I wanted to keep for myself.</p>



<p>Win-win-win! The money comes from their big ol&#8217; community chest of possible rewards, spanning many coins.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-44-1024x259.png" alt="" class="wp-image-329" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-44-1024x259.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-44-300x76.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-44-768x195.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-44.png 1042w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-45-1024x164.png" alt="" class="wp-image-330" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-45-1024x164.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-45-300x48.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-45-768x123.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-45-1536x246.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-45.png 1567w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>In such a way, I&#8217;ve earned BAT, HYDRO and DAI already on the platform &#8211; by voting on 4 articles. Genius!</p>



<p>This is the definition of redistribution of wealth. The communist&#8217;s dream, in a capitalist application!</p>



<p>Hint: they also sport a fancy Ambassador program &#8211; allowing you, too, &#8216;Earn&nbsp;<strong>5%</strong>&nbsp;of every tip generated by your referrals using the tipper at the bottom of each article. This includes both the tip to the author and the amount claimed by your referral.&#8217;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-46-1024x414.png" alt="" class="wp-image-331" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-46-1024x414.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-46-300x121.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-46-768x310.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-46-1536x621.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-46.png 1640w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Check it out! My buddy signed up and tipped a writer.. and I earned, before I even finished this promotional post! That&#8217;s free money begetting free money. I&#8217;m sorry, but you NEED to sign up now! It&#8217;s basically a DAI/BAT/ et cetera faucet for content you&#8217;d enjoy regardless!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-47-1024x338.png" alt="" class="wp-image-335" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-47-1024x338.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-47-300x99.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-47-768x253.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-47-1536x506.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-47.png 1568w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Ready to get paid for reading whatever floats your boat? <a href="https://www.publish0x.com/?a=olejNWvejN">Sign up for Publish0x now</a>!</p>



<h2>A Plug (or Two) (or Three)</h2>



<p><a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/">Read more about how Brave rewards you to browse, while protecting your privacy online!</a></p>



<p>Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<p>Want to learn about new articles in tech and being a madman? Subscribe to my mailing list here:&nbsp;<a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL">http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</a> </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nexo Review for Crypto Loans and Bitcoin Loans and Crypto Cards: MCO Visa, TenX too</title>
		<link>/2020/01/19/nexo-review-for-crypto-loans-and-bitcoin-loans-and-crypto-cards-mco-visa-tenx-too/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brave]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=298</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this article in it’s original form on jare.cloud! Intro What if Nexo had more than $100m USD worth of]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/19/nexo-review-for-crypto-loans-and-bitcoin-loans-and-crypto-cards-mco-visa-tenx-too/">View this article in it’s original form on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<h2>Intro</h2>



<p>What if Nexo had more than $100m USD worth of YOUR assets? More than their centralized bank-backed insurance fund protects?</p>



<p>What if Nexo began speculatively investing YOUR funds into third-party protocols, putting the capital at risk &#8211; or even losing substantial amounts of it?</p>



<p>What if Nexo, Monaco (MCO) or TenX bailed with all your funds &#8211; in massive exit scams the likes of which we have indeed seen before, at Mt. Gox or QuadrigaCX?</p>



<p>What are the alternatives for collateralized loans &#8211; where can we hedge our crypto assets, using Bitcoin or Ether or other underlyings to draw tax-friendly income? </p>



<p>Read on&#8230;</p>



<h2>Centralized Off-Chain Crypto Interest on Holdings &#8211; and Collateralized Loans Against Crypto &#8211; Seems Like a Great Idea</h2>



<p>While Nexo and Nexo clones offer some great incentives to help you feel safe &amp; secure handing over your hard-earned crypto, like a $100 million insurance fund or tax-friendly income while not spending your assets &#8211; there are huge pitfalls to trusting The Man with your units of value&#8230; with YOUR money.</p>



<p>Sure, someone may be in the position where they hold 1 BTC and want to earn a % of that 1 BTC back from an organization while doing absolutely nothing. Seems risk-free, right? &#8216;Compound your crypto&#8217; is a popular sentiment on the Internet of late &#8211; I even <a href="https://twitter.com/jarettdunn">use that phrase in my twitter bio</a>. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-34.png" alt="" class="wp-image-306" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-34.png 996w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-34-300x78.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-34-768x200.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 996px) 100vw, 996px" /></figure>



<p>What does it mean, in actual effect?</p>



<p>Well, if I have 1 BTC now and that BTC earns me 8% APR &#8211; each and every year &#8211; that 8% will earn another 8% on the 8% in year 2. </p>



<p>If we&#8217;re also long BTC, or think it&#8217;ll grow at, say, 5% average per year in value, then our resulting investment would look like this:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-35-1024x303.png" alt="" class="wp-image-307" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-35-1024x303.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-35-300x89.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-35-768x227.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-35.png 1377w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>After 10 years your BTC has nearly doubled, and the value of that BTC is up 112x&#8230;.</p>



<p>That seems to be fantastic, right? And a 5% growth on BTC per year is rather.. well, conservative, right?</p>



<h2>Other Side of That Coin</h2>



<p>Say we&#8217;re even more long on a bullish BTC, and think it&#8217;ll rise in value by &#8211; say &#8211; 30% per year. Now, we can look at Nexo or other centralized bank-backed solutions to lend US Dollar against our asset. I&#8217;m risk averse to clicking on their site, but I imagine their rates are maybe 10-14% APR. So, we lend the max. amount against our BTC at around $4500 USD, and pay 14% on the loan &#8211; while our BTC appreciates 30%.</p>



<p>Here&#8217;s what that math looks like:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-36-1024x334.png" alt="" class="wp-image-308" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-36-1024x334.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-36-300x98.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-36-768x250.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-36.png 1313w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>All else remaining equal, shortly after 6 years we have ALL of our bitcoin back in appreciated value vs what we owe on our loan. </p>



<p>Let&#8217;s go even more bullish BTC &#8211; think The Halvening will grow BTC to $12k, then it&#8217;s a clear road to $20k, then moon? So do I!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-37-1024x334.png" alt="" class="wp-image-309" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-37-1024x334.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-37-300x98.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-37-768x250.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-37.png 1313w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>If BTC grows 230% in a calendar year, we effectively have a free half BTC in loaned amount in less than a year. That&#8217;s fantastic! Free money!</p>



<h2>Now, the Catch</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-38.png" alt="" class="wp-image-310" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-38.png 728w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-38-300x84.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 728px) 100vw, 728px" /></figure>



<p>I wonder if Nexo has overgrown their little insurance scheme? I wonder if too many people have trusted something too good to be true &#8211; in the hands of a select few, a legal entity, and human fallacies?</p>



<p>Even more sinister, let&#8217;s say Nexo was sitting on millions of dollars in Ether. Let&#8217;s say they thought &#8211; nay, they bet on the idea &#8211; that Ether would never ever possibly depreciate past $300. Long Live Ether, right? Now, they use a third party protocol to lend against their Ether bankroll &#8211; to the tune of millions $ USD &#8211; to boost their coffers and all their marketing campaigns to draw more people into their massive &#8216;insured&#8217; ponzi. </p>



<p>Then, as we witnessed, Eth did go down. Way. Past. $300.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-39-1024x473.png" alt="" class="wp-image-311" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-39-1024x473.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-39-300x139.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-39-768x355.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-39.png 1343w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-40-1024x627.png" alt="" class="wp-image-312" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-40-1024x627.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-40-300x184.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-40-768x470.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-40.png 1077w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-41.png" alt="" class="wp-image-313" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-41.png 916w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-41-300x216.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-41-768x552.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 916px) 100vw, 916px" /></figure>



<p>Can you think of anything more sinister&#8230; than risking people&#8217;s funds they trust your insurance to cover, then losing it? </p>



<p>Trust the banks to mess with you like this.</p>



<p>Trust custodial solutions to mess with your hard-earned cash.</p>



<h2>Monaco&#8217;s Visa Card, TenX, Populous, and the Others</h2>



<p>Nexo has another product in the pipes: a crypto-loans backed credit/debit card. When you put your crypto onto a debit/credit card, you&#8217;re actually just giving it to banks to hold onto &#8211; and with that, you&#8217;re giving them all of your personally identifiable information, as well as the right to track you and sell your data to the highest bidder (and all the other bidders with half a dollar). What this means is that you&#8217;re taking the ultimate grassroots revolution against banks and the richest 1% and giving it right back to them. This goes against everything Satoshi and all the other crypto revolutionaries had wanted with their digital cash. Do Your Own Research, and decide what&#8217;s right.</p>



<p>Moreover, existing crypto card solutions like cryptopay.me and xapo all lost their licenses for dealing with North America and loads of other places &#8211; because banks, by and large, don&#8217;t trust crypto. </p>



<p>If you need to spend your crypto look to solutions like localbitcoins.com &#8211; where you can even sell your BTC at around 1% on the dollar value to meet in person and get cold, hard cash.</p>



<h2>The Solution</h2>



<p>Never, ever trust custodial solutions! There&#8217;s such a thing as counter-party risk that&#8217;s well documented, and this is why decentralized exchanges and decentralized finance are winning with a clear advantage &#8211; employing trustless solutions where people are interacting with a tech protocol rather than an organization, person, people, or &#8211; worse yet &#8211; a bank.</p>



<p>Solutions are abound: check <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/14/top-money-making-decentralized-finance-defi-applications/">my article comparing the top 6-8 decentralized finance protocols</a>.</p>



<p>Of these, a few come to mind for compounding your crypto: like <a href="https://compound.finance/">compound.finance</a>, where you can earn interest on your cryptos while holding them in your own damned wallet, secured by your own damned keys. This completely removes the counter-party risk of earning on your crypto. Almost all the other solutions in the above article like <a href="http://nuo.network/">nuo.network</a> or <a href="http://fulcrum.trade/">fulcrum.trade</a> allow you to earn, too, sometimes at higher rates &#8211; and aggregators exist, too, like <a href="http://staked.us/?pid=fr5BC09Vgc">staked.us&#8217;s Robo Advisor for Yield</a> which allows you to passively rebalance your lent portfolio.</p>



<p>Compound also allows you to borrow against your crypto assets &#8211; all on-chain, all non-custodial. You own your own keys. You can receive a number of stablecoins for your Ether or other tokens, or even borrow against non-stable assets &#8211; the choice is yours to long or short whatever you like. </p>



<p>They currently don&#8217;t support borrowing against BTC or the BTC-backed Wrapped BTC (WBTC), but have no fear! Fulcrum.trade has a sister-site powered by the same protocol <a href="https://torque.loans/">https://torque.loans/</a>  where &#8211; at present &#8211; you can get $4800 in stablecoins for your 1 WBTC.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-42.png" alt="" class="wp-image-314" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-42.png 821w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-42-300x232.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-42-768x593.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 821px) 100vw, 821px" /></figure>



<h2>The Verdict</h2>



<p>Never, ever trust The Man with your money. That&#8217;s the point of Blockchain. Banks, governments will collapse and fail, the ATMs will stop giving you money and gas will stop being delivered to your favorite gas stations &#8211; food will stop being delivered to your supermarkets &#8211; but crypto will not fail because the protocols are run without the interference or governance of man (or woman, or other).</p>



<p>Tired of The Man earning from your browsing habits, personally identifiable information and by selling your data? Try the <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/">Brave browser, which not only protects all of your data and privacy,</a> but also axes all those damaging ads around the web &#8211; delivering you a faster, safer browsing experience!</p>



<h2>A Plug (or Two)</h2>



<p>Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness?&nbsp;<a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a></p>



<p>Want to learn about new articles in tech and being a madman? Subscribe to my mailing list here:&nbsp;<a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL">http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</a><br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Better Web: Brave Rewards Your Content! Make money monetizing Twitter!</title>
		<link>/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 04:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Github]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=213</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[What&#8217;s all the fuss about? Download the Brave browser on your computer or mobile phone and start earning now! How]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>What&#8217;s all the fuss about?  <a href="https://brave.com/jar444">Download the Brave browser on your computer or mobile</a> phone and start earning now! <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/21/the-insane-earning-potential-of-the-brave-browser-in-bat-and-how-to-turn-it-into-a-business/">How much can you earn? Try $100s USD a month</a>!</p>



<p><a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/">View this post in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<p> Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<p>Folks welcome to Web 3.0.</p>



<p>Not only does Brave pay me in $BAT for browsing the internet by serving me ads I enjoy watching based on my interests, it literally allows people to tip and automatically contribute to those Twitter users using Brave. </p>



<p>It also allows me to monetize my YouTube &#8211; I have 344 viewers watching my old ass YouTubes for 9.5hrs/month. I can now monetize some of those…</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-14-1024x410.png" alt="" class="wp-image-214" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-14-1024x410.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-14-300x120.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-14-768x308.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-14.png 1231w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Admittedly, my one true passion is finding a way to create evergreen and passive income for myself &#8211; now people viewing my YouTube videos will automagically share some of their $BAT with me. People that like me even more might opt to share more %, or even tip me one-time or repeatedly&#8230;.</p>



<p>I&#8217;ve been aware of BAT as a project and Brave as a browser for a long, long time, being a crypto enthusiast all these years. I resisted doing a tiny 5-second Google search because I assumed it was a new-fangled low-functioning browser that would disappoint. I wasn&#8217;t aware it&#8217;s literally built on chrome, can import my bookmarks and I can use all my favorite extensions!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-15-1024x518.png" alt="" class="wp-image-215" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-15-1024x518.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-15-300x152.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-15-768x389.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-15-1536x777.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-15.png 1804w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>On top of all that, it&#8217;s actively blocking unwanted ads across sites and ad networks while also keeping my private browsing information like cookie data or personally identifiable information from being transmitted from my machine.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-16-1024x682.png" alt="" class="wp-image-216" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-16-1024x682.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-16-300x200.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-16-768x512.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-16-120x80.png 120w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-16.png 1031w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>As <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2016/aug/31/personal-data-corporate-use-google-amazon">an article on theguardian quotes</a>: &#8216;Data appropriation is a form of exploitation because companies use data to create value without providing people with comparable compensation.&#8217;</p>



<p>What&#8217;s the solution? Limit the data you send! Be compensated for the data you do choose to share!</p>



<p>Within a few seconds of having the browser opened, I&#8217;d already earned a penny as they showed me an ad from BlockFi.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-17-1024x629.png" alt="" class="wp-image-217" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-17-1024x629.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-17-300x184.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-17-768x472.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-17.png 1083w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Another ad, advertising BAT&#8217;s community forums, turned out to be incredibly informative: as it turns out, the content creators signup page had more options than just Website, Twitch, YouTube. I had connected all three of these already but on the community forum I found a <a href="https://forum.batcommunity.org/t/use-twitter-to-receive-brave-rewards/5987/12">thread talking about tipping people on Twitter</a> &#8211; I thought: I must have this.</p>



<p>On further clicking I found Brave had loads more options for me to earn as a content creator! It&#8217;s probably just my desktop settings &#8211; at 175% zoom because I&#8217;m blind! </p>



<p>Also, in the interface of their Chrome-based browser, they&#8217;ve very cleverly integrated a &#8216;tip&#8217; button on Twitter tweets &#8211; right there in the UI.  </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-18-1024x663.png" alt="" class="wp-image-218" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-18-1024x663.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-18-300x194.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-18-768x497.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-18-850x550.png 850w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-18.png 1037w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>When I visit a content creator of any kind &#8211; including Github profiles, where I receive 100s more evergreen, passive views than I do on YouTube or even your reddit profile which might be (pardon the pun) more prolific than your Twitter &#8211; they&#8217;re automagically added to my pool of content creators that I&#8217;m going to automagically share some tokens with at the end of the month. I get to set totals, %s for each creator, and every other granular little detail.</p>



<p>Essentially, Brave gives the advertising revenue to the end-user who then chooses which publishers they want to reward with how much tokens &#8211; and they get to up the ante for those publishers they&#8217;re truly fans of. It&#8217;s a brilliant idea!</p>



<p><a href="https://brave.com/jar444">Download the Brave browser on your computer or mobile</a> phone here. You&#8217;ll be earning in a jiffy!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
