<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Coindex &#8211; DunnCreativeSS</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/coindex/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Get Your Git Here!</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 04:31:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-CA</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.3.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Decentralized Social Media</title>
		<link>/2019/12/30/decentralized-social-media/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 03:19:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coindex]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=155</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[**submitted to Hackernoon, submitted to GCNews.io** Incentive I’m not necessarily after $200, I’m after a voice. While published on Hackernoon]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>**submitted to Hackernoon, submitted to GCNews.io**</p>



<h2>Incentive</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-twitter wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Let&#39;s try an experiment: $200 BTC bounty for the best review of decentralized social media.<br><br>The ideal piece covers not just crypto efforts like Voice/Akasha, but allied tech like Mastodon, CRDT, Bittorrent, Git.<br><br>Reply to this tweet with your post! cc <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@cz_binance</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@VitalikButerin</a> <a href="https://t.co/hhS0TXU9fX">https://t.co/hhS0TXU9fX</a></p>&mdash; Balaji S. Srinivasan (@balajis) <a href="https://twitter.com/balajis/status/1210639705143951360?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 27, 2019</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>I’m not necessarily after $200, I’m after a voice. While <a href="https://hackernoon.com/@jare">published on Hackernoon many times</a> and having a <a href="https://github.com/dunncreativess">Github with 100+ repositories</a>, I’d thought it might be a good idea to take part in this competition and get the attention of <a href="https://twitter.com/balajis">https://twitter.com/balajis</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance">https://twitter.com/cz_binance</a> &#8211; maybe even <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin">https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin</a>.</p>



<h1>Preface: Censorship</h1>



<p>This most recent bit of news time saw YouTube censor many crypto-related voices, and a mail broadcast I received from LBRY mentioned a few (or a lot?) of them ended up there to promote their views and opinions. Moreover, we saw MetaMask removed from the Android Play Store (and also, consequently, my device), purportedly for mining crypto and more likely for offering a competing environment where people can consume the internet than the Play Store itself. This level of censorship creates a world where a few big players (aka. the ultra-rich) can dictate to us what content we can consume where, and leads the way to a dangerous version of the internet where all we can possibly consume is the ultra-rich’s agenda.<br></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1gypbqvU8CjCzicIgUaUFeVLX56b7Te7lREUwnDONBeR9DMGKZo5NmhRbJBZ4ZGP5wvN_Ze4cSy0XxFxZ0LcX5YxynExXuxQOQRXXrBQfrvJb7W-aVqSS6ybJrjbRCUkjmx16S-R" alt=""/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/4qwxvQORDVRn_oxTr_nuxml1XJZLFwyXCl8daa-l7-PRVzmaE2r4NGU9vv-AT-p6BU_CPQD7EQwsHA7XnOVhs6aWbxa9LZEeDawyXMMVqyPWFT_EvREpnsAOEt2UGl_I_WoxAPKp" alt=""/></figure>



<p>The answer is an open and vibrant decentralized community where censorship plays no part. Minds.com comes to mind, but there has to be other underlying mechanisms to preserve the rights and freedoms of people everywhere &#8211; even in a censorship-free arena, we shouldn’t be subjected to hate speech and other dark web reminiscent dark corners of the internet. This kind of content from supremacists and trolls alike would hurt the overall image and therein hurt adoption &#8211; which would kill our creation before it’s born.<br></p>



<p>SteemIt comes to mind &#8211; along with it’s various interfaces, (and in recent iterations allow an even more well-thought / which allow a) way for people to downvote ‘bad’ content. This is a great solution for the decentralized community to self-moderate it’s own content monstrosity, but by and large this creates a demand for labor that can’t easily be rewarded (cue Steem’s life-long battle trying to figure out how to balance inflationary rewards with the need to self-moderate &#8211; and their nearly Steem-killing problem with people using the reward structure to bribe rewards and over-reward themselves).<br></p>



<h1>Monetization and Reward Mechanisms</h1>



<p>At this point, it’s crucial to remind ourselves that Blockchain is not cryptocurrency. Read that again! The huge interest that the ICO craze pulled into Blockchain was equally as damaging to the image of Blockchain &#8211; if not more &#8211; than the dark web’s dependency on Bitcoin as an anonymous online currency was to the image of Bitcoin. A reward mechanism for users for a decentralized social platform is not required, but could benefit actual users &#8211; actual people &#8211; for their content and social interactions.<br></p>



<p>If there’s a reward mechanism built into a new decentralized social media, it should be one that allows users to reward their favorite users through micropayments and allows the generation of additional rewards through staking an amount of e-currency someone already has &#8211; showing a dedication to the network and allowing the network more buying pressure than selling pressure. Steem does this, but I’m guessing people would want to stake more if there were more perceived reward &#8211; ie. you could earn more from your social presence as a direct result of staking more.&nbsp;<br></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/tawIPlUa64-MNSJ2LPqEAZDmam5AF-HvZ_d_J6iFcNreeFphWd9CzwRG5AkMrSee2i2Op4R0ivoHrBSHYyu_88pT2YUmCX-oJw5io_LRWixstkez3Q74z8XVczk0mv-dE76LEFvk" alt=""/></figure>



<p>If I had a dime for each time I had this conversation &#8211; with some underemployed or unemployed, disenfranchised friend on the internet &#8211; if we had a way to monetize and reward engaging social content we could empower the unbanked worldwide.&nbsp;<br></p>



<h1>Moderation</h1>



<p>&#8212; Note this isn’t the original (or even unoriginal) purposes of this neural evolutionary AI project &#8211; I’m going out on a limb here, without consulting our AI devs on this &#8211; but I think that the given problem would be socially acceptable content, and one could train the proof of fitness to provide that goal. Why not? &#8212;</p>



<p>In projects in the past like Akasha or Mastadon, one key feature that’s perplexed developers is how to monitor and remove spam, plagiarism, hate speech, etc. In a world with increasingly smart AI, there’s no reason to put this labor onto individual users like in Steem &#8211; one could create a neural evolutionary AI that’s rewarded by achieving happier individuals through a ‘report’ mechanism on leftover content. If something’s reported, then that competing generation responsible for that post is hit with a ‘ding’ that keeps it from being the master genome in that set &#8211; and the master genome carries on to start a new generation of competing genomes to do a better job in the next set of posts that are all moderated.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The computational power required to run these competing and learning sets of problem-solving algos could be served by p2p nodes that are run by users around the world &#8211; with as little as a laptop, in another chain that rewards the users submitting to the champion net.&nbsp;</p>



<p><a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1VBJ0UoY7MjeIEX0ljPj6G35qqnSizTv-XgzCiAx04F8/edit?usp=sharing">Read more in OuroborosChain &#8211; a white paper detailing neural evolutionary AI</a>.</p>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;</em></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization – where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em> !!</em></p>



<h1>Disclaimer</h1>



<p>The author is Chief Liquidity Officer for Coindex Labs.<br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Risk-Free Futures Market Making by Hedging Long Straddle Options</title>
		<link>/2019/11/22/risk-free-futures-market-making-by-hedging-long-straddle-options/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 08:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coindex]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=100</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[See This Article in It&#8217;s Original Form on dunncreativess.github.io! Want to See And Play With The Code? Here it Is]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="http://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/22/risk-free-futures-market-making-by-hedging-long-straddle-options/">See This Article in It&#8217;s Original Form on dunncreativess.github.io!</a></p>



<p><a href="https://github.com/DunnCreativeSS/CryptoFuturesHedgingWithBlackScholesOptions">Want to See And Play With The Code? Here it Is On Github! </a></p>



<p><a href="https://github.com/sponsors/dunncreativess">Sponsor Me On Github!</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-30-1024x130.png" alt="" class="wp-image-101" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-30-1024x130.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-30-300x38.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-30-768x97.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-30.png 1255w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>In the quantitative finance world, there are some holy grails: you can decrease the risk of an exposed position generally by doing something in the opposite direction.</p>



<p>In the simplest form, we can both long and short in two opposite positions on exchanges that use the long-short model like OkEx. In doing so, a price movement up or down will have the exact same effect on your position &#8211; where you&#8217;re losing fees and only fees.</p>



<p>In reality, that&#8217;s no good because we don&#8217;t want to be losing on every trade <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/1f642.png" alt="🙂" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>



<p>What I&#8217;ve decided to try my hand at is something called a &#8216;long straddle.&#8217; This was mentioned during my interview with Coindex Labs a long time ago &#8211; but basically, if you buy a put option and buy a call option &#8216;out of the money&#8217; it&#8217;s relatively cheap &#8211; if the price doesn&#8217;t move at all, they both expire worthless. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-31.png" alt="" class="wp-image-102" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-31.png 741w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-31-300x178.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 741px) 100vw, 741px" /></figure>



<p>But: if the price increases OR decreases a significant amount, one of those options expires in the money.. meaning it gianed value from potentially nothing into potentially something!</p>



<p>What this means is that, while the market maker is performing within specifications and earning money from low price volatility and volumes on the bid/ask, these options can expire worthless and our income from market making pays for the expired options &#8211; and then more!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32-1024x161.png" alt="" class="wp-image-103" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32-1024x161.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32-300x47.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32-768x121.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32-1536x241.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32.png 1649w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>If the market moves too much in one direction, we&#8217;re risking liquidating our funds if we hold market making positions that go sour.</p>



<p>If this happens &#8211; one of our long straddle options expires &#8216;in the money&#8217; enough for us to cover our losses. What this means is risk-free trading &#8211; so long as the assumption holds true that the market making earns more than the cost of the options.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-33-1024x108.png" alt="" class="wp-image-104" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-33-1024x108.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-33-300x32.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-33-768x81.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-33.png 1247w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>In my code, we loop through all the expiries and all the strikes for all the options, and then find the one whose ratio of cost vs. profits for a 15% movement in price (which is 100% liquidated at 6.66x leverage) yields the minimum threshold we need to cover $15 000 in exposed futures ($99 900 notional). In our example output, the Dec 6 options straddle for $6250 put and $9750 call would cost a total of 0.017 BTC for both the long put and long call, and each would earn $342 profit if the underlying price moved 15% and all else remained the same. This means that spending 0.54 BTC would completely cover the risk of liquidating 2 BTC exposed at 6.66x leverage &#8211; at least until implied volatilities change significantly or time value declines as we approach expiry! When these situations occur, the hedging bot would just create new orders in real-time to hedge the risk. Hooah!</p>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization – where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;!!</em></p>



<p>(<strong>Disclaimer</strong>:&nbsp;<em>The Author is the Chief Liquidity Officer at Coindex</em>) </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Verdict is In: I&#8217;ve Got a Vested Stake of a Hedgefund! Best News? You Can Be, Too!</title>
		<link>/2019/11/21/the-verdict-is-in-ive-got-a-vested-stake-of-a-hedgefund-best-news-you-can-be-too/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 20:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coindex]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=95</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View This Article in it&#8217;s Original Form on dunncreativess.github.io! Today Coindex Lab&#8217;s CEO had a sitdown with a capital markets]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/21/the-verdict-is-in-ive-got-a-vested-stake-of-a-hedgefund-best-news-you-can-be-too/">View This Article in it&#8217;s Original Form on dunncreativess.github.io!</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://scontent.fyhz1-1.fna.fbcdn.net/v/t1.15752-9/76702405_2533273790105081_4583222162055233536_n.png?_nc_cat=108&amp;_nc_ohc=4Vbyg5W14HwAQkZ8wLiECu10yKgvGxixDMyWU4xvTgW1tmhU24esQj0Cg&amp;_nc_ht=scontent.fyhz1-1.fna&amp;oh=418a76a2031e74a257d7ae938573091e&amp;oe=5E405713" alt=""/><figcaption><br></figcaption></figure>



<p>Today Coindex Lab&#8217;s CEO had a sitdown with a capital markets guy and then later Two Sigma Ventures &#8211; with the goal of making Coindex a fighting force in quantitative finance.</p>



<p>The good news? Capital markets guy wanted us to start a hedgefund. A random guy from the other coast approached the conversation out of nowhere asking to be connected.</p>



<p>Later, the conversation with TSV yielded &#8216;Good news and bad news:&#8217;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-28.png" alt="" class="wp-image-96" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-28.png 1011w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-28-300x229.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-28-768x587.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1011px) 100vw, 1011px" /></figure>



<p>So we have two &#8211; maybe three! &#8211; pledges for funds when we figure out the legalize of doing so.</p>



<p>The good news for me is that I get both equity share and a cut of the vig (gangster term for the take).</p>



<p>The good news for my readers is that we have the opportunity to get capital into Coindex at ground floor, and start earning on crypto and traditional markets with our patented edge over any given set of market conditions.</p>



<p>You might ask yourself, then ask me, &#8216;but I&#8217;m not a high net worth individual &#8211; how can I contribute to a hedgefund?&#8217;</p>



<p>Well, in keeping with crypto tradition&#8230;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-29.png" alt="" class="wp-image-97" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-29.png 938w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-29-300x137.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-29-768x350.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 938px) 100vw, 938px" /></figure>



<p>We very well might crowdfund in an STO!</p>



<p>While this is still a gleam in the back of my eye and ultimately a rumor &#8211; what this means is that you &#8211; your friends, coworkers, acquaintances, grandma &#8211; can capitalize on <strong><a href="https://hackernoon.com/coindex-labs-novel-search-applied-via-evolutionary-ai-creating-a-money-making-machine-n62j2gei">our value proposition</a></strong>, and learn from my years of experience <a href="https://hackernoon.com/what-ive-learned-from-years-of-arbitrage-and-market-making-975w38rs"><strong>making markets and doing arbitrage trading</strong></a> and <strong><a href="https://hackernoon.com/porting-a-bot-to-binance-futures-market-making-competition-6v6a31qh">derive alphas from our bots</a></strong>!</p>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization – where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p>R<em>emember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em> !!</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Complaint About BitMex&#8217;s WebSocket API, and Update On Profitable Market Makers</title>
		<link>/2019/11/20/complaint-about-bitmexs-websocket-api-and-update-on-profitable-market-makers/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coindex]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=86</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[See this article in it&#8217;s original form, on dunncreativess.github.io! BitMex Taking Away From Their API In BitMex&#8217;s official nodejs websocket]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/20/complaint-about-bitmexs-websocket-api-and-update-on-profitable-market-makers/">See this article in it&#8217;s original form, on dunncreativess.github.io</a>!</p>



<h2>BitMex Taking Away From Their API</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-23-1024x278.png" alt="" class="wp-image-87" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-23-1024x278.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-23-300x81.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-23-768x209.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-23.png 1443w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>In BitMex&#8217;s official nodejs websocket api connector README.md, they mention &#8216;order creation&#8217; via authenticated websocket.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-24.png" alt="" class="wp-image-88" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-24.png 981w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-24-300x111.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-24-768x283.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 981px) 100vw, 981px" /></figure>



<p>Lo and behold, their web hosted websocket docs removed that functionality.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-25-1024x808.png" alt="" class="wp-image-89" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-25-1024x808.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-25-300x237.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-25-768x606.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-25.png 1076w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Common knowledge says their sample market maker they have on GitHub was set up to do websocket orders, but lo! behold! Their market maker has been updated to do all POST-style commands via REST.</p>



<p>:'(</p>



<p>The result is that our Market Making bot template with Coindex Labs hits rate limits incredibly fast when creating or editing orders, and when we enable our rate limiter we see loop times approaching 1min over 4 instruments (BTC perp, ETH perp, BTC futures) and 3 max orders for bid/ask each. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-26.png" alt="" class="wp-image-90" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-26.png 861w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-26-300x202.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-26-768x517.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-26-120x80.png 120w" sizes="(max-width: 861px) 100vw, 861px" /></figure>



<p>Woe is me!</p>



<p>With high-frequency trading one of the key aspects is &#8216;high frequency,&#8217; (no.. no joke!)</p>



<p>The bot, however, is showing net net positive deltas:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-27-1024x387.png" alt="" class="wp-image-91" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-27-1024x387.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-27-300x113.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-27-768x290.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-27.png 1386w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>This brings us to our next section: </p>



<h2>Profitable Market Making Bots!</h2>



<p>Our deribit testnet bot is up nearly 500% on equity, while livenet broke it&#8217;s 10% gains and sits happily around 15%.. in less than a week!</p>



<p>Binance Futures Market Maker will be in play in the coming weeks.. but their 0% fees after a once-a-day rebate might kill the strategy. Woe!</p>



<p>BitMex has much, much more taker volume on their high-volume instruments.. so gains should be more quick to realize! Time will tell!</p>



<h2>Look! A plug!</h2>



<p>Some of these market makers could easily be made available for sale, while there are two READ: two whole bots coming available for sale by people who&#8217;ve hired me in Telegram.</p>



<p><a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">Join Us On Telegram for Updates</a>!</p>



<h2>Look! Another plug!</h2>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization – where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em> !!</em></p>



<h2>Make Markets Across Markets!</h2>



<p>Market making is an art. Like pure arbitrage, the math behind making markets in high- or low-frequency trading makes it very unlikely to lose big &#8211; while the small, incremental gains over time mean that you&#8217;ll receive predictable and measurable gains.</p>



<p>This is made possible, for the most part, by having an edge over a market or a combination of markets &#8211; like market maker rebates, or reduced fees. When your trades have an advantage over the average trader or algorithm, you&#8217;ve got a sure-bet to win <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/1f642.png" alt="🙂" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>



<p>In lamen&#8217;s terms we automate both sides of the bid/ask spread, until such time as we&#8217;re too far exposed in one side of the equation and then we wait to settle those positions. The % amounts of balance we&#8217;re exposed the trigger this safety behavior are configurable in these bots &#8211; all of the input variables are!</p>



<p>And while we&#8217;ve seen ~10% net ROI in less than a week and $hundreds thousands notional ETH and $millions notional BTC traded on one exchange, we&#8217;d like to get people churning deltas, alphas and notionals with subscriptions!</p>



<p>The exchanges we&#8217;re looking to support at first are those with market making fee rebates or a fee structure that&#8217;s condusive to a better trading experience &#8211; ie. Okex has a tiered fee structure that decreases with volume, which is superior to Binance&#8217;s fee tiers that decrease with volume but also require holding illiquid BNB.</p>



<p><a href="https://hackernoon.com/porting-a-bot-to-binance-futures-market-making-competition-6v6a31qh">https://hackernoon.com/porting-a-bot-to-binance-futures-market-making-competition-6v6a31qh</a></p>



<p><a href="https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/20/complaint-about-bitmexs-websocket-api-and-update-on-profitable-market-makers/">https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/20/complaint-about-bitmexs-websocket-api-and-update-on-profitable-market-makers/</a></p>



<p><a href="https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/20/complaint-about-bitmexs-websocket-api-and-update-on-profitable-market-makers/">https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/20/complaint-about-bitmexs-websocket-api-and-update-on-profitable-market-makers/</a></p>



<p>——</p>



<p>To sign up:</p>



<p>Fill out this Google Form:  <a href="https://forms.gle/WVF2SMomanKwLupY9"><strong>https://forms.gle/WVF2SMomanKwLupY9</strong></a> </p>



<p>——</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Market Maker at 10% Realized Live Gains, Signal-Based Bots at 1%, 7%!</title>
		<link>/2019/11/16/market-maker-at-10-realized-live-gains-signal-based-bots-at-1-7/</link>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 19:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coindex]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=18</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[See this post on it&#8217;s original location, github.io! It&#8217;s been a busy few days for me! What&#8217;s Current As I&#8217;d]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/16/market-maker-at-10-realized-live-gains-signal-based-bots-at-1-7/">See this post on it&#8217;s original location, github.io</a>!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-2-1024x722.png" alt="" class="wp-image-19" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-2-1024x722.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-2-300x212.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-2-768x542.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-2.png 1428w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption><br></figcaption></figure>



<p>It&#8217;s been a busy few days for me!</p>



<h2>What&#8217;s Current</h2>



<p>As I&#8217;d mentioned on Hackernoon before, <a href="https://hackernoon.com/porting-a-bot-to-binance-futures-market-making-competition-6v6a31qh">Coindex and I are admitted into the Binance Futures Market Making Competition</a>. This bot is currently being fed into the AI with competing genomes using different input variables, to give us the winning generations in terms of configurations. We&#8217;re running this market making bot on Deribit testnet and livenet &#8211; showing 10% gains on livenet, almost 50% on testnet, but these livenet results aren&#8217;t being published anywhere &#8211; yet!</p>



<p><a href="http://coindexbot.duckdns.org:8080/">You can watch the market maker on Deribit testnet in realtime here</a> &#8211; which will soon be integrated to <a href="https://coindexlabs.com/">coindexlabs.com</a>!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-3-1024x398.png" alt="" class="wp-image-20" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-3-1024x398.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-3-300x117.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-3-768x299.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-3-1536x597.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-3.png 1896w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Next up is the first bot I was hired to create in the last week. Without breaching terms of NDA, it executes trades based on a series of custom price action indicators confirmed twice by regular ol&#8217; indicators. It&#8217;s currently up 0.7% in the last three hours on Binance Futures <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/1f642.png" alt="🙂" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><br><br>You can <a href="http://patbot1.duckdns.org/">watch it live with one indicator confirming trend here</a>, <a href="http://patbo2.duckdns.org/">or two indicators to lessen the noise here</a>!</p>



<p>This bot will be available for a small subscription fee in the future times, and the benefactor has even agreed to share some of that subscription money with me &#8211; for the win! It&#8217;s so far been running 2-3 days in profit. Aweo! This bot&#8217;s ideationmaster has given me more and more income to add indicators, exchanges, and in the future it will even have Telegram bot reporting. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/1f600.png" alt="😀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-4-1024x500.png" alt="" class="wp-image-21" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-4-1024x500.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-4-300x147.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-4-768x375.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-4-1536x750.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-4.png 1892w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>A second bot I was created to hire uses a genius system to identify support and resistence, and enters in Binance Futures limit post-only too &#8211; exiting when trends reverse at market and entering in new post-only orders to win in the next trend. It&#8217;s currently up 6.5% although it hasn&#8217;t traded in a little while, have no fear! It requires the trend to be confirmed one way or another over the course of some other safety inputs.</p>



<p><a href="http://coindexbot.duckdns.org/">You can watch the delta of the delta for this one live here</a>. I don&#8217;t know if this bot&#8217;s benefactor wants to sell access to his creations or just throw some serious capital at them &#8211; stay tuned for details! Either way, he has decided he&#8217;s going to continue feeding me bot projects so I can concentrate on being productive while having the ol&#8217; rent paid <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/1f609.png" alt="😉" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>



<h2>What&#8217;s Next</h2>



<p>Coindex and myself and some of the bot ideationmasters we&#8217;ve mentioned will be working on ways to hedge losses in the case our bots see stoplosses.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-5-1024x542.png" alt="" class="wp-image-22" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-5-1024x542.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-5-300x159.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-5-768x406.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-5-1536x813.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-5.png 1890w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>What this means for Coindex at least is to use different entries for long calls+puts on the same instrument and expiry, which is called a long straddle or strangle. If the price moves up OR down significantly (causing losses on market makers) then the options will go out of money and simultaneously in the money at the same time, and at leverage on a deriviative one of them will be worth some serious money! While we&#8217;re happy to use Deribit for this, we&#8217;re excited to see a new player: Binance JEX, which supports options on many more types of underlyings. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/1f600.png" alt="😀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/1f600.png" alt="😀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>



<p>What&#8217;s beautiful in the above screenshot (among other things&#8230;) is the dynamic leverage based on volatility. One can hedge using a fraction of the funds and balance one&#8217;s exposure with their hedging &#8211; and while the market maker makes money and the options lose money, we&#8217;re still smiling. When the market maker hits stoplosses and the options make money &#8211; we&#8217;re still laughing. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/1f642.png" alt="🙂" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>



<h2>Do You Want to Know More?</h2>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization &#8211; where we&#8217;re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world&#8217;s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;!!</em></p>



<p>(<strong>Disclaimer</strong>:&nbsp;<em>The Author is the Chief Liquidity Officer at Coindex</em>)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
