<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Mental Health &#8211; jare.cloud</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/mental-health/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Jare&#039;s Cloud</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:53:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-CA</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.3.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Maslow&#8217;s Hierarchy of Needs: Universally Applied (for 1st World Countries, anyways), Here&#8217;s a Wellness Pyramid!</title>
		<link>/2020/01/21/maslovs-hierarchy-of-needs-universally-applied-for-1st-world-countries-anyways-heres-a-wellness-pyramid/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:49:25 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=304</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this post in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud! In a given Maslow&#8217;s Hierarchy of Needs you&#8217;ll find a tiered]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/21/maslovs-hierarchy-of-needs-universally-applied-for-1st-world-countries-anyways-heres-a-wellness-pyramid/">View this post in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<p>In a given Maslow&#8217;s Hierarchy of Needs you&#8217;ll find a tiered pyramid that starts with you being fed, and climbs  thru safety then belongingness and love, esteem, and finally &#8211; at the highest tier &#8211; self-actualization.</p>



<p>A brief search on your favorite search engine will find images like so:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/maslow-5.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-358" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/maslow-5.jpg 900w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/maslow-5-300x223.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/maslow-5-768x572.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" /></figure>



<p>What I&#8217;d like to suggest is a Maslow Hierarchy for people in first-world countries: where we take safety for granted. What do we need in our Wellness Pyramid in order to be, well, well?</p>



<p>On our first tier, we&#8217;ll find rest and liquids. Any doctor worth his weight in gold (or bitcoin) will tell you that the tricks to becoming well are rest and liquids. Without sleep, we&#8217;d eventually turn insane and then die &#8211; and without water, we&#8217;d die within days. Days! Interested in bitcoin? <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/">Read here how you can turn your daily browsing into potentially hundreds of dollars a month</a> &#8211; as advertisers pay YOU for viewing your ads, all the while blocking dangerous 3rd-party ads (like YouTube ads).</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-54.png" alt="" class="wp-image-359" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-54.png 981w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-54-300x210.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-54-768x537.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 981px) 100vw, 981px" /></figure>



<p>Stay hydrated!</p>



<p>On our next tier we&#8217;ll find the other stuff that medical professionals recommend for anyone, regardless of their physical or mental ailment (barring extremes, like catatonic schizophrenia): Exercise, and healthy diet!</p>



<p>We can control a whole bunch of our brains worst and best tendencies if we practice these two essential parts of our lifestyles. <a href="https://thesleepdoctor.com/2017/05/22/benefits-exercise-sleep/">With proper and regular exercise we not only sleep better</a>, but we feel better and we live longer. Fact! With healthy diet we can make sure that we keep our body&#8217;s needs in check and also feed our brains the vitamins, minerals and all that jazz that it sorely needs in order to think better, <a href="https://www.theemotionmachine.com/how-to-use-diet-to-impact-positive-thinking/">think more positively</a> and think more often.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-55.png" alt="" class="wp-image-360" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-55.png 999w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-55-300x196.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-55-768x503.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-55-120x80.png 120w" sizes="(max-width: 999px) 100vw, 999px" /></figure>



<p>Now, to be well we need to be stress-free. The #1 way to be stress-free is to distract yourself: like <a href="https://www.verywellmind.com/the-importance-of-hobbies-for-stress-relief-3144574">to spend time with hobbies reduces stress</a>, jobs, a gamenight with family or the internet&#8217;s world of memes and joy can all help you spend the time. These distractions give you little doses of dopamine throughout the day that you can expect and count on. Down this road also lies dangerous, negative solutions like drugs and alcohol giving you that same release &#8211; so take care, and try to surround yourself with activities that attribute to your overall success rather than detract from them. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-56.png" alt="" class="wp-image-361" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-56.png 999w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-56-300x206.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-56-768x527.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 999px) 100vw, 999px" /></figure>



<p>What crowns our new wellness and happiness pyramid? </p>



<p>Fulfillment.</p>



<p>We&#8217;re all trying to be heard, to be cared about and to have an effect on someone&#8217;s life, way of thinking, or their own wellbeing &#8211; whether they be close to us, or the greater population at large. Some of us take up blogging &#8211; some of us, journalism &#8211; and some of us just want to make sure we have some kind of everlasting imprint on our kids, friends or other loved ones.</p>



<p>This is quintessential to your wellbeing and health when all else is taken for granted.</p>



<p>As you grow older, you may notice that your mobility and autonomy start slipping away. You&#8217;ll no longer be able to drive, to garden, to sing &#8211; and you may find yourself less and less responsible for other people&#8217;s schedules, days, and otherwise find yourself proving less and less of a use.</p>



<p>If you&#8217;re young now: enjoy your autonomy and mobility. Enjoy the ways in which you influence others and win friends.</p>



<p>If you&#8217;re getting older: try and find new and exciting ways to have an effect on the world (like blogging, writing a book, or otherwise expressing yourself in a low-effort way. Did you know you could speak to your internet browser, and have it type out what you&#8217;re saying? It&#8217;s called Speech-to-Text!). </p>



<p>Are you interested in blogging, or are you already blogging, but want to feel a little bit extra dopamine when you&#8217;re expressing yourself? <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/20/publish0x-allowing-rewards-for-content-with-their-own-funds-re-distribution-of-wealth-defined/">Sign up for Publish0x as an author and get rewarded by people tipping you</a> &#8211; the tips come from their own funds, and the tipper earns a custom % of the tip, too, so everyone wins!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-57.png" alt="" class="wp-image-362" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-57.png 986w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-57-300x212.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-57-768x543.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 986px) 100vw, 986px" /></figure>



<p>And that concludes our Wellness Pyramid, a Maslow Hierarchy applied to everyone living where the basics are taken for granted!</p>



<h2>A Plug (or Two)</h2>



<p>Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<p>Want to learn about new articles in tech and being a madman? Subscribe to my mailing list here:&nbsp;<a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL">http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</a> </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Two Ultimate Pieces of Self-Help You Need to Achieve Goals, Survive Life One Day at a Time</title>
		<link>/2020/01/19/the-two-ultimate-pieces-of-self-help-you-need-to-achieve-goals-survive-life-one-day-at-a-time/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 04:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=319</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this article in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud! Introduction-ar-ily In order to both survive and thrive we need to]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p> <a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/19/the-two-ultimate-pieces-of-self-help-you-need-to-achieve-goals-survive-life-one-day-at-a-time/">View this article in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud</a>!  </p>



<h2>Introduction-ar-ily </h2>



<p>In order to both survive and thrive we need to take everything with a grain of salt, celebrate the small things and get through the small stuff. 12 Step programs are keen on &#8216;one day at a time,&#8217; but I want to offer up the only two strategies you&#8217;ll need in life (and I thank my mom for these bits of wisdom):</p>



<p>This Too Shall Pass and Onwards and Upwards</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://imgc.artprintimages.com/img/print/this-too-shall-pass_u-l-f7wkq40.jpg?h=550&amp;p=0&amp;w=550&amp;background=fbfbfb" alt="Image result for this too shall pass"/></figure>



<h2>Downs</h2>



<p>If you feel incredibly down, in a valley in the peaks and valleys sense, or a depression in the bipolar sense &#8211; <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/why-schizophrenia-is-the-most-under-represented-of-all-the-death-sentences/">read all about the plights of mental health woes here in another article of mine</a> &#8211; it&#8217;s most important to remember these two mantras. Sometimes the world deals us blow after blow, and it might be the worst few months you&#8217;ve ever faced &#8211; you might have lost a friend or a loved one, or a job or a prospect. Whatever the reason, how we cope with these kinds of situations helps define us as a person &#8211; without the struggle, we&#8217;d never appreciate the good that comes our way with as much of our hearts as we do.</p>



<p>This Too Shall Pass teaches us that no matter how bad it gets and no matter how bleak it might seem, there&#8217;s only up from here to go. It reminds us that we&#8217;ve been through worse &#8211; and we survived. We&#8217;re strong people, and even in the worst-case scenario we can always remember some other kind of time or even compare our experiences to those we see in media or read in books. People have gotten through these traumas.. so can you. It&#8217;s not meant to belittle or take away from your pain, but give you some solace in knowing that recovery is possible. You got this!</p>



<p>Onwards and Upwards teaches us to continue putting in the effort in order to see better manifest itself in our lives. Keep trying. Keep on swimming. We must be the masters of our own destinies and fates &#8211; leaving it up to The Powers that Be (your God, her Shiva and my Science) is taking the backseat and back burner to our own lives. You have to be the mastermind and the architect, the engineer and the manual labor in effecting your own change. Nobody else will do it for you. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://i.pinimg.com/474x/0f/fd/c4/0ffdc46102b89a9ad0bfaa9eac4daf30--narnia-balloon.jpg" alt="Image result for onwards and upwards"/></figure>



<h2> Ups</h2>



<p>What can these mantras tell us about how we should react to the mountains, as opposed to the peaks? The euphoria or mania that we sometimes experience when things are looking up? Sometimes we might get taken away by the rollercoaster of emotion that happen to us in the most joyous of times &#8211; whether it be Christmas, a new baby, graduating medical school or just an unbalanced amount of chemicals in your brain along with misfiring neurons. Whatever the reason, these sayings are just as powerful now as they were in our lowest of lows.</p>



<p>This Too Shall Pass lets us know that we can always expect the buzz and elation to eventually go away &#8211; and to prepare ourselves for more battles at a later date. It&#8217;s not meant to take away from the joy we&#8217;re experiencing, but rather to give us a sobering look at how to prepare for the coming days. We can always enjoy ourselves &#8211; and thoroughly &#8211; while still being ready for the future. An excellent example is in the honeymoon stage of new relationships: most of us have felt it, and some of us have ended up in a world of hurt once the pheromones wore out. What&#8217;s the lesson? Always have a steady head and try to remember the consequences of our actions and decisions, even if they were seen in a different light &#8211; by a later you, by your friends or family, or by society at large.</p>



<p>And when we think of Onwards and Upwards, we can remember that &#8211; on a scale approaching infinity &#8211; there is actually no limit to the amounts of joy and success we can fit into a day. When things are going super well it&#8217;s best to build on that momentum and see if we can make it even better, achieve more things or invigorate ourselves to do more, see more, be more than if we didn&#8217;t have that extra motivation. This allows us to keep pushing forward &#8211; as masters of our own success &#8211; and build the building blocks of a better, safer, happier future. Even if we consider the eventual trough or downturn in our internal state, we can lay the foundation and plant the seeds of further wealth, happiness and prosperity the next time we&#8217;re back on our uppers. </p>



<h2>Finally</h2>



<p>Remember &#8211; you are the master of the universe. You are the commander of your destiny. You are the sole reason you&#8217;re still here, and the sole reason you should keep on moving forward. This might be contrary to some of your beliefs, but at least try to read it and apply it in a way that works with what you believe to be true &#8211; the more active you are in your own life and your own situation, the more effect you&#8217;ll have &#8211; and the more of what you want will manifest. You can attribute these changes where you like!</p>



<p>Want to learn all about other ways to succeed, in a redefined version of the internet where the user wins instead of Big Publishers or Big Advertising Networks? Read all about the <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/">Brave browser here, which pays you to browse and pays you to produce content and protects all your privacy</a> along the way!</p>



<h2>A Plug (or Two)</h2>



<p>Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<p>Want to learn about new articles in tech and being a madman? Subscribe to my mailing list here:&nbsp;<a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL">http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</a> </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 4 (And Bonuses!) Reasons You Should Always Prepare for the Worst</title>
		<link>/2020/01/17/top-4-and-bonuses-reasons-you-should-always-prepare-for-the-worst/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 19:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=230</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster #1: You&#8217;ll Always be]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p> Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<h2>#1: You&#8217;ll Always be Pleasantly Surprised</h2>



<p>This is actually a secret my mom taught me over and over again. If you expect the worst possible outcome in any given situation &#8211; love, relationships, family, work &#8211; then whatever does come to pass will certainly be better than your expectations!</p>



<p>In such a way, you&#8217;ll find little joys throughout your day and week. These little joys will create a sense of reward that you might not have had if you were constantly being let down by your own expectations.</p>



<p>Framing your world in a different light can have certain advantages &#8211; for those with very specific minds, you might lose touch with the &#8216;real reality&#8217; and become a concern for your own self&#8217;s well-being. Read an article I wrote on how <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/14/how-do-people-with-mental-health-illnesses-like-schizophrenia-or-other-psychoses-think/">people with schizophrenia and mental health can actually think</a> (from first-hand experience).</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://live.staticflickr.com/2118/2511788463_03d9281e2e_z.jpg" alt="Image result for pleasant surprise"/></figure>



<h2>#2: Emergency Preparedness Saves Lives</h2>



<p>In a much more literal sense, being prepared for the worst will mean that you create disaster recovery plans &#8211; be they for the zombie apocalypse, should your car die and need repairs you can&#8217;t immediately afford, or if the lights go out for a day or two &#8211; having a plan improves your chances of getting through the scenario measurably. </p>



<p>This is so true that a brief Google search returns many millions islands (results, in Google English Pirate language) for &#8217;emergency preparedness course,&#8217; <a href="https://www.googleadservices.com/pagead/aclk?sa=L&amp;ai=DChcSEwjL39ilpYvnAhVN1sAKHex_BzcYABAAGgJpbQ&amp;ohost=www.google.com&amp;cid=CAESQOD2M1X01icn_Ddsj9d_VtuSw2OJzkWb-hMqPuHbRQdhjHlW1fmxM4R73TFopbDePIk6WevtDEoZfVqZPTnors0&amp;sig=AOD64_0WZlRmA4DrGAF_Av58ZgcPrRp7aA&amp;q=&amp;ved=2ahUKEwixoc2lpYvnAhXFWc0KHTQqBxIQ0Qx6BAgQEAE&amp;adurl=">like this one at a Canadian university</a>.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-19-1024x696.png" alt="" class="wp-image-231" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-19-1024x696.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-19-300x204.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-19-768x522.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-19.png 1178w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2>#3: You&#8217;ll Be Ready for Anything</h2>



<p>Hand in hand with being prepared for the worst-case scenario, you&#8217;ll also be ready for all the other scenarios up and down the range of possible outcomes &#8211; from the best possible ones right down to what could potentially be the absolute worst. Because you have considered and somehow either counted or discounted each possible route, you will have a plan for accomplishing things regardless of how fate will twist your arm. </p>



<p>As you get more and more used to this mental exercise, you&#8217;ll notice that your breadth of perception will naturally expand &#8211; as you&#8217;ll be considering more &#8216;twists of fate,&#8217; having added personal experience and the nature of the universe as it tends towards infinity. What I mean to say, rather, is that as the Powers That Be (whatever you subscribe to) throw new and unexpected curveballs your way, your brain will naturally plan for even more possibilities and outcomes. This will expand your mind way better than the hippie in highschool promised you Lysergic Acid Diethylamide ever could have come close to.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://i.guim.co.uk/img/media/4e83b3f710949ba6d82614821d6d3f93dd1786b9/0_1020_3125_1875/master/3125.jpg?width=300&amp;quality=85&amp;auto=format&amp;fit=max&amp;s=7fd40712c4db8af6b93a0ab9580243a9" alt="Image result for lsd"/></figure>



<h2>#4: You&#8217;ll Achieve More Goals</h2>



<p>Well, #3 was a bit of a doublethink mindfuck. What does it translate to, practically? Why should it be encouraging, rather than something to be afraid of?</p>



<p>In reality, creating new and interesting ways to approach problems will give you new and novel ways of conquering those problems. Your new disaster emergency preparedness attitude &#8211; when applied to everything &#8211; will allow you to accomplish more and more of your goals, more and more frequently. </p>



<p>This has a fantastic effect on your mindset, and overall happiness. If you do end up doing the things you set out to do more often than you do now, or even in fashions you hadn&#8217;t considered before, then you&#8217;ll have more and more dopamine for your pleasure centers &#8211; which means a happier, healthier you!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://images.saba.com/uploads/blog/what-should-you-do-when-you-dont-accomplish-your-goals/what-should-you-do-when-you-dont-accomplish-your-goals.jpg?s=1696x900" alt="Image result for accomplish"/></figure>



<h2>Bonus: Win Friends and Influence Enemies</h2>



<p>With a happier, healthier you comes a number of bonus effects &#8211; like a boost in charisma, confidence, ability. This truly is a snowball effect of positive outcomes.</p>



<p>When you present yourself better &#8211; or at least, more confidently &#8211; it results in people taking you more seriously, or appreciating you (or at least, your opinions and voice) more and more. This will allow you to gain more traction at work, home, and play. </p>



<p>It will allow you to harness your new-found powers of persuasion in two important ways. First, you&#8217;ll be able to befriend more people more frequently &#8211; winning their approval and allowing them to become proponents of whatever causes or values you subscribe to. Second, you&#8217;ll be able to exert your newfound influence over people who might detract from your causes or values &#8211; allowing you to gain more of a say over the people who would do you ill or harm (even just on the theoretical, intellectual level).</p>



<p>Did I interest you already about the ways in which a segregated, compartmentalized mindset can be a blessing &#8211; and a curse? <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/why-schizophrenia-is-the-most-under-represented-of-all-the-death-sentences/">Read my other article here on how schizophrenia increases your chances of an early end to your mortal turmoil</a> (read again: it&#8217;s a fatal diagnosis. No, no joke!)</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/51Ad%2BUal74L.jpg" alt="Image result for win friends influence people"/></figure>



<h2>Bonus (Voice of Reason!) #2: This Is Actually a Lot of Work</h2>



<p>When you&#8217;re tasking your mind with so much data to consume and analyze, you&#8217;re actually spending a lot more time thinking about yourself and your surroundings, experiences and misconceptions an awful lot more than you are should you not be exercising this theory. This can translate to an awful lot of work &#8211; something that might end up tasking you to a point where it can do more harm than good.</p>



<p>Truly, if you become preoccupied by this exercise and it gets in the way of goals rather than helping them &#8211; or prevents you from performing at work, home, school, or anywhere &#8211; then it might not be worth the time that goes into it. As with anything, it&#8217;s good in moderation &#8211; and we should always exercise a good balance in our own minds.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="http://m.quickmeme.com/img/e3/e3a8e54d319943a447a88e1fc37c027eba0991c2af0bf7af9ea6822622db1c13.jpg" alt="Image result for everything in moderation meme"/></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Schizophrenia: Curse or Blessing? Death Sentence or Gift?</title>
		<link>/2020/01/15/why-schizophrenia-is-the-most-under-represented-of-all-the-death-sentences/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 08:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=192</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View This Article in it&#8217;s Original Form on Jare.Cloud! Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/why-schizophrenia-is-the-most-under-represented-of-all-the-death-sentences/">View This Article in it&#8217;s Original Form on Jare.Cloud</a>!</p>



<p> Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<p>With <a href="https://learn.onemonth.com/hacker-noon/">June estimates at 7000+ authors</a>, 69 other Hackernoon contributors might also be a victim of schizophrenia, along with me. This article serves to demonstrate why these people are facing tougher-than-average odds to live to a ripe old age, and how society isn&#8217;t doing them justice in helping or finding a permanent solution.</p>



<h2>Schizophrenia</h2>



<p>Schizophrenia is the psychotic disorder that&#8217;s defined by losing control over your reality. If you start to slip into beliefs or experiences &#8211; auditory, visual &#8211; that others don&#8217;t perceive, you&#8217;re schizophrenic! There&#8217;s other qualifiers to the disorder, like having a certain frequency and total number occurrences of these thoughts &#8211; as well as a lack of other conditions which may otherwise explain these often terrifying and traumatizing thoughts.</p>



<p>What counts as an hallucination or delusion? A hallucination is an effect on your senses that others can&#8217;t perceive. You might see something that isn&#8217;t there, hear something in the distance that only you can hear &#8211; you might even perceive other people perceiving your hallucinations, which is a trap on it&#8217;s own because now your hallucinations are covering your other hallucinations. You can see how easy it would be to lose touch with reality when your own human mind makes up its mind to revolt!</p>



<p>A delusion is a belief in something, some thought or idea or pattern that nobody else can perceive. You might think the media is talking to you, telling you to do things in secret code. You might think that you are somehow special, be it superpowers or the fact that you&#8217;re President &#8211; these delusions can vary in strength and severity, and may even go unnoticed in some for years and years before causing any issues.</p>



<p>There are negative symptoms of schizophrenia, too &#8211; where the positive symptoms are qualities you&#8217;ve gained or acquired from the illness, like hallucinations or delusions &#8211; the negative symptoms are things that you&#8217;ve lost with the new mental state. These could be habits or behaviours like caring about one&#8217;s well-being (cooking, cleaning, self-care) or curtailing one&#8217;s hobbies due to lack of interest.</p>



<h2>Prevalence</h2>



<p><a href="https://www.mentalhelp.net/schizophrenia/statistics/">Schizophrenia affects 1% of the population, 1.5% of Americans and 1.5 million people were diagnosed with it this year.</a> This translates to 300 000 Canadians, nearly 5 million Americans &#8211; verily, 105 million people around the world. Indeed, someone you know &#8211; more than one person you know &#8211; could very well be suffering.</p>



<h2>Concurrent Disorders &amp; Overdoses</h2>



<p><a href="https://www.addictioncenter.com/addiction/schizophrenia/">Nearly half of people suffering from schizophrenia abuse drugs and alcohol</a>. We call this a &#8216;concurrent disorder&#8217; &#8211; meaning that drugs and alcohol abuse are occurring at the same time as the psychological symptoms that lead a professional to diagnose schizophrenia.</p>



<p>I bid you welcome to the first reason schizophrenia is a death sentence: <a href="https://www.drugabuse.gov/related-topics/trends-statistics/overdose-death-rates">0.216% of the American population died from overdoses</a> from 1999-2017 (with a noticeable trend upwards in deaths/year). Given that <a href="https://www.drugabuse.gov/publications/drugfacts/nationwide-trends">9.4% of the population reported using illicit drugs</a> in the last month:</p>



<p>Americans: 300 000 000<br>
Drug abusers: 28 200 000 (9.4%)<br>
Deaths / 18 years: 648 000 (0.216%)<br>
Deaths / abusers: 2.3%<br>
Abusers / schizophrenics: 50%<br>
Schizophrenics: 5 000 000 (1.5%)<br>
Abusers that are schizophrenics: 2 500 000 (0.75%)<br>
Deaths / abusers that are schizophrenics: 57 500 (1.15% of # schizophrenic)<br>
Deaths schizophrenics / deaths abusers: 8.88%</p>



<p>8.88/2.3: you are 3.86 times as likely to die from an overdose than the average drug abuser if you&#8217;re schizophrenic.<br> 1.15/0.216: you are 5.32 times as likely to die from an overdose than the average person if you&#8217;re schizophrenic. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-5-1024x543.png" alt="" class="wp-image-194" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-5-1024x543.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-5-300x159.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-5-768x407.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-5.png 1418w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2>Suicides</h2>



<p>The <a href="https://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;rct=j&amp;q=&amp;esrc=s&amp;source=web&amp;cd=3&amp;cad=rja&amp;uact=8&amp;ved=2ahUKEwj9lIGGiYXnAhXKl-AKHVlcA-kQFjACegQIAxAB&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fafsp.org%2Fabout-suicide%2Fsuicide-statistics%2F&amp;usg=AOvVaw2pQbS5wgQ6GOwg_6X9pNYI">suicide rate for Americans is 0.014%</a> when &#8216;adjusted.&#8217;</p>



<p>The <a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC2951591/">&#8216;lifetime risk of suicide&#8217; for people with schizophrenia is 4.9%</a>.</p>



<p>Americans: 300 000 000<br>
Suicides: 4 200 000 (0.014%)<br>
Suicides / schizophrenics: 4.9%<br>
Schizophrenics: 5 000 000 (1.5%)<br>
Suicides that are schizophrenics: 245 000 (0.08%)</p>



<p>4.9/0.014: you are 350 times as likely to die from suicide than the average person if you&#8217;re schizophrenic.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-6-1024x418.png" alt="" class="wp-image-195" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-6-1024x418.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-6-300x122.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-6-768x313.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-6.png 1064w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>I&#8217;ll let the numbers speak for themselves in this section.</p>



<h2>Smoking Cigarettes</h2>



<p>According to the CDC, <a href="https://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;rct=j&amp;q=&amp;esrc=s&amp;source=web&amp;cd=1&amp;cad=rja&amp;uact=8&amp;ved=2ahUKEwi2nbLEioXnAhVlmeAKHYs-AM4QFjAAegQIARAB&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cdc.gov%2Ftobacco%2Fdata_statistics%2Ffact_sheets%2Fadult_data%2Fcig_smoking%2Findex.htm&amp;usg=AOvVaw1lrsmaMLcnUe3I1S6iAF4g">34 000 000 Americans smoke</a>. <a href="http://www.schizophrenia.com/smokereport.htm#">90% of schizophrenics smoke</a>. <a href="https://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;rct=j&amp;q=&amp;esrc=s&amp;source=web&amp;cd=5&amp;cad=rja&amp;uact=8&amp;ved=2ahUKEwjIgLz6ioXnAhXSmOAKHUO6CMEQFjAEegQIDBAU&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.washingtonpost.com%2Fnews%2Fwonk%2Fwp%2F2015%2F02%2F26%2Fthe-terrifying-rate-at-which-smokers-die-from-smoking%2F&amp;usg=AOvVaw0z4xmvDAkNBTEm8aQAQVMf">67% of smokers die from smoking</a>, 474500 a year. Excuse the changing numbers here, in the previous calculation the 1.5% of schizophrenics was from the stat &#8211; and in this second calculation it&#8217;s divided into my guesstimation of total Americans, so 1.666%.</p>



<p>Americans: 300 000 000<br>
Smokers: 34 000 000 (11.33%)<br>
Smokers that die from smoking: 387600 (0.1292%)<br>
Deaths / smokers: 1.14%<br>
Deaths / population: 2 193 000 (0.731%)<br>
Dead smokers / deaths: 17.67%<br>
Smokers / schizophrenics: 90%<br>
Schizophrenics: 5 000 000 (1.666%)<br>
Smokers that are schizophrenics: 4 500 000 (1.5%)<br>
Smokers that are schizophrenics that die: 63 000 <br>
Deaths schizophrenic smokers: 1.26%</p>



<p>You are 11% more likely to die if you smoke while schizophrenic than the average smoker.<br> You are 1.72x as likely to die in a given year if you smoke while schizophrenic than the  average population.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-7-1024x463.png" alt="" class="wp-image-196" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-7-1024x463.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-7-300x136.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-7-768x347.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-7-1536x694.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-7.png 1614w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2>Research</h2>



<p><a href="https://www.hiv.gov/federal-response/funding/budget">0.856 billion is spent on HIV/AIDS efforts a year</a>, affecting <a href="https://www.hiv.gov/hiv-basics/overview/data-and-trends/statistics">1.1 million Americans</a> and <a href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/how-many-people-die-from-aids-each-year-49053">26 000 Americans die from HIV/AIDS each year</a>. $<a href="https://www.cancer.gov/about-cancer/understanding/statistics">147 000 000 000 is spent on cancer research</a> a year and <a href="https://www.cancer.gov/about-cancer/understanding/statistics">609 000 Americans will die from cancer every year</a> &#8211; 38.4% of people will or have had or do have cancer.</p>



<p><a href="http://www.schizophrenia.com/szfacts.htm">$74.65 is spent on research per person diagnosed with schizophrenia</a>, <a href="https://www.hiv.gov/federal-response/funding/budget">$788.70 for HIV/AIDS per person</a> and $1276.04 for cancer per person. </p>



<p>Seems a bit strange, no?</p>



<h2>The Good News</h2>



<p>While the debate of nature vs nature rages on &#8211; including <a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2006-01387-000">scholarly articles with 1000+ citations</a>, I firmly stand as a testament: nurture wins. Even when dealt with an incredibly bad &#8211; and incredibly rare &#8211; hand of cards, I&#8217;ve managed to change all the detriments of psychosis and sociopathy into benefits. In some degree or another, most of my symptomatic behaviors have indeed become some kind of tool for me to be more successful.</p>



<h2>Hand of Cards </h2>



<p>My current diagnoses include: </p>



<p>Schizo-affective disorder, which evolved from diagnoses of drug-induced schizophrenia and paranoid schizophrenia. Schizo-affective is &#8216;enough symptoms to be diagnosed schizophrenic but also with an underlying major mood disorder,&#8217; in my case bipolar. <a href="https://www.nami.org/learn-more/mental-health-conditions/schizoaffective-disorder">Prevalence of schizo-affective disorder: 0.3% of general population</a>.</p>



<p>I&#8217;m also diagnosed with panic disorder, which looks and feels very much like Post Traumatic Stress Disorder except without an actual logical trauma or trigger. It&#8217;s random, and fits in with the psychoses.  <a href="https://www.nimh.nih.gov/health/statistics/panic-disorder.shtml">Prevalence of panic disorder: 2.7% of general population</a>. </p>



<p>A final diagnosis is much newer, and this one&#8217;s iffy. They discussed it, along with whether or not I&#8217;d like to be tested on the Autism spectrum, but never wrote down any of this discussion &#8211; leading me to think that my psychosis made up sociopathy. Irregardless, there&#8217;s nothing you can do to actually treat a personality type &#8211; so there&#8217;s no real point officially diagnosing it. However, it does explain a lot of my personality and some of my traits: <a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/conditions/antisocial-personality-disorder">Anti-Social Personality Disorder has a prevalence of 3% in men, 1% in women</a>. On paper, it looks a lot like narcissism except less likely to think myself as special and more likely to discount social convention or norms, including things like paying back debts (whoops) or feeling a need to pay taxes (ha).</p>



<h2>Advantages</h2>



<p>Probably my favorite psychotic symptom I draw strength from is called &#8216;clanging.&#8217; It&#8217;s a proclivity to rhythm or cadence, rhyming in speech. It gives me a very specific way of typing and writing that a certain kind of reader finds some poetry to &#8211; and it&#8217;s one of the main reasons I like hearing or re-reading my own content. This, in turn, is one of the reasons I push out as much content as I do. Content is king, and a regular contributor is more likely to gain a following and make a dollar doing this for fun &amp; profit! Without the symptom, I&#8217;d do far less content. <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h5aSa4tmVNM">Bi-winning</a>! My content here on Hackernoon and on other publications alone has led me to basically skip interviews and acquire employment as a founding member of a tech startup that has legs &#8211; <a href="https://hackernoon.com/coindex-labs-novel-search-applied-via-evolutionary-ai-creating-a-money-making-machine-n62j2gei">read about Coindex Labs and how we&#8217;re building a money-making machine here</a>.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-32-1024x602.png" alt="" class="wp-image-257" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-32-1024x602.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-32-300x176.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-32-768x452.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-32-850x500.png 850w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-32.png 1277w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>What&#8217;s more is that a sheer depth and breadth of understanding and perception gives me insight into people, communications, arguments and perspectives that not many people have. This has led me to be a fantastic manager of people and stakeholders, balancing everyone&#8217;s opinions and underlying emotions better than the average Joe Product or Project manager. Even at a less stressful level, this allowed me to excel in call centers as customer &amp; technical support &#8211; all the way throughout my career, conquering first technical account management and then later community management (especially in cryptocurrency). This one single factor has led me to be successfully employed in extended contracts that allowed me to be alive and thrive in ways I&#8217;d never thought possible when first wrestling through my diagnoses. When you live the lives of countless people you&#8217;ve never met, you start to become more attuned with everyone &#8211; by natural extension.</p>



<p>While some other symptoms really do prove to be a negative &#8211; things like losing an interest in my appearance, or upkeep of my surroundings &#8211; the real benefit here comes from challenging one&#8217;s own nature and making sure that the important thing that don&#8217;t seem so important are done anyways. If you can prioritize things in your life that you might not otherwise prioritize because it improves the mood and expectations of others, then you can apply this to then workplace in wondrous and effective ways. Sometimes, the mundane and repetitive tasks might make your role as a developer or manager seem daunting on a daily basis &#8211; but there&#8217;s probably a reason you were delegated these tasks, and I assure you it doesn&#8217;t go unnoticed &#8211; someone notices it. Conquering my deficiencies in the world around me has led me to be a pro at assuming more requirements and responsibilities, making me a more and more integral and critical cog in the overall mechanism. This quickly helps me add value. When I&#8217;m delegated something that could be automated I automate it and achieve double winnings with my time and effort. After all, delegation and automation (also: elimination. Don&#8217;t delegate or automate something that can just simply not be done!) are the <a href="https://tim.blog/4-hour-workweek-tools/">keys to a 4-hour workweek</a> (or any other measure of success). </p>



<h2>A Plug</h2>



<p>Want to learn about new articles in tech and being a madman? Subscribe to my mailing list here: <a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL">http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>How do people with mental health illnesses like schizophrenia or other psychoses think?</title>
		<link>/2020/01/14/how-do-people-with-mental-health-illnesses-like-schizophrenia-or-other-psychoses-think/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 01:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=168</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this article in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud! Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/722/0*xYsewcQ1HGRJq-Us" alt=""/></figure>



<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/14/how-do-people-with-mental-health-illnesses-like-schizophrenia-or-other-psychoses-think/">View this article in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud!</a></p>



<p> Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<p>He stared out from behind his eyes wide shut. In front of him, displayed like countless myriad millions television screens laid one next to each other, were the lives of everyone he’d ever lived — partially, completely, not at all or fully.</p>



<p>He focused on one where he was little Jane being picked up and twirled by her dad. In ecstasy, Jane laughed in joy and giggled in fear as she twirled higher and faster. These are the moments she would remember with elation for the rest of her life, years after her father died in a tragic motorbike accident that could have been avoided — years after Jane has her own kids, twirling them with the same gusto every opportunity she’d had.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/591/0*qdoq097kM6cGT8MP.jpg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Focusing again, James was Ira being raped by four men in a back alley. The pain, anguish, fear and feel of the knife built anxiety and pain, paranoia and shame for a lifetime — never to be forgiven, forgotten, and never to be repaired.</p>



<p>He was the rapists, exacting dominance. Both the shameful and the shameless.</p>



<p>He was the onlooker, too scared to intervene. Coward. Dastardly.</p>



<p>He was the doctor, the father, the stillborn.</p>



<p>James’ eyes shifted and saw 100s more ‘screens,’ 100s more entries into the days, moments, lifetimes of people around the world — billions of people he was doomed to relive the lives of, over and over, backwards and forwards throughout time and back again.</p>



<p>There was no escape.</p>



<p>He is God, having only ever wanted to sacrifice immortality and — as is the only Godly pursuit — die and be forgotten.</p>



<p>He is Jane.</p>



<p>He is Ira.</p>



<p>He will wake up tomorrow and be Josh for a day.</p>



<p>A moment, Alex.</p>



<p>An infinity, Gods long dead and forgotten by history. Contrived and devised, planned and propagated by people — propagated to subjugate, control, extract money and exact dominance — immortal by design, infinite in the eyes of those who can’t plausibly conceive infinity.</p>



<p>Eyes wide shut.</p>



<p>Countless more animals, rocks, alien worlds — dissociation is a scary, scary thing. One loses one’s senses and knowledge of one’s self, one loses one’s memories and sense of humanity. As a rock on Mars, what do we remember of the Holocaust? What do we remember of Christianity? What do we remember of James? As a rock on Neptune, what do we remember of the rock on Mars?</p>



<p>Being God, how could he refute God?</p>



<p>He’d long since felt the panic leave his body. He’d long since laid there, catatonic, wishing for a sanity he remembered in his childhood. Drifting in and out of consciousness, drifting in and out of the conscience of others. He was all of his ex lovers, he was every side of every argument he’d ever had. He was the ultra-rich. He was the ultra-poor. He was puppy, squid, house. Woman, house, fish, bee. Acceleration, deceleration. Up, down.</p>



<p>As his mind entered the all-familiar mantra of dichotomies, a part of him wondered if he were stuck like this — forever lost between perceptions and realities, forever without a name, legacy, or history. A part of him chimed in that this is what happens every time, and like the Beatles said the sun will come out tomorrow.. There will always be another day, another dawn, another lapse of time where he was he and he wasn’t Jane, Ira, or God. These two parts argued — there were other voices that chimed in — the voices argued, and took bets amongst themselves about whether or not this was the last time, the final straw that broke that camel’s back and landed him forever lost. The voices took bets whether or not he would commit suicide today, tomorrow, die by arrow or die by plane engines falling from the sky — the voices argued…</p>



<p>The dichotomies grew louder to keep them from taking over. To keep them at bay: ocean, sky. Arrow, wound. Nothingness, everything. Quantum. Three states. On, off, both and neither. 1, 0,…</p>



<p>Catatonic. Not moving. Not interacting. Fearing the next day, fearing the chances the voices won and saw him off himself with a bottle of bleach. Fearing God’s revenge. Fearing Ira’s rapists. Fearing Jane’s dad’s drunk driver hit-and-run. Panic sets in…</p>



<p>The heart feels on fire, the heart feels as though it’ll give out. The breathing speeds up. The thoughts continue, and the feedback cycle sets in — faster heart, faster breathing, more psychosis, faster heart, faster breathing.. In the past, James had called emergency services fearing the physical symptoms. Now, having learned how his body tricks his mind tricks his body — a tango nobody wants to endure — he endures it. He sits through it. Looking out from eyes wide shut, he’s aware of the room around him behind closed eyes. Open eyes? He can’t tell anymore. They’re shutting and opening, he can see through them when shut. He is infinite. He is God.</p>



<p>He wouldn’t wish this fate on his worst enemies.</p>



<p>He is patient zero.</p>



<p>He wants to start support groups. He wants to help. He wants to educate, lift stigma, teach, and help others find a peace within themselves they can’t find on their own. He wants to be a voice for those without a voice.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/827/0*FUcYxeuEueSWPZ0J" alt=""/></figure>



<p>He can’t.</p>



<p>He’s disabled.</p>



<p>He’s destroyed — inwardly, outwardly — he lays there each night on the brink of madness and puts on a smile each day for friends and family. He turns to drugs and alcohol to turn down the mantra, turn down the voices, and takes his medication knowing that The Man’s pharmaceutical agenda is to keep his voice from being heard. He’s dangerous. He threatens the status quo.</p>



<p>He’s not alone.</p>



<p>Squelched by the drugs — prescribed and not — he’s silenced by a system that didn’t give him a chance. The trade is a fair one — lose your autonomy for a series of time that goes by without hallucinations or delusions. Keep yourself in the ‘real’ reality, take these pills, we’ve supplied loads of cocaine on the street to keep you in check.</p>



<p>He is your cousin, your son, your friend, your lover.</p>



<p>As much as he’s everyone, everyone is him.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
