<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; DunnCreativeSS</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Get Your Git Here!</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 03:20:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-CA</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.3.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Decentralized Social Media</title>
		<link>/2019/12/30/decentralized-social-media/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 03:19:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=155</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[**submitted to Hackernoon, submitted to GCNews.io** Incentive I’m not necessarily after $200, I’m after a voice. While published on Hackernoon]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>**submitted to Hackernoon, submitted to GCNews.io**</p>



<h2>Incentive</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-twitter wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Let&#39;s try an experiment: $200 BTC bounty for the best review of decentralized social media.<br><br>The ideal piece covers not just crypto efforts like Voice/Akasha, but allied tech like Mastodon, CRDT, Bittorrent, Git.<br><br>Reply to this tweet with your post! cc <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@cz_binance</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@VitalikButerin</a> <a href="https://t.co/hhS0TXU9fX">https://t.co/hhS0TXU9fX</a></p>&mdash; Balaji S. Srinivasan (@balajis) <a href="https://twitter.com/balajis/status/1210639705143951360?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 27, 2019</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>I’m not necessarily after $200, I’m after a voice. While <a href="https://hackernoon.com/@jare">published on Hackernoon many times</a> and having a <a href="https://github.com/dunncreativess">Github with 100+ repositories</a>, I’d thought it might be a good idea to take part in this competition and get the attention of <a href="https://twitter.com/balajis">https://twitter.com/balajis</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance">https://twitter.com/cz_binance</a> &#8211; maybe even <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin">https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin</a>.</p>



<h1>Preface: Censorship</h1>



<p>This most recent bit of news time saw YouTube censor many crypto-related voices, and a mail broadcast I received from LBRY mentioned a few (or a lot?) of them ended up there to promote their views and opinions. Moreover, we saw MetaMask removed from the Android Play Store (and also, consequently, my device), purportedly for mining crypto and more likely for offering a competing environment where people can consume the internet than the Play Store itself. This level of censorship creates a world where a few big players (aka. the ultra-rich) can dictate to us what content we can consume where, and leads the way to a dangerous version of the internet where all we can possibly consume is the ultra-rich’s agenda.<br></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/1gypbqvU8CjCzicIgUaUFeVLX56b7Te7lREUwnDONBeR9DMGKZo5NmhRbJBZ4ZGP5wvN_Ze4cSy0XxFxZ0LcX5YxynExXuxQOQRXXrBQfrvJb7W-aVqSS6ybJrjbRCUkjmx16S-R" alt=""/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/4qwxvQORDVRn_oxTr_nuxml1XJZLFwyXCl8daa-l7-PRVzmaE2r4NGU9vv-AT-p6BU_CPQD7EQwsHA7XnOVhs6aWbxa9LZEeDawyXMMVqyPWFT_EvREpnsAOEt2UGl_I_WoxAPKp" alt=""/></figure>



<p>The answer is an open and vibrant decentralized community where censorship plays no part. Minds.com comes to mind, but there has to be other underlying mechanisms to preserve the rights and freedoms of people everywhere &#8211; even in a censorship-free arena, we shouldn’t be subjected to hate speech and other dark web reminiscent dark corners of the internet. This kind of content from supremacists and trolls alike would hurt the overall image and therein hurt adoption &#8211; which would kill our creation before it’s born.<br></p>



<p>SteemIt comes to mind &#8211; along with it’s various interfaces, (and in recent iterations allow an even more well-thought / which allow a) way for people to downvote ‘bad’ content. This is a great solution for the decentralized community to self-moderate it’s own content monstrosity, but by and large this creates a demand for labor that can’t easily be rewarded (cue Steem’s life-long battle trying to figure out how to balance inflationary rewards with the need to self-moderate &#8211; and their nearly Steem-killing problem with people using the reward structure to bribe rewards and over-reward themselves).<br></p>



<h1>Monetization and Reward Mechanisms</h1>



<p>At this point, it’s crucial to remind ourselves that Blockchain is not cryptocurrency. Read that again! The huge interest that the ICO craze pulled into Blockchain was equally as damaging to the image of Blockchain &#8211; if not more &#8211; than the dark web’s dependency on Bitcoin as an anonymous online currency was to the image of Bitcoin. A reward mechanism for users for a decentralized social platform is not required, but could benefit actual users &#8211; actual people &#8211; for their content and social interactions.<br></p>



<p>If there’s a reward mechanism built into a new decentralized social media, it should be one that allows users to reward their favorite users through micropayments and allows the generation of additional rewards through staking an amount of e-currency someone already has &#8211; showing a dedication to the network and allowing the network more buying pressure than selling pressure. Steem does this, but I’m guessing people would want to stake more if there were more perceived reward &#8211; ie. you could earn more from your social presence as a direct result of staking more.&nbsp;<br></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/tawIPlUa64-MNSJ2LPqEAZDmam5AF-HvZ_d_J6iFcNreeFphWd9CzwRG5AkMrSee2i2Op4R0ivoHrBSHYyu_88pT2YUmCX-oJw5io_LRWixstkez3Q74z8XVczk0mv-dE76LEFvk" alt=""/></figure>



<p>If I had a dime for each time I had this conversation &#8211; with some underemployed or unemployed, disenfranchised friend on the internet &#8211; if we had a way to monetize and reward engaging social content we could empower the unbanked worldwide.&nbsp;<br></p>



<h1>Moderation</h1>



<p>&#8212; Note this isn’t the original (or even unoriginal) purposes of this neural evolutionary AI project &#8211; I’m going out on a limb here, without consulting our AI devs on this &#8211; but I think that the given problem would be socially acceptable content, and one could train the proof of fitness to provide that goal. Why not? &#8212;</p>



<p>In projects in the past like Akasha or Mastadon, one key feature that’s perplexed developers is how to monitor and remove spam, plagiarism, hate speech, etc. In a world with increasingly smart AI, there’s no reason to put this labor onto individual users like in Steem &#8211; one could create a neural evolutionary AI that’s rewarded by achieving happier individuals through a ‘report’ mechanism on leftover content. If something’s reported, then that competing generation responsible for that post is hit with a ‘ding’ that keeps it from being the master genome in that set &#8211; and the master genome carries on to start a new generation of competing genomes to do a better job in the next set of posts that are all moderated.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The computational power required to run these competing and learning sets of problem-solving algos could be served by p2p nodes that are run by users around the world &#8211; with as little as a laptop, in another chain that rewards the users submitting to the champion net.&nbsp;</p>



<p><a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1VBJ0UoY7MjeIEX0ljPj6G35qqnSizTv-XgzCiAx04F8/edit?usp=sharing">Read more in OuroborosChain &#8211; a white paper detailing neural evolutionary AI</a>.</p>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;</em></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization – where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em> !!</em></p>



<h1>Disclaimer</h1>



<p>The author is Chief Liquidity Officer for Coindex Labs.<br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Benefits of Neomenia and Crypto Growth Hacker &#8211; Compound Your Crypto!</title>
		<link>/2019/12/23/benefits-of-neomenia-and-crypto-growth-hacker-compound-your-crypto/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 11:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=146</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Hi SteemIt! View this post in it&#8217;s original form on dunncreativess.github.io! View my other posts on Hackernoon. Yes I&#8217;m promoting]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hi SteemIt! View this post in it&#8217;s <a href="http://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/12/23/benefits-of-neomenia-and-crypto-growth-hacker-compound-your-crypto/">original form on dunncreativess.github.io</a>! View my <a href="https://hackernoon.com/@jare">other posts on Hackernoon.</a> Yes I&#8217;m promoting this post &#8211; I think I have some info you folks might appreciate!</p>



<p>With results among users ranging from 3-4%, and a total net returns for some users at 16-22+% over a few days, it looks as though Neomenia is here to make an improvement in people&#8217;s lives.</p>



<p>Trading on three exchanges simultaneously and hedging risk by altering strategies based on conditions on a given exchange, it looks like Crypto Growth Hacker is the one-stop-shop for crypto investment diversification.</p>



<p>Neomenia now supports trailing takeprofit, meaning the upwards potential of a good buy or sell has increased significantly with your configurable takeprofit. It also has a special feature where the stop size is reduced by the difference in price as a percent when it moves in the right direction, so that you can lock in your profits faster while having a larger stoploss in case sh#t hits the fan.</p>



<p>The win/lose ratio is 5:1&#8230; and <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/XBTUSD/FkIqJJcy-Introducing-Neomenia/">it backtested 10 000% on TradingView</a>.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s a price action observed in one spot confirmed in another confirmed again by a direcitonal indicator, and that&#8217;s all I&#8217;m allowed saying under NDA.. but if you want to know more, join the Neomenia chat on Telegram! <a href="https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A">https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-1024x408.png" alt="" class="wp-image-149" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-1024x408.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-300x119.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-768x306.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-1536x611.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1.png 1874w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Crypto Growth Hacker is indexing Bitmex, Deribit and Binance Futures now and using a complex market making strategy on the first two while employing Neomenia on the third. The result is a bot that&#8217;s incredibly resilient and doesn&#8217;t take very many hits that last too too long &#8211; and shows steady gains.</p>



<p>Want to know more? Join our Telegram! <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-148" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1.png 880w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1-300x163.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1-768x416.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 880px) 100vw, 880px" /></figure>



<p>What&#8217;s great about both offerings is the community. We have scores of new users &#8211; and scores of people supporting us through thick and thin &#8211; and that all starts with posts like these, to raise awareness.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4-498x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-150" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4-498x1024.png 498w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4-146x300.png 146w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4.png 622w" sizes="(max-width: 498px) 100vw, 498px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5-498x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-151" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5-498x1024.png 498w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5-146x300.png 146w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5.png 622w" sizes="(max-width: 498px) 100vw, 498px" /></figure>



<p>We&#8217;re helping each other, and helping ourselves. You&#8217;re more than welcome to join! We&#8217;d be happy to have you. Ask questions! Grow with us!</p>



<p>We also have attractive referral campaigns for those of you who have an audience or know the inner workings of the magical internet.. ask us how to get 10% of your referral&#8217;s profits, or a straight (and recurring.. ) fee!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-147" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1.png 899w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1-288x300.png 288w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1-768x800.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 899px) 100vw, 899px" /></figure>



<p><a href="https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A">Neomenia Telegram</a></p>



<p><a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">Crypto Growth Hacker Telegram</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
