<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Bots &#8211; jare.cloud</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/bots/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Jare&#039;s Cloud</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 04:38:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-CA</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.3.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Amazon Ebay Aliexpress Retail-Arbitrage-As-A-Service</title>
		<link>/2020/01/16/amazon-ebay-aliexpress-retail-arbitrage-as-a-service/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 04:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insanely Marketable Business Ideas]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=222</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[As I detailed in this recent article surrounding Twitter automation to buy cryptocurrency during pumps and in this way-old Hackernoon]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As I detailed in this recent article surrounding <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/automated-crypto-trading-bot-to-buy-pump-and-dump-sentiment-signals-from-twitter/">Twitter automation to buy cryptocurrency during pumps</a> and in this way-old Hackernoon and Medium discussing how I once <a href="https://medium.com/@jarettdunn/i-1000th-idea-to-make-money-online-via-python-chained-sqlmaps-8acb25cc9ad8?source=your_stories_page---------------------------">toyed with the morality of ethical hacking for profit</a> &#8211; it&#8217;s obvious that I often have ideas for tech businesses that don&#8217;t really get off the ground. I lack the marketing chops to execute these things, so I&#8217;m going to continue letting you guys know how my Proof of Concepts go and maybe one day some of you can make a living with one of my ideas!</p>



<p>This is another entry in Insanely Marketable Business Ideas. Hooah!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/606522166166421534/667572917105590282/unknown.png" alt=""/><figcaption>Source: My code just a minute ago</figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/606522166166421534/667573207414341633/unknown.png" alt=""/><figcaption>Source: My code a minute after that</figcaption></figure>



<p>What you might notice about these two images is the insanely obvious: if someone were to buy one of these generic handhold consoles on Aliexpress and then sell it on Ebay they could pocket the difference in costs. This is called &#8216;retail arbitrage,&#8217; where retail is what we&#8217;re trading and arbitrage is the act of buying low and immediately selling high. It&#8217;s preferable to sell before you have to buy &#8211; which you can effectively do selling on these marketplaces.</p>



<p>You&#8217;ll notice that I&#8217;m lacking a corresponding Amazon screenshot &#8211; their Product Advertising API requires you to have 3 sales in a certain amount of time as an affiliate before you can have access to the API. D&#8217;oh! I&#8217;ve sent them a message saying I&#8217;m creating a shopping comparison engine &#8211; it might be unwise to say we&#8217;re propagating the arbitrage &#8216;problem.&#8217; Sometimes, people that buy an item on Ebay and receive a package wrapped up by Amazon Fulfillment will become irate they&#8217;ve been the victim of not knowing they can search more than one site, and they might kick up a customer service complaint&#8230;</p>



<p>Either way, there&#8217;s money to be made!</p>



<p>But, that&#8217;s not my idea. That idea&#8217;s been tried and done effectively by many, and you can google for more info. My idea is buried in those screenshots, above, and in my explanation of the Amazon part too &#8211; these are affiliate links. If someone were to visit Aliexpress or Ebay after clicking my link and place an order within a month or a few months, I get a little % kickback from that sale. </p>



<p>In the case of providing this as a service, the model would be that I create a beautiful and effective comparison tool to find the highest potential margins for search results or by the best possible margins in a given category and finding exact (or near-exact by text compare) title matches, then display them in easy-to-organize lists for arbitrageurs to peruse, click the links, buy a bulk order of many items or maybe just an item or two, and as I build my network &#8211; and community &#8211; of arbitrageurs, my income from the % of a % of each initial sale will exponentially increase above and beyond the potential returns from the actual arbitraging. </p>



<p>Retail arbitrage is fraught with potential pitfalls: from max. orders or max. sales, all the way to the customer service burden &#8211; and potential returns, restocking fees or concerns &#8211; it is easy to lose some or all of your profits in a second with retail arbitraging if you&#8217;re not careful. When building a service that provides instant comparisons for the potential arbitrageur &#8211; and a supportive, helpful community of arbitraging friends &#8211; we can ensure the overall success and growth of the operation.</p>



<p>Sunk costs?</p>



<p>Upkeep of servers, initial dev and MARKETING.</p>



<p>Potential upside?</p>



<p>We&#8217;d run the site for free. Everyone can come in and discuss the opportunities of Retail Arbitrage, and use the tool to their heart&#8217;s content. In return, our marketing efforts will reflect the fact that other arbitraging tools require a monthly or yearly subscription &#8211; putting ours leagues ahead of the competition.</p>



<p>Ebay Partner Network pays 1-6% per sale depending on geo, if the sale happens within 24hrs of clicking the link. Aliexpress up to 9%, and Amazon pays up to a walloping 10%! When someone wants to arbitrage again, they&#8217;d certainly want to find a new-and-improved arbitrage deal &#8211; they&#8217;d return to our platform, find a new killer deal, place another order and boombingbang more affiliate income!</p>



<p>NOW, for the win, let&#8217;s review some code.</p>



<p>First, after running npm install for the required packages, we&#8217;ll require them in the code:</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>let eBay = require('ebay-node-api')
var request = require('request')</code></pre>



<p>Next we&#8217;ll instantiate our eBay object, like so:</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>let ebay = new eBay({
    clientID: '',
    env: 'PRODUCTION', // optional default = 'PRODUCTION'
    headers:{ // optional
        'X-EBAY-C-MARKETPLACE-ID': 'EBAY_US' // For Great Britain https://www.ebay.co.uk/
    }
})</code></pre>



<p>Now, I found out that I could use eBay&#8217;s affiliate tools to build an affiliate URL using my account and campaign. Afterwards, I hijack the &amp;mpre= field and replace the item URL with my URL for any given item, to build a new-and-improved eBay aff link for any given URL.</p>



<p>For fun and profit, we set our eBay affiliate URL &#8216;template&#8217; as well as our hard-coded search term:</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>var template = 'http://rover.ebay.com/rover/1/706-53473-19255-0/1?ff3=4&amp;pub=5575480811&amp;toolid=10001&amp;campid=5338476385&amp;customid=&amp;mpre='
var search = '500in1 nes'</code></pre>



<p>In our ebaydo function, we search eBay products using the eBay node package and loop over the resulting json. The url for the item is parsed then encoded, and we create our affiliate URL by joining our template from above with this new encoded item&#8217;s url. </p>



<p>Voila! Paydirt!</p>



<p>We log to console the network, affiliate URL, title, and price object for fun and profit. If there&#8217;s an error, let&#8217;s also log the error! Debugging is fun, right?</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>function ebaydo(keywords) {

    ebay.findItemsByKeywords({
        keywords: keywords
    }).then((data) => {
        for (var item in data[0].searchResult[0].item) {
            url = encodeURIComponent(data[0].searchResult[0].item[item].viewItemURL[0])
            url = template + url
            console.log('ebay:')
            console.log('affiliate url: ' + url)
            console.log(data[0].searchResult[0].item[item].title[0])
            console.log(data[0].searchResult[0].item[item].sellingStatus[0].currentPrice[0])
            console.log(' ')
        }
    }, (error) => {
        console.log(error);
    });
}</code></pre>



<p>The ali function is more complicated. First, we&#8217;ll get and parse the current time into url-encoded string. Phew, that took a lot of Googling to figure out&#8230;</p>



<p>Next, we&#8217;ll encode our keywords. That probably means some handy %20s (spaces). Then, we load a list of products based on those keywords from Alibaba&#8217;s API, parse the result into json, loop over the products and save some useful info to vars for later. We&#8217;ll take note of the price, product url, image url (why not? Should have done this for eBay too! People can compare the images when finding their like products&#8230;) and product title. Next, we send some of these vars off to a separate function.</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>function ali(keywords) {
    var time = new Date();
    var time2 = (time.getHours().toString() + "%20" + time.getMinutes().toString() + "%20" + time.getSeconds().toString());
    keywords = encodeURIComponent(keywords)

    var url = "http://gw.api.alibaba.com/openapi/param2/2/portals.open/api.listPromotionProduct/76080?sort=volumeDown&amp;fields=salePrice,productTitle,volume,imageUrl,productUrl&amp;keywords=" + keywords;
    console.log('keywords?: ' + url);
    var responses = new Array();
    try {
        var result2 = request.get(url, function(e, r, result2) {
            var json = JSON.parse(result2)
            if (json.result != null) {
                for (var i in json.result.products) {
                    console.log(json.result.products[i]);
                    var price = json.result.products[i].salePrice;
                    var id = json.result.products[i].productUrl;
                    var img = json.result.products[i].imageUrl;
                    var title = json.result.products[i].productTitle;

                    
                    dosearchurl(id, title, img, price)
                }
            } 
        })
    } catch (e) {
        console.log('exception: ' + e.toString());
    }
}
</code></pre>



<p>In dosearchurl, this genius technique allows me to have the variables persistent over the next request.get call, which returns a promise, meaning that if we did request.get inside a for loop then tried to access our old variables (like title in this case, for example) it would only find the variable value at the state in the new point in time when the promise has resolved (ie. the request completes) &#8211; meaning all our results would output the same data as the for loop has completed and it executes the console.log code with the for loops final value, instead of each incremented value.</p>



<p>So, by taking the for loop and feeding it the variables in a different scope, the variables remain persistent even though there&#8217;s a time delay for the promise &#8211; and we can output the variables in their proper sequence, instead of only the final one over and over again.</p>



<p>In here, we load the product id on another alibaba api endpoint &#8211; this one to create an affiliate url for our product we&#8217;ve found. Then, we output to console all the juicey details about our potential arbitrageur&#8217;s opportunity &#8211; and our potential affiliate income.</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>function dosearchurl(id, title, img, price) {
    var url2 = "http://gw.api.alibaba.com/openapi/param2/2/portals.open/api.getPromotionLinks/76080?fields=promotionUrl&amp;trackingId=4632&amp;urls=" + id;
    var responses = new Array();
    try {
        var result3 = request.get(url2, function(e, r, result3) {

            var json = JSON.parse(result3)
            console.log('aliexpress:')
            console.log('title: ' + title.replace(/&lt;[^>]*>?/gm, ''))
            console.log('affiliate url: ' + json.result.promotionUrls[0].promotionUrl);
            console.log('img: ' + img)
            console.log('price: ' + price)
            console.log(' ')

        });

    } catch (e) {
        console.log('exception: ' + e.toString());
    }
}</code></pre>



<p>It&#8217;s a win-win-win: goldmoney for the arbitrageur who earns surebet money, paydirt for me as I gain a tiny percent of those sales over and over again, and of course it&#8217;s a good thing &#8211; big bucks &#8211; for the retail marketplace. Hooah!</p>



<p>I hope you&#8217;re as excited about my POC as I was creating it then describing it here. Someone will surely bet some time and effort and marketing chops to execute this vision.. will it be me?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Automated Crypto Trading Bot to Buy Pump and Dump Sentiment Signals from Twitter</title>
		<link>/2020/01/15/automated-crypto-trading-bot-to-buy-pump-and-dump-sentiment-signals-from-twitter/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 21:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Github]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=202</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View This Article in it&#8217;s Original Form on Jare.Cloud! Strategy We follow Twitter accounts we trust: exchanges, coins, Twitter crypto]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="/2020/01/15/automated-crypto-trading-bot-to-buy-pump-and-dump-sentiment-signals-from-twitter/">View This Article in it&#8217;s Original Form on Jare.Cloud</a>!</p>



<h2>Strategy</h2>



<ol><li>We follow Twitter accounts we trust: exchanges, coins, Twitter crypto influencers</li><li>We wait around until someone tweets a coin name or coin ticker</li><li>We measure the sentiment of the message: is it buy or sell?</li><li>On strong buys, or multiple instances of buys in a period of time, we execute a market buy order on Binance Spot</li><li>We wait around until our exits are hit</li><li>1 out of every 3-4 signals we act on the crowd will also act on&#8230; </li><li>&#8230;meaning there&#8217;s upwards potential for everyone</li><li>and we can net 100s 1000s% gains!</li></ol>



<p>In practice:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-10.png" alt="" class="wp-image-205" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-10.png 862w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-10-300x289.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-10-768x739.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 862px) 100vw, 862px" /><figcaption> <br></figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://media.discordapp.net/attachments/666371834102677565/667093503817547794/tempFileForShare_20200115-205117.jpg?width=340&amp;height=659" alt=""/></figure>



<h2>NLTK &amp; New Words</h2>



<p>The Python programming language has a package called Natural Language Tool Kit, or NLTK. Inside NLTK are lexicons that you can use to accomplish different goals &#8211; in our project, the Vader Lexicon is useful because we can rank all sorts of English words on a scale of -1 to 1 based on how strongly they express good or bad emotions. This is called &#8216;sentiment analysis.&#8217;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-8.png" alt="" class="wp-image-203" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-8.png 451w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-8-300x199.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-8-120x80.png 120w" sizes="(max-width: 451px) 100vw, 451px" /></figure>



<p>We add some new words to the mix.. given our very specific scenario.</p>



<h2>Weighted Twitter Accounts and Tiers</h2>



<p>Of the accounts in our followed list, we&#8217;ll have exchanges, coins and crypto influencers. Of these, exchanges have the highest amount of influence when they make an announcement about an alt, the coins themselves have a medium amount and the influencers have a variable but usually less amount.</p>



<p>We organize each account we follow (or simply have in a static list) into a list with corresponding ratios for how they affect our sentiment scores. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-9.png" alt="" class="wp-image-204" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-9.png 304w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-9-300x128.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 304px) 100vw, 304px" /></figure>



<h2>Parsing and Referencing All the Binance Spot Coins</h2>



<p>Here&#8217;s what Binance&#8217;s 24hr ticker endpoint looks like:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-11.png" alt="" class="wp-image-206" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-11.png 649w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-11-217x300.png 217w" sizes="(max-width: 649px) 100vw, 649px" /></figure>



<p>We loop through all these results, look for ones that end in BTC and then replace the BTC out of the symbol string &#8211; leaving the coin. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12-1024x172.png" alt="" class="wp-image-207" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12-1024x172.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12-300x50.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12-768x129.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12-1536x258.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12.png 1890w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>We now have a list of coins!</p>



<h2>Get Twitter Followed, 100 Recent Tweets Within Last Hour</h2>



<p>This is optional and I may replace the followed list with a flat and static file or coded list, but presently the bot will read the followed list and then loop through it, grabbing everyone&#8217;s 100 most recent tweets (and and/or and not retweets &#8211; optional) and then cycle through those to see which occurred in the last (given timeframe). These are the goldmoney&#8230; we save tweets we&#8217;ve previously indexed to an array so as to not re-index them.</p>



<h2>Find Potential Coinnames, Compare to Our Binance List and Tweeter List</h2>



<p>We split the text of the tweets up by &#8216; &#8216; (space) and &#8216;\n&#8217; (newline). We then look at each resulting word or hashtag, capitalize them and compare them (or $ + the word, like $MANA or $mana or mana or Mana) against our list of tickers from the Binance API. We also then compare against a list of tickers that correspond to specific Twitter accounts, in the event of something like the MANA tweet above that didn&#8217;t mention &#8216;MANA.&#8217; So we can tell that decentraland tweets are, usually, unless otherwise specified, for MANA.</p>



<h2>For High Sentiment Scores, Buy</h2>



<p>On Binance we market buy with a % of our holdings. The % is configurable, and depends on someone&#8217;s aversion to risk.</p>



<h2>For Repeat Occurrences, Buy Again</h2>



<p>If another one of our trusted tweeters tweets another signal confirming the same trend, we &#8216;double down&#8217; and buy another % of remaining balance worth of the coin.</p>



<h2>1% Trailing Take Profit</h2>



<p>If the price immediately drops 1%, we gracefully exit as a stoploss and count our losses. If the price goes up 2% and then down 1%, we exit the trade at 1% gains less fees. If, however, the coin goes up 10% 40% 100% before dropping 1% &#8211; as it might do with mass hysteria &#8211; then we laugh all the way to the bank! 1%, of course, is configurable.</p>



<h2>Rinse, Wash, Repeat</h2>



<p>Another signal another coin another potential 100%!</p>



<h2>Considerations</h2>



<p>We want to use a custom list of crypto influencers because most of the people calling out signals on twitter are actually doing so in their own vested interest &#8211; having posted a buy signal in their private Pump &amp; Dump discords, their private group buys up the coin and then &#8211; 5 minutes later &#8211; they all post signals to their twitters and bought &#8216;influencer&#8217; twitters as tweets that seem to double, triply, quadruply confirm each other. In reality, these folks are dumping by the time anyone else starts to buy in &#8211; meaning that you&#8217;d likely face losses if you used a twitter-wide sentiment analysis and automated trading tool. This is where all existing tools &#8211; including AI-driven ones &#8211; fail in this space, and why my bot has a considerable edge on the competition.</p>



<h2>Next Steps</h2>



<p>I&#8217;d like the bot to keep track of the win/lose rate and severity of wins/losses from specific tweeters, so that it can potentially modify the sentiment score by a previous success factor &#8211; so if someone was right about a buy signal 2/5 times it&#8217;s worth more than someone with 1/5 times. If someone is right 1/10 times, though, and their signal does 25x better than the first two in these examples &#8211; that one is worth considerably more.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-13-1024x629.png" alt="" class="wp-image-208" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-13-1024x629.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-13-300x184.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-13-768x471.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-13.png 1471w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>It&#8217;d be nice to incorporate a python django webserver like a hackathon starter so I can take advantage of their Twitter oauth2 sign-in scheme. This way I can potentially have accounts log in without supplying their own twitter API credentials &#8211; which require an application process now &#8211; and more accounts can work with my bot. This would increase the amount of actionable data and win/loss rates and severities that can be used to package tailored lists of tweeters to know.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Simple Terms: Risk-Free (Free Money!) Futures Trading by Leveraging Options Strategy</title>
		<link>/2020/01/14/in-simple-terms-risk-free-free-money-futures-trading-by-leveraging-options-strategy/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 01:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=176</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this content in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud! Introduction In short: using an options strategy, we can trade any]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1575/1*wQN_FGI4ff7a26rJBS45Og.jpeg" alt=""/></figure>



<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/14/in-simple-terms-risk-free-free-money-futures-trading-by-leveraging-options-strategy/">View this content in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<h1 id="4def">Introduction</h1>



<p>In short: using an options strategy, we can trade any sideways futures strategy with absolutely 0 risk. Price movements up, down, or sideways all yield profitable results. Markets go bullish, bearish, sideways or do a dance — you win no matter what!</p>



<p>Awhile ago, on my Hackernoon, I penned this technical article on&nbsp;<a href="https://hackernoon.com/risk-free-futures-market-making-by-hedging-long-straddle-options-pc1236bl" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Risk-Free Futures Market Making by Hedging Long Straddle Options</a>. In this article I will strive to deliver the points discussed in that first article to a less technical audience — who might be left scratching their heads.</p>



<p>What I mean by ‘sideways’ is that the futures strategy wants to earn the best it can when the markets are neither upwards (bullish) or downwards (bearish).</p>



<h1 id="3b67">Options Strategy</h1>



<p>Places like Deribit via&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/c1bc81c4789b?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Deribit</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/c1bc81c4789b?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Deribit</a>&nbsp;(yes, two separate accounts) and Binance’s JEX platform via&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/57600910a883?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Binance</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/590e572dc6e7?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Miko Ilas</a>&nbsp;allow you to buy and sell BTC (and other coins…) options. An option is a deriviative, meaning that it’s value is derived from the underlying asset but not necessarily correlated — there’s loads of other ‘deriviatives,’ like futures, and that’s why we can trade with so much more leverage on options and futures — they’re not representing the actual asset, but an ‘derived’ idea.</p>



<p>When you buy a call and a put you’re buying the right or ability to buy or sell (respectively) an underlying asset for the specified quantity and price sometime in the future. In European options, this point in the future is only on the day the options expire — or when they run out of time. Note that I’m not obligated to buy or sell — I simply have the right to, should I want to (or it makes financial sense). This means that (if I pay enough money, and someone is there to sell me this option) I should be able to buy the ABILITY to buy BTC for $1 sometime within the next month. That’s probably going to be a very lucrative deal, right? That’s why this option would be worth A LOT of money, and probably astronomically expensive to buy. The price at which you may buy or sell the underlying in the future is called ‘the strike.’</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/2118/1*_Ox5mK27cfvVSMM-VMvZhA.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>In the above screenshot, we see the calls and puts for BTC should the underlying index reach a price of $6750 on expiry or $6500 on expiry. Not that the price of the calls — the right to buy the asset — increases as the strike price decreases, while the cost of puts is decreasing along with it.</p>



<p>On the other side of potential prices for BTC on 24 Jan 2020 (the date the options expire, or end), we see the opposite effect.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/2128/1*90q1y2_UhEPPSN60AfcKew.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Calls are cheaper, puts are more expensive.</p>



<p>Anyways, to get to my point — if you buy both a call and a put with two different strike prices at the same expiry, then you can do so for&nbsp;<em>VERY&nbsp;</em>cheap.</p>



<p>What happens if the price remains around the same? The value of both the call and the put will reduce over time (as their distance to expiry is one of the things that gives them value — the uncertainty and possibility of volatility in this case means that they’re worth more now than they are tomorrow). Eventually, by expiry, they expire worthless.</p>



<p>What happens if the price goes up? The value of the put goes down, and the call goes up. The more the price moves upwards, the less the put is worth — all the way down to worthless — while the call increases in value&nbsp;<em>EXPONENTIALLY</em>.</p>



<p>What happens if the price goes down? The&nbsp;<em>OPPOSITE</em>. One $0 and the other gains value&nbsp;<em>EXPONENTIALLY</em>.</p>



<p>This options strategy is called a ‘long straddle,’ and it essentially means you’re betting on the price moving up or down by a large amount. It’s handy in markets you expect to be volatile — like stocks on days they report earnings or, much less likely in practice, you’re aware of someone’s unannounced merger and acquisition. What this also means is that cryptocurrencies — arguably the most volatile of the assets — allow an options trader to reap in the benefits of a highly volatile market.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1680/1*YnzM0Mta90lpGCtm-wzjKg.jpeg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>For instance, we know that Bitcoin’s mining yields will be half what they have been for awhile sometime in the not-so-distant future. We can surely bet that the price will either go up or down&nbsp;<em>drastically</em>&nbsp;in a short period of time. Take out a long straddle!</p>



<p>Anyways, the above article I wrote on Hackernoon goes on to say that you can use some smart guys math to guesstimate the potential future ‘fair value’ for these long straddles. There’s a few smart guys to choose from, I chose Black Scholes. Now we have a programmatic way to say ‘hey if price moves 5% then I can expect my long straddle to be worth x% more,’ their math model solves for x.</p>



<p>Now, where long straddles lose money is when the markets are sideways. I actually found this strategy when I was dreaming up ways to have less risk with my sideways market trading strategies — be they market makers, for instance, they lose money when the markets go up and down and they’re caught holding a bag of $$ that takes away all my yields.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/974/1*OeEhtZQFJ88ZqAvFzTlVjQ.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>These Market Makers make $$ when the markets are sideways, by earning on $ fees and $ spread. On Deribit,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/94b52ae5502e?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">BitMEX</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/b7ff9821c710?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bybit</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/724240b60d22?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bitfinex</a>&nbsp;Kraken and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/316a1a75d708?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinFLEX</a>&nbsp;they give you REBATES on fees you can earn when people trade against your orders. When you add liquidity to their exchanges, they split their earnings with you — sometimes 50/50!</p>



<p>This means that if I was to know that my max exposure is (how many positions of what sizes I might hold if the markets go one way or another) in $$ and if the market moves y% at 6x leverage, I then liquidate at y%. This is normally bad, but…</p>



<p>I can buy the exact (or almost exact) number puts/calls I need to make sure that if price goes up OR down by any % all the way up to liquidation % then I’m making money on my long straddle when I’m losing money on my Market Maker.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1096/1*f-8ikqYVWMFzCSgXAEthng.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>This applies to any strategy that generates yield when sideways, not just market makers. Say price goes up 5% in a day and my sideways strategy liquidates, and out of my puts and calls one of them is $0 and the other one increased in value&nbsp;<em>A WHOLE HECK OF A LOT.</em></p>



<p>The only way this doesn’t work is if your sideways strategy doesn’t earn more than what you lose when you hold onto the long straddles and their value goes down over time…</p>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization — where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;!!</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Benefits of Neomenia and Crypto Growth Hacker &#8211; Compound Your Crypto!</title>
		<link>/2019/12/23/benefits-of-neomenia-and-crypto-growth-hacker-compound-your-crypto/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 11:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=146</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Hi SteemIt! View this post in it&#8217;s original form on dunncreativess.github.io! View my other posts on Hackernoon. Yes I&#8217;m promoting]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hi SteemIt! View this post in it&#8217;s <a href="http://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/12/23/benefits-of-neomenia-and-crypto-growth-hacker-compound-your-crypto/">original form on dunncreativess.github.io</a>! View my <a href="https://hackernoon.com/@jare">other posts on Hackernoon.</a> Yes I&#8217;m promoting this post &#8211; I think I have some info you folks might appreciate!</p>



<p>With results among users ranging from 3-4%, and a total net returns for some users at 16-22+% over a few days, it looks as though Neomenia is here to make an improvement in people&#8217;s lives.</p>



<p>Trading on three exchanges simultaneously and hedging risk by altering strategies based on conditions on a given exchange, it looks like Crypto Growth Hacker is the one-stop-shop for crypto investment diversification.</p>



<p>Neomenia now supports trailing takeprofit, meaning the upwards potential of a good buy or sell has increased significantly with your configurable takeprofit. It also has a special feature where the stop size is reduced by the difference in price as a percent when it moves in the right direction, so that you can lock in your profits faster while having a larger stoploss in case sh#t hits the fan.</p>



<p>The win/lose ratio is 5:1&#8230; and <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/XBTUSD/FkIqJJcy-Introducing-Neomenia/">it backtested 10 000% on TradingView</a>.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s a price action observed in one spot confirmed in another confirmed again by a direcitonal indicator, and that&#8217;s all I&#8217;m allowed saying under NDA.. but if you want to know more, join the Neomenia chat on Telegram! <a href="https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A">https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-1024x408.png" alt="" class="wp-image-149" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-1024x408.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-300x119.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-768x306.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-1536x611.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1.png 1874w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Crypto Growth Hacker is indexing Bitmex, Deribit and Binance Futures now and using a complex market making strategy on the first two while employing Neomenia on the third. The result is a bot that&#8217;s incredibly resilient and doesn&#8217;t take very many hits that last too too long &#8211; and shows steady gains.</p>



<p>Want to know more? Join our Telegram! <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-148" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1.png 880w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1-300x163.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1-768x416.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 880px) 100vw, 880px" /></figure>



<p>What&#8217;s great about both offerings is the community. We have scores of new users &#8211; and scores of people supporting us through thick and thin &#8211; and that all starts with posts like these, to raise awareness.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4-498x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-150" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4-498x1024.png 498w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4-146x300.png 146w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4.png 622w" sizes="(max-width: 498px) 100vw, 498px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5-498x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-151" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5-498x1024.png 498w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5-146x300.png 146w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5.png 622w" sizes="(max-width: 498px) 100vw, 498px" /></figure>



<p>We&#8217;re helping each other, and helping ourselves. You&#8217;re more than welcome to join! We&#8217;d be happy to have you. Ask questions! Grow with us!</p>



<p>We also have attractive referral campaigns for those of you who have an audience or know the inner workings of the magical internet.. ask us how to get 10% of your referral&#8217;s profits, or a straight (and recurring.. ) fee!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-147" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1.png 899w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1-288x300.png 288w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1-768x800.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 899px) 100vw, 899px" /></figure>



<p><a href="https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A">Neomenia Telegram</a></p>



<p><a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">Crypto Growth Hacker Telegram</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Week of Neomenia LIVE Trading Binance Futures</title>
		<link>/2019/12/18/a-week-of-neomenia-live-trading-binance-futures/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=140</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Neomenia is currently running on 8 subscriber&#8217;s accounts, creating predictable yield in sideways or bullish or bearish markets! The strategy]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1024x635.png" alt="" class="wp-image-141" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1024x635.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-300x186.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-768x476.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1.png 1276w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Neomenia is currently running on 8 subscriber&#8217;s accounts, creating predictable yield in sideways or bullish or bearish markets! </p>



<p>The strategy itself is protected under NDA, but as much as I can say it finds price indication in one place confirms it in another then also confirms with directional indication. The result is magic!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1024x692.png" alt="" class="wp-image-142" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1024x692.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-300x203.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-768x519.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-120x80.png 120w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1.png 1224w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>I&#8217;ve created a web interface to launch bots on our own Google Cloud Compute account, taking the hassle and potential issues with configuring your own VPS with bot options straight off your shoulders.. and as it costs us a pretty penny a month, and saves you renting your own VPS, it&#8217;s basically a free VPS giveaway! Woot!</p>



<p>I&#8217;m writing an update predominantly to create FOMO, but the community results speak for themselves&#8230;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-143" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-1.png 626w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-1-300x124.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 626px) 100vw, 626px" /></figure>



<p>The price of the bot will increase from $49 or $59 (depending if you use our Binance Futures referral code) up to minimum $99 in the new year. The time to come onboard is now! Have no fear, our team and community moderators have your back through thick and thin.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn4.png" alt="" class="wp-image-144" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn4.png 606w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn4-300x137.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 606px) 100vw, 606px" /></figure>



<p>So &#8211; come on in, grab it while it&#8217;s cheap!</p>



<p>There are other monetization methods for people who otherwise have no access to futures, join <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> and check out the pin!</p>



<p>Interested in Neomenia? Join here! <a href="https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A">https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A</a></p>



<p><em>! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization – where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;!!</em>(<strong>Disclaimer</strong>:&nbsp;<em>The Author is the Chief Liquidity Officer at Coindex</em>) </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trade Smarter, Trade Together! Crypto Growth Hacker Crowdfunded Bot Tokens to Mint</title>
		<link>/2019/12/14/trade-smarter-trade-together-crypto-growth-hacker-crowdfunded-bot-tokens-to-mint/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 02:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=134</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;m offering my market maker bot one of two possible ways: 1. I provide you the source code and you]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1024x612.png" alt="" class="wp-image-135" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1024x612.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-300x179.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-768x459.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2.png 1452w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>I&#8217;m offering my market maker bot one of two possible ways: 1. I provide you the source code and you can configure your apikey and secret and review the code to make sure nothing malicious happens, on a profit-share scheme where you provide 40% of the earnings after every month &#8211; as confirmed by API. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3.png" alt="" class="wp-image-136" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3.png 1000w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-300x296.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-768x759.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></figure>



<p>2. I&#8217;m creating a dividend token for sale to the general public (including Americans) that I then pay monthly 70% of the profit (10% for me, 15% reinvested for compounding effect, 5% BNB holdings). The dividend trading fund would span multiple bots, with an initial spread of 25% Neomenia BTC 25% Neomenia ETH 25% Deribit arb + options BTC 25% Eth. The dividend token script I&#8217;m using doesn&#8217;t have voting, but we&#8217;ll vote on bot % holdings and bot strategies using an off-chain voting system enabled by etherscan reports on holding %, anything more than 5% gets a vote.</p>



<p>The benefits of option 1 is that you get to run one of my bots with a profit-share model, the benefits of option 2 are: a. if you&#8217;re an american citizen you can now kindof take part in leveraged futures trading, by way of the token. b. as our BNB accumulates, we pay less fees c. as our BNB accumulates, we get more % from our referrals d. the combined notional traded on Binance will allow us to further climb their fee ladder. You can also refer people to the crowdfunded bot, for every 100 tokens at $1 worth of Eth apiece minted you get 10 tokens. For every 100 tokens that a referral of your referral mints you get 5 tokens.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-imgur wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-imgur"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="imgur-embed-pub" lang="en" data-id="PBQZAB1"><a href="https://imgur.com/PBQZAB1">View post on imgur.com</a></blockquote><script async src="//s.imgur.com/min/embed.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<ol><li>Join Telegram https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</li><li>Fill out this form.</li><li>Send your Eth here: 0x9c33b574c8D013Ba501a897484E3b92a27A3FDB8</li><li>Fill the TXID in this form.</li><li>Tokens will be minted as often as possible, with the least often being once a month before dividends are paid.</li></ol>



<p>Form to fill: https://forms.gle/bDQmuUhQQ5FJPvgN6</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Our Next-Gen Crypto Trading Bot Neomenia Goes Live!</title>
		<link>/2019/12/05/our-next-gen-crypto-trading-bot-neomenia-goes-live/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 19:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=128</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Intro http://patbot1.duckdns.org/ Start: Sat Nov 30 2019 14:21:06 GMT+0000 (UTC) Now: Sun Dec 01 2019 05:17:39 GMT+0000 (UTC) BTC Notional]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>Intro</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-473x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-129" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-473x1024.png 473w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-139x300.png 139w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image.png 591w" sizes="(max-width: 473px) 100vw, 473px" /></figure>



<p>http://patbot1.duckdns.org/<br> Start: Sat Nov 30 2019 14:21:06 GMT+0000 (UTC)<br> Now: Sun Dec 01 2019 05:17:39 GMT+0000 (UTC)<br> BTC Notional traded recent memory: 38.44400000000188<br> Current position: -1.952<br> BTC % Delta: 31.89%<br> BTC % ROI / day projected: 51.22%<br> BTC % APR projected: 1.869e+4%</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-1-473x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-130" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-1-473x1024.png 473w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-1-139x300.png 139w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-1.png 591w" sizes="(max-width: 473px) 100vw, 473px" /></figure>



<h2>Steps to Reproduce</h2>



<p>Step 1. Join our Telegram https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A<br> Step 2. Create a net-new Binance account, and enable futures, and create an api key after enabling futures http://www.binance.com/en/register?ref=27039658, You&#8217;re allowed to have as many Binance accounts as you like, while only verifying one &#8211; the max daily withdrawal on an unverified account is still huge<br> Step 3: Sent the subscription fee to our wallet 0x55FC78F760fBeb15A8a14ce2B8e9DCfA4CE0f966<br> Step 4: Enter your transaction ID on this form.<br> Step 5: And the last 6 characters of your API key.<br> Step 6: The team will manually add you to the bot&#8217;s license, and send you the executable file and other directions.<br> Step 7: Run the appropriate exports or setx&#8217;s from within env.sh. DO NOT simply run env.sh, it won&#8217;t work, copy and paste the commands into a terminal/cmd window. On windows, open a net new cmd when finished.<br> Step 8: Run the executable for app for BTCUSDT, eth for ETHUSDT, and balance for a balance output graph like the ones you&#8217;re used to seeing.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-2-473x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-131" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-2-473x1024.png 473w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-2-139x300.png 139w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-2.png 591w" sizes="(max-width: 473px) 100vw, 473px" /></figure>



<h2>Neomenia FAQs</h2>



<h1>FAQ 1: Settings</h1>



<p>variables with ‘eth’ prepended are the same, for the ethusdt bot<br></p>



<p>delaybetweenorder, higher for more delay before a new limit order</p>



<p>takeProfit, in % what gains to lock in before market out</p>



<p>stopLoss, in % what losses to accept before market out</p>



<p>tgUser, your Telegram username for use with the Telegram bot</p>



<p>key, APIkey</p>



<p>secret, APIsecret<br></p>



<p>&#8212;-<br></p>



<p>Note that the key and secret are never communicated anywhere off the local machine, except in signed requests to the exchange (which hide your details). Wireshark sniffing can confirm this.<br></p>



<p>&#8212;-<br></p>



<p>site, the http or https address where your server is located. You can google curl ipify to find your address if you’re in a headless server, or google ‘what is my ip’ if you have an interface. You can set up DNS forwarding on duckdns.org or register your own spiffy shiny new domain if you like.</p>



<p>poirt, which port to run the balance server on. Use 80 for http 443 for https (which isn’t enabled anyhow) or a higher number like 8080 if you’re having permissions issues.</p>



<p>maxFreePerc, what maximum % of the wallet will be used before stopping ordering in the same direction. Note this doesn’t count existing limit orders, which could max our margin if your delay is too small.</p>



<p>orderSizeMult, for a $50 USDT account use 5, for $250 use 1, for $500 use 0.5. Etc.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-3-1024x549.png" alt="" class="wp-image-132" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-3-1024x549.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-3-300x161.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-3-768x412.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-3.png 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2>FAQ 2: Legal Mumbo Jumbo</h2>



<p>In no way are our team or any affiliated member responsible for any gains or losses you might experience. Previous action is no indication implied or assured of future performance. Risk only what you can afford to lose. This bot does not constitute financial advice by any means, and is meant to be used in an educational, communal, and fun format.</p>



<h2>Sign Up Now!</h2>



<p><a href="https://forms.gle/hWa7uzZFg9nD1khg8">https://forms.gle/hWa7uzZFg9nD1khg8</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Skip the SSL w/ Serverless Telegram Bot via Now.js</title>
		<link>/2019/11/24/skip-the-ssl-w-serverless-telegram-bot-via-now-js/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=109</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[See this article in it&#8217;s original form on dunncreativess.github.io! Try this bot on Telegram! https://t.me/JareBotBot! Sponsor my opensource efforts on]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/24/skip-the-ssl-w-serverless-telegram-bot-via-now-js/">See this article in it&#8217;s original form on dunncreativess.github.io!</a></p>



<p>Try this bot on Telegram! <a href="https://t.me/JareBotBot">https://t.me/JareBotBot</a>!</p>



<p><a href="https://github.com/sponsors/dunncreativess">Sponsor my opensource efforts on GitHub</a>!</p>



<p>Note: these directions come without much conversation, let the hacking begin!</p>



<p>Set up a Bot with @BotFather<br> </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-34.png" alt="" class="wp-image-110" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-34.png 641w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-34-289x300.png 289w" sizes="(max-width: 641px) 100vw, 641px" /></figure>



<p>Create a package.json</p>



<p><code>{<br>   "name": "tg-bot-now",<br>   "version": "0.2.0",<br>   "description": "A sample Telegram bot via now.js",<br>   "main": "app.js",<br>   "scripts": {<br>     "start": "node app.js"<br>   },<br>   "dependencies": {<br>     "axios": "<em>",     "body-parser": "</em>",<br>     "express": "*",<br>     "request": "^2.88.0",<br>     "requests": "^0.3.0"<br>   },<br>   "license": "MIT"<br> }</code></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-35.png" alt="" class="wp-image-111" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-35.png 827w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-35-300x150.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-35-768x384.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 827px) 100vw, 827px" /></figure>



<p>Create a now.json</p>



<p><code>{<br>   "version": 2,<br>   "builds": [<br>     { "src": "app.js", "use": "@now/node-server" }<br>   ],<br>   "routes": [<br>     { "src": "/(.*)", "dest": "app.js" }<br>   ]<br> }</code></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-36.png" alt="" class="wp-image-112" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-36.png 606w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-36-300x139.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 606px) 100vw, 606px" /></figure>



<p>Create an app.js</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>var express = require("express");
 var app = express();
 var request = require('request');
 var bodyParser = require("body-parser");
 const axios = require("axios");
 app.use(bodyParser.json());
 app.use(
     bodyParser.urlencoded({
         extended: true
     })
 );
 console.log("run"); 
function sendMessage(url, message, reply, res) {
axios.post(url, {
    chat_id: message.chat.id,
    text: reply
}).then(response => {
    console.log("Message posted");
    res.end("ok");
}).catch(error => {
    console.log(error);
});
}
 app.get('/', function(req, res) {
     res.send('hello');
 })
 var bots = &#91;"http://patbot1.duckdns.org/update", "http://coindexbot.duckdns.org:8080/update"]
 app.post("/startbot", function(req, res) {
     console.log("startbot");
     const {
         message
     } = req.body;
     let reply = "Welcome to Jare's bot bot";
     if (message.text != undefined) {
         if (message.text.toLowerCase().indexOf("statusupdate") != -1) {
             reply = ""
             for (var b in bots) {
 r = request.get(bots&#91;b], function(e, r, d) {

                j = JSON.parse(d)
                start = j.btc&#91;0]&#91;0]
                btc = j.btc&#91;j.btc.length - 1]&#91;1]
                end = j.btc&#91;j.btc.length - 1]&#91;0]
                diff = end - start
                var s = diff / 1000
                var m = s / 60
                var h = m / 60
                var d = h / 24
                var y = d / 365
                var apr = (j.btc&#91;j.btc.length - 1]&#91;1] - j.btc&#91;0]&#91;1]) / y
                reply += r.request.uri.href.substring(0, r.request.uri.href.length - 7) + '\n'
                reply += "Start: " + new Date(start) + '\n'
                reply += "Now: " + new Date(end) + "\n"
                reply += "BTC Notional traded recent memory: " + j.qty + "\n"
                reply += "Current position: " + j.pos + "\n"
                reply += "BTC % Delta: " + btc.toPrecision(4) + '%\n'
                reply += "BTC % ROI / day projected: " + (apr / 365).toPrecision(4) + '%\n'
                reply += "BTC % APR projected: " + (apr).toPrecision(4) + '%\n\n'
            })
        }
        setTimeout(function() {
            sendMessage(telegram_url, message, reply, res);
        }, 2000);
    } else {
        res.end("ok");
    }
}
});
 let telegram_url = "https://api.telegram.org/bot" + process.env.key + "/sendMessage";
 app.listen(8000, () => console.log("Telegram bot is listening on port 8000!"));</code></pre>



<p>Note: it&#8217;s important to send a res.end in every case, or else your bot will get hung up on old messages it couldn&#8217;t process and no res.end was sent &#8211; putting it in a forever loop of never sending a response!</p>



<p>set your env key</p>



<p><code>export key="whateverbotfathergaveyou"</code></p>



<p>npm i</p>



<p><code>npm i</code></p>



<p>install now</p>



<p><code>npm i -g now</code></p>



<p>run now</p>



<p><code>now</code></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-37.png" alt="" class="wp-image-113" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-37.png 902w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-37-300x58.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-37-768x148.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 902px) 100vw, 902px" /></figure>



<p>Register your POST callback wtih Telegram&#8217;s grandmasters</p>



<p><code>curl -F "url=https://URL_FROM_NOW/startbot" https://api.telegram.org/botYOUR_TELEGRAM_API_TOKEN/setWebhook</code></p>



<p>Congrats!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-38.png" alt="" class="wp-image-114" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-38.png 655w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-38-300x298.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-38-150x150.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 655px) 100vw, 655px" /></figure>



<p><a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">Join Us on Telegram</a></p>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization – where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;!!</em></p>



<p>(<strong>Disclaimer</strong>:&nbsp;<em>The Author is the Chief Liquidity Officer at Coindex</em>)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Risk-Free Futures Market Making by Hedging Long Straddle Options</title>
		<link>/2019/11/22/risk-free-futures-market-making-by-hedging-long-straddle-options/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 08:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coindex]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=100</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[See This Article in It&#8217;s Original Form on dunncreativess.github.io! Want to See And Play With The Code? Here it Is]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="http://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/22/risk-free-futures-market-making-by-hedging-long-straddle-options/">See This Article in It&#8217;s Original Form on dunncreativess.github.io!</a></p>



<p><a href="https://github.com/DunnCreativeSS/CryptoFuturesHedgingWithBlackScholesOptions">Want to See And Play With The Code? Here it Is On Github! </a></p>



<p><a href="https://github.com/sponsors/dunncreativess">Sponsor Me On Github!</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-30-1024x130.png" alt="" class="wp-image-101" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-30-1024x130.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-30-300x38.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-30-768x97.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-30.png 1255w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>In the quantitative finance world, there are some holy grails: you can decrease the risk of an exposed position generally by doing something in the opposite direction.</p>



<p>In the simplest form, we can both long and short in two opposite positions on exchanges that use the long-short model like OkEx. In doing so, a price movement up or down will have the exact same effect on your position &#8211; where you&#8217;re losing fees and only fees.</p>



<p>In reality, that&#8217;s no good because we don&#8217;t want to be losing on every trade <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/1f642.png" alt="🙂" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>



<p>What I&#8217;ve decided to try my hand at is something called a &#8216;long straddle.&#8217; This was mentioned during my interview with Coindex Labs a long time ago &#8211; but basically, if you buy a put option and buy a call option &#8216;out of the money&#8217; it&#8217;s relatively cheap &#8211; if the price doesn&#8217;t move at all, they both expire worthless. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-31.png" alt="" class="wp-image-102" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-31.png 741w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-31-300x178.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 741px) 100vw, 741px" /></figure>



<p>But: if the price increases OR decreases a significant amount, one of those options expires in the money.. meaning it gianed value from potentially nothing into potentially something!</p>



<p>What this means is that, while the market maker is performing within specifications and earning money from low price volatility and volumes on the bid/ask, these options can expire worthless and our income from market making pays for the expired options &#8211; and then more!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32-1024x161.png" alt="" class="wp-image-103" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32-1024x161.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32-300x47.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32-768x121.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32-1536x241.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-32.png 1649w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>If the market moves too much in one direction, we&#8217;re risking liquidating our funds if we hold market making positions that go sour.</p>



<p>If this happens &#8211; one of our long straddle options expires &#8216;in the money&#8217; enough for us to cover our losses. What this means is risk-free trading &#8211; so long as the assumption holds true that the market making earns more than the cost of the options.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-33-1024x108.png" alt="" class="wp-image-104" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-33-1024x108.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-33-300x32.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-33-768x81.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-33.png 1247w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>In my code, we loop through all the expiries and all the strikes for all the options, and then find the one whose ratio of cost vs. profits for a 15% movement in price (which is 100% liquidated at 6.66x leverage) yields the minimum threshold we need to cover $15 000 in exposed futures ($99 900 notional). In our example output, the Dec 6 options straddle for $6250 put and $9750 call would cost a total of 0.017 BTC for both the long put and long call, and each would earn $342 profit if the underlying price moved 15% and all else remained the same. This means that spending 0.54 BTC would completely cover the risk of liquidating 2 BTC exposed at 6.66x leverage &#8211; at least until implied volatilities change significantly or time value declines as we approach expiry! When these situations occur, the hedging bot would just create new orders in real-time to hedge the risk. Hooah!</p>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization – where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;!!</em></p>



<p>(<strong>Disclaimer</strong>:&nbsp;<em>The Author is the Chief Liquidity Officer at Coindex</em>) </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Verdict is In: I&#8217;ve Got a Vested Stake of a Hedgefund! Best News? You Can Be, Too!</title>
		<link>/2019/11/21/the-verdict-is-in-ive-got-a-vested-stake-of-a-hedgefund-best-news-you-can-be-too/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 20:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coindex]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=95</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View This Article in it&#8217;s Original Form on dunncreativess.github.io! Today Coindex Lab&#8217;s CEO had a sitdown with a capital markets]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/11/21/the-verdict-is-in-ive-got-a-vested-stake-of-a-hedgefund-best-news-you-can-be-too/">View This Article in it&#8217;s Original Form on dunncreativess.github.io!</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://scontent.fyhz1-1.fna.fbcdn.net/v/t1.15752-9/76702405_2533273790105081_4583222162055233536_n.png?_nc_cat=108&amp;_nc_ohc=4Vbyg5W14HwAQkZ8wLiECu10yKgvGxixDMyWU4xvTgW1tmhU24esQj0Cg&amp;_nc_ht=scontent.fyhz1-1.fna&amp;oh=418a76a2031e74a257d7ae938573091e&amp;oe=5E405713" alt=""/><figcaption><br></figcaption></figure>



<p>Today Coindex Lab&#8217;s CEO had a sitdown with a capital markets guy and then later Two Sigma Ventures &#8211; with the goal of making Coindex a fighting force in quantitative finance.</p>



<p>The good news? Capital markets guy wanted us to start a hedgefund. A random guy from the other coast approached the conversation out of nowhere asking to be connected.</p>



<p>Later, the conversation with TSV yielded &#8216;Good news and bad news:&#8217;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-28.png" alt="" class="wp-image-96" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-28.png 1011w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-28-300x229.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-28-768x587.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1011px) 100vw, 1011px" /></figure>



<p>So we have two &#8211; maybe three! &#8211; pledges for funds when we figure out the legalize of doing so.</p>



<p>The good news for me is that I get both equity share and a cut of the vig (gangster term for the take).</p>



<p>The good news for my readers is that we have the opportunity to get capital into Coindex at ground floor, and start earning on crypto and traditional markets with our patented edge over any given set of market conditions.</p>



<p>You might ask yourself, then ask me, &#8216;but I&#8217;m not a high net worth individual &#8211; how can I contribute to a hedgefund?&#8217;</p>



<p>Well, in keeping with crypto tradition&#8230;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-29.png" alt="" class="wp-image-97" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-29.png 938w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-29-300x137.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/11/image-29-768x350.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 938px) 100vw, 938px" /></figure>



<p>We very well might crowdfund in an STO!</p>



<p>While this is still a gleam in the back of my eye and ultimately a rumor &#8211; what this means is that you &#8211; your friends, coworkers, acquaintances, grandma &#8211; can capitalize on <strong><a href="https://hackernoon.com/coindex-labs-novel-search-applied-via-evolutionary-ai-creating-a-money-making-machine-n62j2gei">our value proposition</a></strong>, and learn from my years of experience <a href="https://hackernoon.com/what-ive-learned-from-years-of-arbitrage-and-market-making-975w38rs"><strong>making markets and doing arbitrage trading</strong></a> and <strong><a href="https://hackernoon.com/porting-a-bot-to-binance-futures-market-making-competition-6v6a31qh">derive alphas from our bots</a></strong>!</p>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization – where we’re setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the world’s greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p>R<em>emember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em> http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em> !!</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
