<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Bots &#8211; jare.cloud</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/bots/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Jare&#039;s Cloud</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 07:42:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-CA</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.3.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Now ANYONE can Make Money Online with My FREE Retail Arbitrage Tool!</title>
		<link>/2020/01/25/now-anyone-can-make-money-online-with-my-free-retail-arbitrage-tool/</link>
				<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 07:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insanely Marketable Business Ideas]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=455</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[For anyone who doesn&#8217;t know, #Retail #Arbitrage is #buying #low and #selling #high from different retail outlets or #platforms. I]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>For anyone who doesn&#8217;t know, #Retail #Arbitrage is #buying #low and #selling #high from different retail outlets or #platforms. I created an #aggregator that gets items via search and compares them for similar titles and shows the % and $ #gains, from #aliexpress to #ebay, for the top 300 results on each site. </p>



<p>This tool is #free! </p>



<p>Tool: <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://arb.jare.cloud/" target="_blank">http://arb.jare.cloud/</a></p>



<p>Backstory: <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/16/amazon-ebay-aliexpress-retail-arbitrage-as-a-service/" target="_blank">https://jare.cloud/2020/01/16/amazon-ebay-aliexpress-retail-arbitrage-as-a-service/</a> </p>



<p>Youtube of it in development: <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f7Pj7q3hXsU" target="_blank">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f7Pj7q3hXsU</a> </p>



<p>Opensource Github repository: <a href="https://github.com/DunnCreativeSS/arb.jare.cloud">https://github.com/DunnCreativeSS/arb.jare.cloud</a></p>



<h1>arb.jare.cloud</h1>



<p><a href="http://arb.jare.cloud/">http://arb.jare.cloud/</a></p>



<h2><a href="https://github.com/DunnCreativeSS/arb.jare.cloud#changelog"></a>Changelog:</h2>



<p>0.01.01: initial commit. Live. Works with Aliexpress and Ebay. Earns thru affiliate $.</p>



<p>0.01.02: Changed the logic so that ebay and ali objects are unique to sessions. This increases performance if there is more than one concurrent user from an unusable platform.</p>



<p>0.01.03: Added Git link to result page. Added Google Analytics tracking.</p>



<h2><a href="https://github.com/DunnCreativeSS/arb.jare.cloud#todo"></a>Todo:</h2>



<ol><li>Get Amazon affiliate sales.</li><li>Implement Amazon affiliate API for third aggregate source.</li></ol>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-64-1024x431.png" alt="" class="wp-image-457" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-64-1024x431.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-64-300x126.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-64-768x324.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-64-1536x647.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-64.png 1901w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2>The Pitch</h2>



<p>You can secure surebet, arbitrage income by searching whatever floats your boat and seeing how similar the titles match for these goods on Ebay and Aliexpress, For free! See those links there? Those are affiliate links &#8211; meaning that if you do find a way to earn big money buying low and selling high from one marketplace to another, I earn a percent of those sales. Want to sell hundreds of these items? Buy hundreds, then! Want to wait until your sale has gone through on Ebay, then buy the item with the proceeds and ship it directly to the customer? Chances are you&#8217;ll be doing it through my same referral link.. and we all win!</p>



<h2>Next Steps</h2>



<p>I want to include Amazon Affiliate API results to compare against these two. There&#8217;s a chance for more ways for people to arbitrage &#8211; buy on ebay, sell on Amazon? Alas, Amazon&#8217;s Affiliate API is only open for business after you sell three items on their affiliate platform. Boo!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-65-1024x632.png" alt="" class="wp-image-458" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-65-1024x632.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-65-300x185.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-65-768x474.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-65.png 1334w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2>How Does It Compare?</h2>



<p>Other retail arbitrage tools will charge you hundreds a month for membership. They also have fancy tools to help you bulk import selections, but my revenue model comes from those little affiliate links &#8211; so the bulk import tools aren&#8217;t necessarily conducive. Some people might prefer paying a subscription to get access to these premium tools &#8211; others would prefer cut costs and use a free tool to find their sure-fire winning merchandise!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Build a Winning Tool for Sentiment Analysis of Twitter Data</title>
		<link>/2020/01/22/how-to-build-a-winning-tool-for-sentiment-analysis-of-twitter-data/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coindex]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=368</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[See this post in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud! Today, we&#8217;ll summarize my continued efforts to build a sentiment analysis]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/22/how-to-build-a-winning-tool-for-sentiment-analysis-of-twitter-data/">See this post in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<p>Today, we&#8217;ll summarize my continued efforts to build a sentiment analysis tool. This tool is using the Twitter API to consume 97 different Twitter handles, that provide Crypto trading signals. This method can easily be applied to traditional markets &#8211; effectively capitalizing on new and highly lucrative means for trading stocks online. We&#8217;ll be reviewing the opportunities to add a neuro evolutionary AI to our bot. You can review the <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/automated-crypto-trading-bot-to-buy-pump-and-dump-sentiment-signals-from-twitter/">first iteration of this series on Twitter sentiment bots here</a> on my blog.</p>



<p>When it comes to classical issues facing sentiment analysis applications, it&#8217;s important to consider how algorithms work. If we&#8217;re using a Natural Language Processing tool to rank the individual words in a phrase based on positive, neutral and negative sentiment, wouldn&#8217;t a product review like &#8216;All these wonderful new features! Although none of them work!&#8217; confuse the machine? Words like &#8216;none&#8217; are the true sentiment &#8211; being negative &#8211; but the overall feeling the programming gets from the message involve words like &#8216;wonderful&#8217; &#8216;new&#8217; &#8216;work.&#8217; This would yield a false positive in the ranking and scoring of phrases. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-14-1024x329.png" alt="" class="wp-image-370" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-14-1024x329.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-14-300x96.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-14-768x247.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/1-14.png 1110w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>What we need is a way for the computer to overcome this sarcasm in the tweets. Certain <a href="https://medium.com/dair-ai/detecting-sarcasm-with-deep-convolutional-neural-networks-4a0657f79e80">AIs are capable of establishing context</a> by ranking sentiment, emotion and personality. We&#8217;ll then apply this when we analyze Twitter data. As <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jarettdunn/">Chief Liquidity Officer of Coindex Labs</a>, I have access to a new and novel way to train datasets and apply resulting genomes on configurations &#8211; using an AI that&#8217;s naturally resilient to over-fitting.</p>



<p> AI has other advantages when it comes to sentiment analysis, like identifying unique opinions that may otherwise get re-hashed, re-worded, and delivered in a separate &#8216;original content&#8217; tweet. This doesn&#8217;t really apply as much in our trading bot, as we&#8217;re limiting our input tweets to those 97 Twitter accounts, but with a larger dataset this is critical. To identify the true emotion of the Internet at large, we&#8217;d need a way to filter out people (and even computers) with accounts that are used to artificially manipulate people&#8217;s sentiment bots. It&#8217;s &#8216;a feint within a feint within a feint,&#8217; as Muad&#8217;Dib would have said!</p>



<p>Once we&#8217;ve created our new model and use it to weed out the bad apples, our analysis of sentiment will be far more effective. As far as sentiment scores go, this tweet that my Twitter bot picks up on is ahead of the bell curve &#8211; but, on manual inspection, it looks as though it&#8217;s a joke rather than actual sentiment one way or another.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-58.png" alt="" class="wp-image-369" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-58.png 815w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-58-300x99.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-58-768x253.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 815px) 100vw, 815px" /></figure>



<p>Entries like these should be ignored in the final product. I&#8217;ve toyed with the idea of human intervention before acting on a given signal, but the delays involved would mean that the average trader would miss 70% of the swing. Ideally, the bot would act on the &#8216;good&#8217; signals within a matter of seconds or minutes &#8211; beating the overall shift in the markets when others pick up on the sentiment, before everyone exits. This is how the goldmoney is made.</p>



<p>This is what a profitable tweet looks like, and currently our win/lose ratio is far higher than 50% &#8211; combined with a creative trailing takeprofit, we can establish an edge on the market:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-59-1024x190.png" alt="" class="wp-image-372" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-59-1024x190.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-59-300x56.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-59-768x143.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-59.png 1361w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://media.discordapp.net/attachments/666371834102677565/667705444596187136/SmartSelect_20200117-122805_TabTrader.jpg?width=367&amp;height=658" alt=""/></figure>



<p>The next steps are to build out the AI&#8217;s training set with loads of tweets to run analysis on. These will then serve as a benchmark with which to apply to forward-testing data with live, real incoming tweets based on our followed list. Then, our evolutionary part of the neuro evolutionary AI will create competing sets of genomes with the different input variables, and the best-performing genome will become the champion set that runs the live trader. The next generation of genomes will then (likely, by and large) perform better vs the previous generation, and a new champion might be selected. </p>



<p>Are you more interested in how to automagically grow your Twitter following? Check out this article I wrote on <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/21/7-days-creating-a-twitter-growth-service/">consuming the Twitter API to hack your account&#8217;s growth</a>! All in all, we have a clear plan for how our analysis of Twitter for fun &amp; profit will continue to become more sophisticated and the win/lose ratio will increase significantly. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>7 Days Creating a Twitter Growth Service</title>
		<link>/2020/01/21/7-days-creating-a-twitter-growth-service/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 17:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brave]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=234</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[See this post in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud! Interested in a way to utilize Crypto Pump n Dump tweets]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/21/7-days-creating-a-twitter-growth-service/">See this post in it&#8217;s original form on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<p>Interested in a way to utilize Crypto Pump n Dump tweets &#8211; for fun &amp; profit? <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/automated-crypto-trading-bot-to-buy-pump-and-dump-sentiment-signals-from-twitter/">Check out this article I wrote on making mad stacks on Twitter sentiment</a>!</p>



<h2>Day 1</h2>



<p>I had a thought: if some of my traffic comes from Twitter to Medium and my blog, wouldn&#8217;t I want to maximize this &#8211; in a hands-free fashion? I&#8217;ve done this before &#8211; some of my accounts had 5k+ followers in a few months. I had bought a Google sheets templated sheet doc with Twitter integrations, and bam it flew. I later created a Github repo for a hackathon starter fork where I put in all these juicey follow, retweet, favorite logics into a prettier UI.</p>



<p>The benefit of the hackathon starter is that I can login via oauth &#8211; meaning the app has api keys, but the user does not. We&#8217;re all used to oauth login &#8211; do you want to login using gmail/facebook/twitter? Redirect to platform, redirect to site, success!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-21.png" alt="" class="wp-image-236" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-21.png 876w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-21-300x245.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-21-768x627.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 876px) 100vw, 876px" /></figure>



<p>I resurrected my gsheet today and started the magic. I made some edits to the code: specifically we want to follow, retweet and favorite. Hooah!</p>



<p>Let&#8217;s set our benchmark&#8230;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-20-1024x303.png" alt="" class="wp-image-235" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-20-1024x303.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-20-300x89.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-20-768x227.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-20.png 1032w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<h2>Day 2</h2>



<p>Well, we have some initial results! Twitter app on my phone has been blowing up. Let&#8217;s analyze the results so far&#8230;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-22.png" alt="" class="wp-image-237" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-22.png 1009w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-22-300x98.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-22-768x250.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1009px) 100vw, 1009px" /></figure>



<p>We&#8217;ve gained 13 followers in 24 hours! That might not sound like much, but it&#8217;s a full 10.8% increase over where we were. Even better than that, the amount of followers vs the amount of people I&#8217;ve followed &#8211; an important metric on Twitter &#8211; has actually increased! </p>



<p>I did notice that the UI on Twitter wouldn&#8217;t let me follow people. This is dangerous, as if we try to follow too many people and get errors because our account is limited, Twitter may ban the account. We remove the follow directives, and increase retweets and likes.</p>



<h2>Day 3</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-23-1024x364.png" alt="" class="wp-image-238" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-23-1024x364.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-23-300x107.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-23-768x273.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-23.png 1048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Wow! A further 12% increase in followers! Our ratio increased again, too. That&#8217;s fantastic news&#8230; I&#8217;m greedy now, and so I&#8217;m going to increase the retweets and favorites from one per search term per hour up to 3. This should accelerate this monster&#8230; let&#8217;s wait and find out!</p>



<p>UPDATE: 3/4 the way through Day 3, let&#8217;s take a look at results. Just because I hate waiting. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-24.png" alt="" class="wp-image-239" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-24.png 977w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-24-300x119.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-24-768x306.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 977px) 100vw, 977px" /></figure>



<p>Well, that strategy appears to be working! No longer is my account limited, and also my followers increased a further 12% on top of the last 12% and 10% &#8211; an increase in rate. When we check in in another 6ish hours we&#8217;ll hopefully see that the data for the 18th reflect a massive increase.</p>



<p>What&#8217;s even better is that my follower vs followed ratio is increasing SIGNIFICANTLY. Because I&#8217;m no longer following people using the bot &#8211; although I did some manually, messing up stats &#8211; this ratio is now EXPLODING. </p>



<p>Twitter limits your ability to follow new people after you follow 5k, and if this ratio is too too deep then everyone will assume you&#8217;re digging for followers and your rate of follow backs will decrease. D&#8217;oh!</p>



<h2>Day 4</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-33-1024x761.png" alt="" class="wp-image-295" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-33-1024x761.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-33-300x223.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-33-768x571.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-33.png 1045w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption>Twitter: Free Money</figcaption></figure>



<p>Social traffic and engagements are literally free money if you monetize your visitors in any way, or put a dollar value on them.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-48-1024x249.png" alt="" class="wp-image-339" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-48-1024x249.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-48-300x73.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-48-768x187.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-48.png 1050w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Plus &#8211; we&#8217;ve seen a massive increase in both followers and the ratio! Booya!</p>



<h2>Day 5</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-49-1024x259.png" alt="" class="wp-image-340" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-49-1024x259.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-49-300x76.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-49-768x194.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-49.png 1035w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>The followers and ratio continue their upwards trend, although slowing down&#8230;</p>



<h2>Day 6</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-50-1024x285.png" alt="" class="wp-image-341" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-50-1024x285.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-50-300x84.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-50-768x214.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-50.png 1041w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Oh! I know why my followed is still trending up. My code had a hard-coded &#8216;followback&#8217; feature. Let&#8217;s turn that off!</p>



<h2>Day 7</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51-1024x680.png" alt="" class="wp-image-342" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51-1024x680.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51-300x199.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51-768x510.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51-120x80.png 120w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-51.png 1035w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Looking good&#8230;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-52.png" alt="" class="wp-image-343" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-52.png 1022w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-52-300x97.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-52-768x248.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1022px) 100vw, 1022px" /></figure>



<p>We&#8217;ve now accomplished the 2nd-highest daily increase in % follower/followed ratio. Hooah!</p>



<p>That concludes our 7-day adventure into automating Twitter engagements, for fun and profit. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-53.png" alt="" class="wp-image-344" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-53.png 337w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-53-300x87.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 337px) 100vw, 337px" /></figure>



<p>We&#8217;ve seen an 85% increase &#8211; nearly double! In followers over 7 days, and 30% increase in follower/followed ratio. These are huge numbers, indicative of a healthy and growing Twitter following.</p>



<p><a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/better-web-brave-rewards-your-content-make-money-monetizing-twitter/">Learn how to monetize your new Twitter following with Brave Browser and BAT tokens</a>! Better yet? It blocks all third-party ads! AND protects your privacy!</p>



<h2>A Plug (or Two)</h2>



<p>Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<p>Want to learn about new articles in tech and being a madman? Subscribe to my mailing list here:&nbsp;<a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL">http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</a> </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>What are trade bots? Robot traders explained!</title>
		<link>/2020/01/17/what-are-trade-bots-robot-traders-explained/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 06:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=226</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Read this article in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud! Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/17/what-are-trade-bots-robot-traders-explained/">Read this article in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<p> Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<h2>Introduction</h2>



<p>There&#8217;s nothing more enjoyable than trading for a living. You basically sit there, and exchange money for other things of value and then back again. Rinse wash  repeat, and you can certainly support yourself taking small profits every so often &#8211; or heavier ones, usually less often!</p>



<p>Eventually, all traders will settle into a routine they&#8217;re comfortable with. They&#8217;ll build up an overall strategy of smaller strategies ranging in complexity and different input variables &#8211; from indicators to position sizing, there&#8217;s a lot to consider!</p>



<p>What&#8217;s important is that it&#8217;s easy to make a day&#8217;s salary in one trade, with very little investment. It&#8217;s also easy &#8211; probably easier &#8211; to lose your entire nest egg in that same day. Remember, invest only what you can afford to lose!</p>



<p>Let&#8217;s discuss a bit about the history of consumer-level trade bots, how trade bots can be used by near-infinite amounts of money by institutions, and how we can make money today using trading bots!</p>



<h2>Historical Trade Bots: Expert Advisors</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://media.fxcm.com/fxpress/fxcmcom/base/page/metatrader-4/carousel-image-1.jpg?fit=cover&amp;auto=webp" alt="Image result for mt4"/></figure>



<p>Most consumer-level brokers over recent years have offered a universal integration for people to day-trade: it&#8217;s called MetaTrader, and most popular of the versions is MetaTrader 4. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://forexmt4ea.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/fdiamond_real_latest2.png" alt="Image result for mt4 ea"/></figure>



<p>It included all sorts of handy features, and could trade anything you could imagine &#8211; from stocks and deriviatives to commodities and forex, it was easy to win or lose quickly and with a laugh or a tear. </p>



<p>One of the most important features you could find was the Expert Advisor. What this was was a way for users &#8211; or developer shops &#8211; to program their own strategies into the machine, allowing it to trade automagically. Even when you were away to the Caribbean or when you were sleeping &#8211; and markets were open &#8211; the expert advisor code would be watching, and reacting to the markets. </p>



<p>You could use all sorts of indicators &#8211; like directional ones like RSI, price ones like VWAP, volatility ones like EWMA, and the list goes on &#8211; and your own variables to manipulate the info and act on your strategies.</p>



<p>This bred a whole new world where people could show off or even sell their Expert Advisors to other people. This marketplace was soon fraught with scams and genuine people trying to help out &#8211; like any other capitalist venue, it&#8217;s as important now as then to always Do Your Own Research before committing funds to anything.</p>



<p>One popular scam was to employ a version of the Martingale Betting System. What this means is that when you lose a bet (or a trade), you double (or increase) your risk so then when you win the next bet (or trade) you earn back everything you lost plus a little extra that you&#8217;ve just now won. Then, when you bet again you start with the base amount again (or less, anyhow) and repeat the process.</p>



<p>This sounds genius &#8211; you&#8217;ll never lose!</p>



<p>In reality, probability works against you and the longer you play this game the more likely it is that you&#8217;ll see a large enough streak of losses to wipe out all your earnings. Neigh, even nations would lose when playing Martingale strategies &#8211; in roulette or in trading. <br><br>Eventually.</p>



<p>Probably.</p>



<p>What this looks like is a smooth chart with minimum drawdown right up until the end event where everything is lost. What this means for an expert advisor developer is that they can have a fantastic, promising looking chart &#8211; even when tested in real-time, with live funds &#8211; and they can promote that using their marketing budget to get many new subscribers. </p>



<p>End event!</p>



<p>I lost my money this way once with an expert advisor&#8230; I learned to not trust backtests, not trust test accounts and only trust my own forward tests &#8211; and remember the first rule: Only invest what you can afford to lose!</p>



<p>Anyways, loads of people earned great money on forex robot trades. Many people still do. You can, too, if you have a good strategy that can&#8217;t easily be duplicated and you maintain your edge over the market. Many more will make money on Expert Advisors, or other forms of trading automation.  </p>



<p>Hooah!</p>



<h2>Robot Traders at Scale: Wall Street</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://timeentertainment.files.wordpress.com/2013/12/twows-02401r.jpg?w=720&amp;h=480&amp;crop=1" alt="Image result for wolf of wall street"/></figure>



<p>Movie theatrics and fiction aside, The Wolf of Wallstreet made all his money by manipulating IPOs that he then controlled a relatively large stake in at arm&#8217;s length. </p>



<p>How does one manipulate IPO prices? One trades. Using many accounts. One trades back and forth, and loses a bit on the fees and the spread but encourages other parties on the market to trade more and more and even influence the price &#8211; at just the right times in just the right increments &#8211; and voila, you&#8217;ve committed securities fraud but you&#8217;re mad rich!</p>



<p>In reality, most of Wall St probably aren&#8217;t committing securities fraud. Probably.</p>



<p>In reality, all of Wall St are using some form of trading automation and high-frequency trading to achieve their goals. Definitely.</p>



<p>By the time any sort of opportunity exists long enough to be traded against, 10s 1000s other parties employing your same or a very like strategy have noticed that opportunity and already traded it. In traditional markets.</p>



<p>How do you react? Be the first. Be the fastest. Poor tens millions dollars into developing faster infrastructure, faster code, and faster trades. Automation and delegation are the keys to success, no?</p>



<p>What this boils down to is that the consumer with their expert advisors and trading terminals on $500 computers instead of $500 000 supercomputers are beaten to the punch by Wall St at every turn.</p>



<p>Darn! All is lost!</p>



<p>No&#8230; Read on!</p>



<h2>Most Profitable Automated Trades: Cryptocurrency</h2>



<p>Where Wall St haven&#8217;t yet conquered the markets &#8211; even better: new markets are introduced daily &#8211; and where market discrepencies even across exchanges offer up opportunities for arbitrage (sure-bet, guaranteed profit.. look into it! Do your own research&#8230; or <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/16/amazon-ebay-aliexpress-retail-arbitrage-as-a-service/">read this article I wrote, it&#8217;s about a retail arbitrage business </a>&#8211; same idea! Buy low sell high!) and the execution times and volumes of big players don&#8217;t necessarily &#8216;own&#8217; the markets?</p>



<p>Bitcoin and cryptocurrency.</p>



<p>Everyone has a fair chance in crypto to earn a dollar &#8211; even though the big boys still spend millions on their trading bots, the little guys control much more of the market share than vs Wall St and traditional markets.</p>



<p>Things like sentiment &#8211; feelings expressed on Twitter &#8211; have a massive, predictable effect on smaller-volume coins. <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/automated-crypto-trading-bot-to-buy-pump-and-dump-sentiment-signals-from-twitter/">Read about my Twitter sentiment bot I&#8217;m presently creating here</a> (it&#8217;s fairly technical &#8211; but gives a good overview!)</p>



<p>All in all, it&#8217;s easier to make a quick buck with less capital on crypto &#8211; reliably, predictably &#8211; than it is in traditional markets.</p>



<p>You can try <a href="https://3commas.io/?c=tc174830">3commas &#8211; where you can automate your favorite strategy</a>, pull in a given strategy from places like TradingView, or subscribe to any number live automated trading strategies. For the win!</p>



<h2>Conclusion</h2>



<p>You, too, can earn with automation! You, too can create or hire someone to create your own trading bots &#8211; for traditional markets, or for cryptocurrencies! You, too, can feel that little joy and hit of dopamine when your trades exit in the green!</p>



<p>Go for it!</p>



<h2>A Plug</h2>



<p>Want to learn about&nbsp;new articles&nbsp;in tech and being a madman? Subscribe to my mailing list here:&nbsp;<a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL">http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</a><br></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Ebay Aliexpress Retail-Arbitrage-As-A-Service</title>
		<link>/2020/01/16/amazon-ebay-aliexpress-retail-arbitrage-as-a-service/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 04:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insanely Marketable Business Ideas]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=222</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster As I detailed in]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p> Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<p>As I detailed in this recent article surrounding <a href="https://jare.cloud/2020/01/15/automated-crypto-trading-bot-to-buy-pump-and-dump-sentiment-signals-from-twitter/">Twitter automation to buy cryptocurrency during pumps</a> and in this way-old Hackernoon and Medium discussing how I once <a href="https://medium.com/@jarettdunn/i-1000th-idea-to-make-money-online-via-python-chained-sqlmaps-8acb25cc9ad8?source=your_stories_page---------------------------">toyed with the morality of ethical hacking for profit</a> &#8211; it&#8217;s obvious that I often have ideas for tech businesses that don&#8217;t really get off the ground. I lack the marketing chops to execute these things, so I&#8217;m going to continue letting you guys know how my Proof of Concepts go and maybe one day some of you can make a living with one of my ideas!</p>



<p>This is another entry in Insanely Marketable Business Ideas. Hooah!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/606522166166421534/667572917105590282/unknown.png" alt=""/><figcaption>Source: My code just a minute ago</figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/606522166166421534/667573207414341633/unknown.png" alt=""/><figcaption>Source: My code a minute after that</figcaption></figure>



<p>What you might notice about these two images is the insanely obvious: if someone were to buy one of these generic handhold consoles on Aliexpress and then sell it on Ebay they could pocket the difference in costs. This is called &#8216;retail arbitrage,&#8217; where retail is what we&#8217;re trading and arbitrage is the act of buying low and immediately selling high. It&#8217;s preferable to sell before you have to buy &#8211; which you can effectively do selling on these marketplaces.</p>



<p>You&#8217;ll notice that I&#8217;m lacking a corresponding Amazon screenshot &#8211; their Product Advertising API requires you to have 3 sales in a certain amount of time as an affiliate before you can have access to the API. D&#8217;oh! I&#8217;ve sent them a message saying I&#8217;m creating a shopping comparison engine &#8211; it might be unwise to say we&#8217;re propagating the arbitrage &#8216;problem.&#8217; Sometimes, people that buy an item on Ebay and receive a package wrapped up by Amazon Fulfillment will become irate they&#8217;ve been the victim of not knowing they can search more than one site, and they might kick up a customer service complaint&#8230;</p>



<p>Either way, there&#8217;s money to be made!</p>



<p>But, that&#8217;s not my idea. That idea&#8217;s been tried and done effectively by many, and you can google for more info. My idea is buried in those screenshots, above, and in my explanation of the Amazon part too &#8211; these are affiliate links. If someone were to visit Aliexpress or Ebay after clicking my link and place an order within a month or a few months, I get a little % kickback from that sale. </p>



<p>In the case of providing this as a service, the model would be that I create a beautiful and effective comparison tool to find the highest potential margins for search results or by the best possible margins in a given category and finding exact (or near-exact by text compare) title matches, then display them in easy-to-organize lists for arbitrageurs to peruse, click the links, buy a bulk order of many items or maybe just an item or two, and as I build my network &#8211; and community &#8211; of arbitrageurs, my income from the % of a % of each initial sale will exponentially increase above and beyond the potential returns from the actual arbitraging. </p>



<p>Retail arbitrage is fraught with potential pitfalls: from max. orders or max. sales, all the way to the customer service burden &#8211; and potential returns, restocking fees or concerns &#8211; it is easy to lose some or all of your profits in a second with retail arbitraging if you&#8217;re not careful. When building a service that provides instant comparisons for the potential arbitrageur &#8211; and a supportive, helpful community of arbitraging friends &#8211; we can ensure the overall success and growth of the operation.</p>



<p>Sunk costs?</p>



<p>Upkeep of servers, initial dev and MARKETING.</p>



<p>Potential upside?</p>



<p>We&#8217;d run the site for free. Everyone can come in and discuss the opportunities of Retail Arbitrage, and use the tool to their heart&#8217;s content. In return, our marketing efforts will reflect the fact that other arbitraging tools require a monthly or yearly subscription &#8211; putting ours leagues ahead of the competition.</p>



<p>Ebay Partner Network pays 1-6% per sale depending on geo, if the sale happens within 24hrs of clicking the link. Aliexpress up to 9%, and Amazon pays up to a walloping 10%! When someone wants to arbitrage again, they&#8217;d certainly want to find a new-and-improved arbitrage deal &#8211; they&#8217;d return to our platform, find a new killer deal, place another order and boombingbang more affiliate income!</p>



<p>NOW, for the win, let&#8217;s review some code.</p>



<p>First, after running npm install for the required packages, we&#8217;ll require them in the code:</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>let eBay = require('ebay-node-api')
var request = require('request')</code></pre>



<p>Next we&#8217;ll instantiate our eBay object, like so:</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>let ebay = new eBay({
    clientID: '',
    env: 'PRODUCTION', // optional default = 'PRODUCTION'
    headers:{ // optional
        'X-EBAY-C-MARKETPLACE-ID': 'EBAY_US' // For Great Britain https://www.ebay.co.uk/
    }
})</code></pre>



<p>Now, I found out that I could use eBay&#8217;s affiliate tools to build an affiliate URL using my account and campaign. Afterwards, I hijack the &amp;mpre= field and replace the item URL with my URL for any given item, to build a new-and-improved eBay aff link for any given URL.</p>



<p>For fun and profit, we set our eBay affiliate URL &#8216;template&#8217; as well as our hard-coded search term:</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>var template = 'http://rover.ebay.com/rover/1/706-53473-19255-0/1?ff3=4&amp;pub=5575480811&amp;toolid=10001&amp;campid=5338476385&amp;customid=&amp;mpre='
var search = '500in1 nes'</code></pre>



<p>In our ebaydo function, we search eBay products using the eBay node package and loop over the resulting json. The url for the item is parsed then encoded, and we create our affiliate URL by joining our template from above with this new encoded item&#8217;s url. </p>



<p>Voila! Paydirt!</p>



<p>We log to console the network, affiliate URL, title, and price object for fun and profit. If there&#8217;s an error, let&#8217;s also log the error! Debugging is fun, right?</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>function ebaydo(keywords) {

    ebay.findItemsByKeywords({
        keywords: keywords
    }).then((data) => {
        for (var item in data[0].searchResult[0].item) {
            url = encodeURIComponent(data[0].searchResult[0].item[item].viewItemURL[0])
            url = template + url
            console.log('ebay:')
            console.log('affiliate url: ' + url)
            console.log(data[0].searchResult[0].item[item].title[0])
            console.log(data[0].searchResult[0].item[item].sellingStatus[0].currentPrice[0])
            console.log(' ')
        }
    }, (error) => {
        console.log(error);
    });
}</code></pre>



<p>The ali function is more complicated. First, we&#8217;ll get and parse the current time into url-encoded string. Phew, that took a lot of Googling to figure out&#8230;</p>



<p>Next, we&#8217;ll encode our keywords. That probably means some handy %20s (spaces). Then, we load a list of products based on those keywords from Alibaba&#8217;s API, parse the result into json, loop over the products and save some useful info to vars for later. We&#8217;ll take note of the price, product url, image url (why not? Should have done this for eBay too! People can compare the images when finding their like products&#8230;) and product title. Next, we send some of these vars off to a separate function.</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>function ali(keywords) {
    var time = new Date();
    var time2 = (time.getHours().toString() + "%20" + time.getMinutes().toString() + "%20" + time.getSeconds().toString());
    keywords = encodeURIComponent(keywords)

    var url = "http://gw.api.alibaba.com/openapi/param2/2/portals.open/api.listPromotionProduct/76080?sort=volumeDown&amp;fields=salePrice,productTitle,volume,imageUrl,productUrl&amp;keywords=" + keywords;
    console.log('keywords?: ' + url);
    var responses = new Array();
    try {
        var result2 = request.get(url, function(e, r, result2) {
            var json = JSON.parse(result2)
            if (json.result != null) {
                for (var i in json.result.products) {
                    console.log(json.result.products[i]);
                    var price = json.result.products[i].salePrice;
                    var id = json.result.products[i].productUrl;
                    var img = json.result.products[i].imageUrl;
                    var title = json.result.products[i].productTitle;

                    
                    dosearchurl(id, title, img, price)
                }
            } 
        })
    } catch (e) {
        console.log('exception: ' + e.toString());
    }
}
</code></pre>



<p>In dosearchurl, this genius technique allows me to have the variables persistent over the next request.get call, which returns a promise, meaning that if we did request.get inside a for loop then tried to access our old variables (like title in this case, for example) it would only find the variable value at the state in the new point in time when the promise has resolved (ie. the request completes) &#8211; meaning all our results would output the same data as the for loop has completed and it executes the console.log code with the for loops final value, instead of each incremented value.</p>



<p>So, by taking the for loop and feeding it the variables in a different scope, the variables remain persistent even though there&#8217;s a time delay for the promise &#8211; and we can output the variables in their proper sequence, instead of only the final one over and over again.</p>



<p>In here, we load the product id on another alibaba api endpoint &#8211; this one to create an affiliate url for our product we&#8217;ve found. Then, we output to console all the juicey details about our potential arbitrageur&#8217;s opportunity &#8211; and our potential affiliate income.</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>function dosearchurl(id, title, img, price) {
    var url2 = "http://gw.api.alibaba.com/openapi/param2/2/portals.open/api.getPromotionLinks/76080?fields=promotionUrl&amp;trackingId=4632&amp;urls=" + id;
    var responses = new Array();
    try {
        var result3 = request.get(url2, function(e, r, result3) {

            var json = JSON.parse(result3)
            console.log('aliexpress:')
            console.log('title: ' + title.replace(/&lt;[^>]*>?/gm, ''))
            console.log('affiliate url: ' + json.result.promotionUrls[0].promotionUrl);
            console.log('img: ' + img)
            console.log('price: ' + price)
            console.log(' ')

        });

    } catch (e) {
        console.log('exception: ' + e.toString());
    }
}</code></pre>



<p>It&#8217;s a win-win-win: goldmoney for the arbitrageur who earns surebet money, paydirt for me as I gain a tiny percent of those sales over and over again, and of course it&#8217;s a good thing &#8211; big bucks &#8211; for the retail marketplace. Hooah!</p>



<p>I hope you&#8217;re as excited about my POC as I was creating it then describing it here. Someone will surely bet some time and effort and marketing chops to execute this vision.. will it be me?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Automated Crypto Trading Bot to Buy Pump and Dump Sentiment Signals from Twitter</title>
		<link>/2020/01/15/automated-crypto-trading-bot-to-buy-pump-and-dump-sentiment-signals-from-twitter/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 21:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Github]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=202</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View This Article in it&#8217;s Original Form on Jare.Cloud! Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="/2020/01/15/automated-crypto-trading-bot-to-buy-pump-and-dump-sentiment-signals-from-twitter/">View This Article in it&#8217;s Original Form on Jare.Cloud</a>!</p>



<p> Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<h2>Strategy</h2>



<ol><li>We follow Twitter accounts we trust: exchanges, coins, Twitter crypto influencers</li><li>We wait around until someone tweets a coin name or coin ticker</li><li>We measure the sentiment of the message: is it buy or sell?</li><li>On strong buys, or multiple instances of buys in a period of time, we execute a market buy order on Binance Spot</li><li>We wait around until our exits are hit</li><li>1 out of every 3-4 signals we act on the crowd will also act on&#8230; </li><li>&#8230;meaning there&#8217;s upwards potential for everyone</li><li>and we can net 100s 1000s% gains!</li></ol>



<p>In practice:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-10.png" alt="" class="wp-image-205" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-10.png 862w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-10-300x289.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-10-768x739.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 862px) 100vw, 862px" /><figcaption> <br></figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://media.discordapp.net/attachments/666371834102677565/667093503817547794/tempFileForShare_20200115-205117.jpg?width=340&amp;height=659" alt=""/></figure>



<h2>NLTK &amp; New Words</h2>



<p>The Python programming language has a package called Natural Language Tool Kit, or NLTK. Inside NLTK are lexicons that you can use to accomplish different goals &#8211; in our project, the Vader Lexicon is useful because we can rank all sorts of English words on a scale of -1 to 1 based on how strongly they express good or bad emotions. This is called &#8216;sentiment analysis.&#8217;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-8.png" alt="" class="wp-image-203" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-8.png 451w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-8-300x199.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-8-120x80.png 120w" sizes="(max-width: 451px) 100vw, 451px" /></figure>



<p>We add some new words to the mix.. given our very specific scenario.</p>



<h2>Weighted Twitter Accounts and Tiers</h2>



<p>Of the accounts in our followed list, we&#8217;ll have exchanges, coins and crypto influencers. Of these, exchanges have the highest amount of influence when they make an announcement about an alt, the coins themselves have a medium amount and the influencers have a variable but usually less amount.</p>



<p>We organize each account we follow (or simply have in a static list) into a list with corresponding ratios for how they affect our sentiment scores. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-9.png" alt="" class="wp-image-204" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-9.png 304w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-9-300x128.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 304px) 100vw, 304px" /></figure>



<h2>Parsing and Referencing All the Binance Spot Coins</h2>



<p>Here&#8217;s what Binance&#8217;s 24hr ticker endpoint looks like:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-11.png" alt="" class="wp-image-206" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-11.png 649w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-11-217x300.png 217w" sizes="(max-width: 649px) 100vw, 649px" /></figure>



<p>We loop through all these results, look for ones that end in BTC and then replace the BTC out of the symbol string &#8211; leaving the coin. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12-1024x172.png" alt="" class="wp-image-207" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12-1024x172.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12-300x50.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12-768x129.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12-1536x258.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-12.png 1890w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>We now have a list of coins!</p>



<h2>Get Twitter Followed, 100 Recent Tweets Within Last Hour</h2>



<p>This is optional and I may replace the followed list with a flat and static file or coded list, but presently the bot will read the followed list and then loop through it, grabbing everyone&#8217;s 100 most recent tweets (and and/or and not retweets &#8211; optional) and then cycle through those to see which occurred in the last (given timeframe). These are the goldmoney&#8230; we save tweets we&#8217;ve previously indexed to an array so as to not re-index them.</p>



<h2>Find Potential Coinnames, Compare to Our Binance List and Tweeter List</h2>



<p>We split the text of the tweets up by &#8216; &#8216; (space) and &#8216;\n&#8217; (newline). We then look at each resulting word or hashtag, capitalize them and compare them (or $ + the word, like $MANA or $mana or mana or Mana) against our list of tickers from the Binance API. We also then compare against a list of tickers that correspond to specific Twitter accounts, in the event of something like the MANA tweet above that didn&#8217;t mention &#8216;MANA.&#8217; So we can tell that decentraland tweets are, usually, unless otherwise specified, for MANA.</p>



<h2>For High Sentiment Scores, Buy</h2>



<p>On Binance we market buy with a % of our holdings. The % is configurable, and depends on someone&#8217;s aversion to risk.</p>



<h2>For Repeat Occurrences, Buy Again</h2>



<p>If another one of our trusted tweeters tweets another signal confirming the same trend, we &#8216;double down&#8217; and buy another % of remaining balance worth of the coin.</p>



<h2>1% Trailing Take Profit</h2>



<p>If the price immediately drops 1%, we gracefully exit as a stoploss and count our losses. If the price goes up 2% and then down 1%, we exit the trade at 1% gains less fees. If, however, the coin goes up 10% 40% 100% before dropping 1% &#8211; as it might do with mass hysteria &#8211; then we laugh all the way to the bank! 1%, of course, is configurable.</p>



<h2>Rinse, Wash, Repeat</h2>



<p>Another signal another coin another potential 100%!</p>



<h2>Considerations</h2>



<p>We want to use a custom list of crypto influencers because most of the people calling out signals on twitter are actually doing so in their own vested interest &#8211; having posted a buy signal in their private Pump &amp; Dump discords, their private group buys up the coin and then &#8211; 5 minutes later &#8211; they all post signals to their twitters and bought &#8216;influencer&#8217; twitters as tweets that seem to double, triply, quadruply confirm each other. In reality, these folks are dumping by the time anyone else starts to buy in &#8211; meaning that you&#8217;d likely face losses if you used a twitter-wide sentiment analysis and automated trading tool. This is where all existing tools &#8211; including AI-driven ones &#8211; fail in this space, and why my bot has a considerable edge on the competition.</p>



<h2>Next Steps</h2>



<p>I&#8217;d like the bot to keep track of the win/lose rate and severity of wins/losses from specific tweeters, so that it can potentially modify the sentiment score by a previous success factor &#8211; so if someone was right about a buy signal 2/5 times it&#8217;s worth more than someone with 1/5 times. If someone is right 1/10 times, though, and their signal does 25x better than the first two in these examples &#8211; that one is worth considerably more.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-13-1024x629.png" alt="" class="wp-image-208" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-13-1024x629.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-13-300x184.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-13-768x471.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2020/01/image-13.png 1471w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>It&#8217;d be nice to incorporate a python django webserver like a hackathon starter so I can take advantage of their Twitter oauth2 sign-in scheme. This way I can potentially have accounts log in without supplying their own twitter API credentials &#8211; which require an application process now &#8211; and more accounts can work with my bot. This would increase the amount of actionable data and win/loss rates and severities that can be used to package tailored lists of tweeters to know.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Simple Terms: Risk-Free (Free Money!) Futures Trading by Leveraging Options Strategy</title>
		<link>/2020/01/14/in-simple-terms-risk-free-free-money-futures-trading-by-leveraging-options-strategy/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 01:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=176</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[View this content in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud! Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1575/1*wQN_FGI4ff7a26rJBS45Og.jpeg" alt=""/></figure>



<p><a href="http://jare.cloud/2020/01/14/in-simple-terms-risk-free-free-money-futures-trading-by-leveraging-options-strategy/">View this content in it&#8217;s original form, on jare.cloud</a>!</p>



<p> Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<h1 id="4def">Introduction</h1>



<p>In short: using an options strategy, we can trade any sideways futures strategy with absolutely 0 risk. Price movements up, down, or sideways all yield profitable results. Markets go bullish, bearish, sideways or do a dance  you win no matter what!</p>



<p>Awhile ago, on my Hackernoon, I penned this technical article on&nbsp;<a href="https://hackernoon.com/risk-free-futures-market-making-by-hedging-long-straddle-options-pc1236bl" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Risk-Free Futures Market Making by Hedging Long Straddle Options</a>. In this article I will strive to deliver the points discussed in that first article to a less technical audience  who might be left scratching their heads.</p>



<p>What I mean by sideways is that the futures strategy wants to earn the best it can when the markets are neither upwards (bullish) or downwards (bearish).</p>



<h1 id="3b67">Options Strategy</h1>



<p>Places like Deribit via&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/c1bc81c4789b?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Deribit</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/c1bc81c4789b?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Deribit</a>&nbsp;(yes, two separate accounts) and Binances JEX platform via&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/57600910a883?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Binance</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/590e572dc6e7?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Miko Ilas</a>&nbsp;allow you to buy and sell BTC (and other coins) options. An option is a deriviative, meaning that its value is derived from the underlying asset but not necessarily correlated  theres loads of other deriviatives, like futures, and thats why we can trade with so much more leverage on options and futures  theyre not representing the actual asset, but an derived idea.</p>



<p>When you buy a call and a put youre buying the right or ability to buy or sell (respectively) an underlying asset for the specified quantity and price sometime in the future. In European options, this point in the future is only on the day the options expire  or when they run out of time. Note that Im not obligated to buy or sell  I simply have the right to, should I want to (or it makes financial sense). This means that (if I pay enough money, and someone is there to sell me this option) I should be able to buy the ABILITY to buy BTC for $1 sometime within the next month. Thats probably going to be a very lucrative deal, right? Thats why this option would be worth A LOT of money, and probably astronomically expensive to buy. The price at which you may buy or sell the underlying in the future is called the strike.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/2118/1*_Ox5mK27cfvVSMM-VMvZhA.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>In the above screenshot, we see the calls and puts for BTC should the underlying index reach a price of $6750 on expiry or $6500 on expiry. Not that the price of the calls  the right to buy the asset  increases as the strike price decreases, while the cost of puts is decreasing along with it.</p>



<p>On the other side of potential prices for BTC on 24 Jan 2020 (the date the options expire, or end), we see the opposite effect.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/2128/1*90q1y2_UhEPPSN60AfcKew.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Calls are cheaper, puts are more expensive.</p>



<p>Anyways, to get to my point  if you buy both a call and a put with two different strike prices at the same expiry, then you can do so for&nbsp;<em>VERY&nbsp;</em>cheap.</p>



<p>What happens if the price remains around the same? The value of both the call and the put will reduce over time (as their distance to expiry is one of the things that gives them value  the uncertainty and possibility of volatility in this case means that theyre worth more now than they are tomorrow). Eventually, by expiry, they expire worthless.</p>



<p>What happens if the price goes up? The value of the put goes down, and the call goes up. The more the price moves upwards, the less the put is worth  all the way down to worthless  while the call increases in value&nbsp;<em>EXPONENTIALLY</em>.</p>



<p>What happens if the price goes down? The&nbsp;<em>OPPOSITE</em>. One $0 and the other gains value&nbsp;<em>EXPONENTIALLY</em>.</p>



<p>This options strategy is called a long straddle, and it essentially means youre betting on the price moving up or down by a large amount. Its handy in markets you expect to be volatile  like stocks on days they report earnings or, much less likely in practice, youre aware of someones unannounced merger and acquisition. What this also means is that cryptocurrencies  arguably the most volatile of the assets  allow an options trader to reap in the benefits of a highly volatile market.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1680/1*YnzM0Mta90lpGCtm-wzjKg.jpeg" alt=""/></figure>



<p>For instance, we know that Bitcoins mining yields will be half what they have been for awhile sometime in the not-so-distant future. We can surely bet that the price will either go up or down&nbsp;<em>drastically</em>&nbsp;in a short period of time. Take out a long straddle!</p>



<p>Anyways, the above article I wrote on Hackernoon goes on to say that you can use some smart guys math to guesstimate the potential future fair value for these long straddles. Theres a few smart guys to choose from, I chose Black Scholes. Now we have a programmatic way to say hey if price moves 5% then I can expect my long straddle to be worth x% more, their math model solves for x.</p>



<p>Now, where long straddles lose money is when the markets are sideways. I actually found this strategy when I was dreaming up ways to have less risk with my sideways market trading strategies  be they market makers, for instance, they lose money when the markets go up and down and theyre caught holding a bag of $$ that takes away all my yields.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/974/1*OeEhtZQFJ88ZqAvFzTlVjQ.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>These Market Makers make $$ when the markets are sideways, by earning on $ fees and $ spread. On Deribit,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/94b52ae5502e?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">BitMEX</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/b7ff9821c710?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bybit</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/724240b60d22?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Bitfinex</a>&nbsp;Kraken and&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/u/316a1a75d708?source=post_page-----5018feca9791----------------------" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">CoinFLEX</a>&nbsp;they give you REBATES on fees you can earn when people trade against your orders. When you add liquidity to their exchanges, they split their earnings with you  sometimes 50/50!</p>



<p>This means that if I was to know that my max exposure is (how many positions of what sizes I might hold if the markets go one way or another) in $$ and if the market moves y% at 6x leverage, I then liquidate at y%. This is normally bad, but</p>



<p>I can buy the exact (or almost exact) number puts/calls I need to make sure that if price goes up OR down by any % all the way up to liquidation % then Im making money on my long straddle when Im losing money on my Market Maker.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://miro.medium.com/max/1096/1*f-8ikqYVWMFzCSgXAEthng.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>This applies to any strategy that generates yield when sideways, not just market makers. Say price goes up 5% in a day and my sideways strategy liquidates, and out of my puts and calls one of them is $0 and the other one increased in value&nbsp;<em>A WHOLE HECK OF A LOT.</em></p>



<p>The only way this doesnt work is if your sideways strategy doesnt earn more than what you lose when you hold onto the long straddles and their value goes down over time</p>



<p><em>!! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a></p>



<p><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization  where were setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the worlds greater humanitarian issues.</em></p>



<p><em>Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;!!</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Benefits of Neomenia and Crypto Growth Hacker &#8211; Compound Your Crypto!</title>
		<link>/2019/12/23/benefits-of-neomenia-and-crypto-growth-hacker-compound-your-crypto/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 11:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=146</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster Hi SteemIt! View this]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p> Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<p>Hi SteemIt! View this post in it&#8217;s <a href="http://dunncreativess.github.io/2019/12/23/benefits-of-neomenia-and-crypto-growth-hacker-compound-your-crypto/">original form on dunncreativess.github.io</a>! View my <a href="https://hackernoon.com/@jare">other posts on Hackernoon.</a> Yes I&#8217;m promoting this post &#8211; I think I have some info you folks might appreciate!</p>



<p>With results among users ranging from 3-4%, and a total net returns for some users at 16-22+% over a few days, it looks as though Neomenia is here to make an improvement in people&#8217;s lives.</p>



<p>Trading on three exchanges simultaneously and hedging risk by altering strategies based on conditions on a given exchange, it looks like Crypto Growth Hacker is the one-stop-shop for crypto investment diversification.</p>



<p>Neomenia now supports trailing takeprofit, meaning the upwards potential of a good buy or sell has increased significantly with your configurable takeprofit. It also has a special feature where the stop size is reduced by the difference in price as a percent when it moves in the right direction, so that you can lock in your profits faster while having a larger stoploss in case sh#t hits the fan.</p>



<p>The win/lose ratio is 5:1&#8230; and <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/XBTUSD/FkIqJJcy-Introducing-Neomenia/">it backtested 10 000% on TradingView</a>.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s a price action observed in one spot confirmed in another confirmed again by a direcitonal indicator, and that&#8217;s all I&#8217;m allowed saying under NDA.. but if you want to know more, join the Neomenia chat on Telegram! <a href="https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A">https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-1024x408.png" alt="" class="wp-image-149" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-1024x408.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-300x119.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-768x306.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1-1536x611.png 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn110-1.png 1874w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Crypto Growth Hacker is indexing Bitmex, Deribit and Binance Futures now and using a complex market making strategy on the first two while employing Neomenia on the third. The result is a bot that&#8217;s incredibly resilient and doesn&#8217;t take very many hits that last too too long &#8211; and shows steady gains.</p>



<p>Want to know more? Join our Telegram! <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-148" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1.png 880w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1-300x163.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1-768x416.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 880px) 100vw, 880px" /></figure>



<p>What&#8217;s great about both offerings is the community. We have scores of new users &#8211; and scores of people supporting us through thick and thin &#8211; and that all starts with posts like these, to raise awareness.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4-498x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-150" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4-498x1024.png 498w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4-146x300.png 146w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-4.png 622w" sizes="(max-width: 498px) 100vw, 498px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5-498x1024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-151" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5-498x1024.png 498w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5-146x300.png 146w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/image-5.png 622w" sizes="(max-width: 498px) 100vw, 498px" /></figure>



<p>We&#8217;re helping each other, and helping ourselves. You&#8217;re more than welcome to join! We&#8217;d be happy to have you. Ask questions! Grow with us!</p>



<p>We also have attractive referral campaigns for those of you who have an audience or know the inner workings of the magical internet.. ask us how to get 10% of your referral&#8217;s profits, or a straight (and recurring.. ) fee!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-147" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1.png 899w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1-288x300.png 288w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1-768x800.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 899px) 100vw, 899px" /></figure>



<p><a href="https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A">Neomenia Telegram</a></p>



<p><a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">Crypto Growth Hacker Telegram</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Week of Neomenia LIVE Trading Binance Futures</title>
		<link>/2019/12/18/a-week-of-neomenia-live-trading-binance-futures/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=140</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster Neomenia is currently running]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1024x635.png" alt="" class="wp-image-141" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-1024x635.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-300x186.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1-768x476.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn1.png 1276w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p> Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<p>Neomenia is currently running on 8 subscriber&#8217;s accounts, creating predictable yield in sideways or bullish or bearish markets! </p>



<p>The strategy itself is protected under NDA, but as much as I can say it finds price indication in one place confirms it in another then also confirms with directional indication. The result is magic!</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1024x692.png" alt="" class="wp-image-142" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-1024x692.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-300x203.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-768x519.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1-120x80.png 120w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1.png 1224w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>I&#8217;ve created a web interface to launch bots on our own Google Cloud Compute account, taking the hassle and potential issues with configuring your own VPS with bot options straight off your shoulders.. and as it costs us a pretty penny a month, and saves you renting your own VPS, it&#8217;s basically a free VPS giveaway! Woot!</p>



<p>I&#8217;m writing an update predominantly to create FOMO, but the community results speak for themselves&#8230;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-143" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-1.png 626w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-1-300x124.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 626px) 100vw, 626px" /></figure>



<p>The price of the bot will increase from $49 or $59 (depending if you use our Binance Futures referral code) up to minimum $99 in the new year. The time to come onboard is now! Have no fear, our team and community moderators have your back through thick and thin.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn4.png" alt="" class="wp-image-144" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn4.png 606w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn4-300x137.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 606px) 100vw, 606px" /></figure>



<p>So &#8211; come on in, grab it while it&#8217;s cheap!</p>



<p>There are other monetization methods for people who otherwise have no access to futures, join <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> and check out the pin!</p>



<p>Interested in Neomenia? Join here! <a href="https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A">https://t.me/joinchat/G3tz4RdZGmNdxs9vXdum7A</a></p>



<p><em>! Click here to subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>Be notified about new articles? Welcome to the Jarett Dunn email subscriber list! Each new signup will receive a link to download the Coindex Labs non-NDA teaser, which includes information about the value proposition for my organization  where were setting our sights first on a money-printing machine, then returning later as conquering heroes in order to then defeat the worlds greater humanitarian issues.Remember to CLICK, subscribe:</em><a href="http://eepurl.com/gIykNL"><em>&nbsp;http://eepurl.com/gIykNL</em></a><em>&nbsp;!!</em>(<strong>Disclaimer</strong>:&nbsp;<em>The Author is the Chief Liquidity Officer at Coindex</em>) </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trade Smarter, Trade Together! Crypto Growth Hacker Crowdfunded Bot Tokens to Mint</title>
		<link>/2019/12/14/trade-smarter-trade-together-crypto-growth-hacker-crowdfunded-bot-tokens-to-mint/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 02:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jare]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bots]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=134</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster I&#8217;m offering my market]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1024x612.png" alt="" class="wp-image-135" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-1024x612.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-300x179.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2-768x459.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn2.png 1452w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p> Join our growing Telegram community for blog updates, bot chat, general fun and crypto madness? <a href="https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster">https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</a> </p>



<p>I&#8217;m offering my market maker bot one of two possible ways: 1. I provide you the source code and you can configure your apikey and secret and review the code to make sure nothing malicious happens, on a profit-share scheme where you provide 40% of the earnings after every month &#8211; as confirmed by API. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3.png" alt="" class="wp-image-136" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3.png 1000w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-300x296.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/12/hn3-768x759.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></figure>



<p>2. I&#8217;m creating a dividend token for sale to the general public (including Americans) that I then pay monthly 70% of the profit (10% for me, 15% reinvested for compounding effect, 5% BNB holdings). The dividend trading fund would span multiple bots, with an initial spread of 25% Neomenia BTC 25% Neomenia ETH 25% Deribit arb + options BTC 25% Eth. The dividend token script I&#8217;m using doesn&#8217;t have voting, but we&#8217;ll vote on bot % holdings and bot strategies using an off-chain voting system enabled by etherscan reports on holding %, anything more than 5% gets a vote.</p>



<p>The benefits of option 1 is that you get to run one of my bots with a profit-share model, the benefits of option 2 are: a. if you&#8217;re an american citizen you can now kindof take part in leveraged futures trading, by way of the token. b. as our BNB accumulates, we pay less fees c. as our BNB accumulates, we get more % from our referrals d. the combined notional traded on Binance will allow us to further climb their fee ladder. You can also refer people to the crowdfunded bot, for every 100 tokens at $1 worth of Eth apiece minted you get 10 tokens. For every 100 tokens that a referral of your referral mints you get 5 tokens.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-imgur wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-imgur"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="imgur-embed-pub" lang="en" data-id="PBQZAB1"><a href="https://imgur.com/PBQZAB1">View post on imgur.com</a></blockquote><script async src="//s.imgur.com/min/embed.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<ol><li>Join Telegram https://t.me/ManyVolumeSignalMonster</li><li>Fill out this form.</li><li>Send your Eth here: 0x9c33b574c8D013Ba501a897484E3b92a27A3FDB8</li><li>Fill the TXID in this form.</li><li>Tokens will be minted as often as possible, with the least often being once a month before dividends are paid.</li></ol>



<p>Form to fill: https://forms.gle/bDQmuUhQQ5FJPvgN6</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
